1-6	O	-
-	O	-
6	O	-

Santan	B-PER	European
from	O	-
the	O	-
V-V	B-LOC	European
x	O	-
AJ	B-PER	European

Man	O	-
mystic	O	-
with	O	-
the	O	-
pen	O	-
like	O	-
J	B-PER	European
.	I-PER	European
K	I-PER	European

True	O	-
say	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
ain't	O	-
really	O	-
a	O	-
drinker	O	-

But	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
love	O	-
for	O	-
brandy	B-MISC	European
like	O	-
Ray	B-PER	North America
J	I-PER	European

Champagne	O	-
popper	O	-
,	O	-
.	O	-
44	O	-
chopper	B-MISC	North America

In	O	-
a	O	-
black	O	-
Nike	B-ORG	North America
bomber	O	-
,	O	-
heartbeat	O	-
stopper	O	-

Half-heart	O	-
MC	B-MISC	North America
dropper	O	-

.	O	-
45	O	-
wapper	O	-
,	O	-
leave	O	-
you	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
states	O	-
like	O	-
Kaká	B-PER	Latin

AJ	B-PER	European
from	O	-
the	O	-
l-l	B-LOC	
x	O	-
Santan	B-PER	European

Man's	O	-
got	O	-
style	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
riddim	B-MISC	North America
like	O	-
Gangnam	B-MISC	Eastern Asian

Two	O	-
young	O	-
bruddas	B-MISC	European
tryna	O	-
eat	O	-
off	O	-
of	O	-
music	O	-

But	O	-
we	O	-
used	O	-
to	O	-
eat	O	-
off	O	-
of	O	-
pebs	O	-
and	O	-
the	O	-
sand	O	-
bags	O	-

Now	O	-
we	O	-
get	O	-
money	O	-
,	O	-
music	O	-
money	O	-

Money	O	-
that	O	-
could	O	-
put	O	-
your	O	-
girlfriend	O	-
in	O	-
a	O	-
handbag	O	-

White	O	-
tee	O	-
,	O	-
Balenciagas	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
man	O	-
bag	O	-

Left-winger	O	-
with	O	-
a	O	-
long	O	-
stick	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
granddad	O	-

AJ	B-PER	European
Tizzy	I-PER	European
from	O	-
T-H	B-LOC	European
-	O	-
E	O	-
lizzy	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
all	O	-
out	O	-
for	O	-
the	O	-
Lizzy	B-PER	European

I	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
look	O	-
like	O	-
you	O	-
,	O	-
you're	O	-
broke	O	-

And	O	-
I've	O	-
been	O	-
telling	O	-
broke	O	-
bruddas	O	-
"	O	-
move	O	-
"	O	-
like	O	-
Grizzy	B-PER	European

Still	O	-
brandy	B-MISC	European
but	O	-
the	O	-
hand	O	-
ting	O	-
fizzy	O	-

Probs	O	-
be	O	-
in	O	-
bin	O	-
if	O	-
a	O	-
man	O	-
weren't	O	-
busy	O	-

I'm	O	-
a	O	-
mic	O	-
king	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
a	O	-
king	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
mic	O	-

And	O	-
I'll	O	-
spin	O	-
bruddas	O	-
til	O	-
the	O	-
whole	O	-
scene	O	-
gets	O	-
dizzy	O	-

Walk	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
rave	O	-
,	O	-
smile	O	-
on	O	-
my	O	-
face	O	-

Drink	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
cup	O	-
,	O	-
hand	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
jeans	O	-

Man	O	-
talk	O	-
tough	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-
look	O	-
up	O	-
,	O	-
down	O	-
,	O	-
left	O	-
,	O	-
right	O	-

Straight	O	-
to	O	-
a	O	-
bang	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
teeth	O	-

Man	O	-
still	O	-
talk	O	-
tough	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-
saw	O	-
man	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
flesh	O	-

Now	O	-
man's	O	-
tryna	O	-
talk	O	-
to	O	-
my	O	-
Gs	B-MISC	North America

Nah	O	-
,	O	-
none	O	-
of	O	-
that	O	-
,	O	-
none	O	-
,	O	-
.	O	-
45	O	-
drum	O	-

Run	O	-
you	O	-
right	O	-
out	O	-
of	O	-
your	O	-
street	O	-

Walk	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
dance	O	-
,	O	-
chicks	O	-
wanna	O	-
glance	O	-

Hand	O	-
on	O	-
my	O	-
hip	O	-
,	O	-
shank	B-MISC	European
for	O	-
the	O	-
dip	O	-

If	O	-
I	O	-
shout	O	-
"	O	-
oi	O	-
"	O	-
,	O	-
them	O	-
man	O	-
there	O	-
best	O	-
skip	O	-

Better	O	-
tie	O	-
up	O	-
your	O	-
laces	O	-
tight	O	-
and	O	-
don't	O	-
trip	O	-

Trip	O	-
,	O	-
get	O	-
splashed	O	-

Couldn't	O	-
care	O	-
less	O	-
about	O	-
my	O	-
man's	O	-
gang	B-MISC	North America

We're	O	-
not	O	-
fam	B-MISC	European
,	O	-
we're	O	-
not	O	-
friends	O	-
or	O	-
bredrins	B-MISC	European

You'll	O	-
get	O	-
tanned	O	-
and	O	-
binned	B-MISC	European
,	O	-
cock	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
blam	O	-

Santan	B-PER	European
Dave	I-PER	European
from	O	-
the	O	-
Vale	B-LOC	European
and	O	-
Tracey	B-PER	European

Duck	O	-
man	O	-
down	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
road	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
pacey	O	-

Two	O	-
lighties	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
phone	O	-
,	O	-
so	O	-
facety	O	-

One	O	-
named	O	-
Jordan	B-PER	North American
and	O	-
one	O	-
named	O	-
Stacey	B-PER	North American

S	O	-
with	O	-
the	O	-
S	O	-
from	O	-
the	O	-
S	O	-
,	O	-
ask	O	-
Showkey	B-PER	European

Dust	O	-
man	O	-
down	O	-
with	O	-
a	O	-
mask	O	-
like	O	-
Tobi	B-PER	European

Tell	O	-
a	O	-
boy	O	-
cotch	O	-
,	O	-
my	O	-
man's	O	-
telling	O	-
me	O	-
lots	O	-

But	O	-
we	O	-
are	O	-
not	O	-
Gs	B-MISC	North America
so	O	-
don't	O	-
watch	O	-
my	O	-
face	O	-

Ladbroke	B-LOC	European
Grove	I-LOC	European
is	O	-
where	O	-
I	O	-
re	O	-
-	O	-
who	O	-
?	O	-

Man	O	-
get	O	-
burst	O	-
up	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
G	B-MISC	North America
-	O	-
who	O	-
?	O	-

Came	O	-
back	O	-
with	O	-
a	O	-
fresh	O	-
one	O	-
,	O	-
it's	O	-
new	O	-

Don't	O	-
come	O	-
around	O	-
for	O	-
a	O	-
two	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
blue	O	-

I	O	-
don't	O	-
give	O	-
a	O	-
fuck	O	-
if	O	-
you're	O	-
old	O	-
or	O	-
new	O	-

I'll	O	-
just	O	-
yawn	O	-
like	O	-
"	O	-
blackball	O	-
who	O	-
?	O	-
"	O	-

Put	O	-
a	O	-
couple	O	-
dead	O	-
MCs	B-MISC	North America
in	O	-
the	O	-
grave	O	-

Trust	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
darg	B-MISC	European
,	O	-
you	O	-
can	O	-
go	O	-
there	O	-
too	O	-

Trust	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
darg	B-MISC	European
,	O	-
you	O	-
can	O	-
go	O	-
there	O	-
free	O	-

I	O	-
don't	O	-
ever	O	-
watch	O	-
F-A	O	-
-	O	-
C-E	O	-

AJT	B-PER	European
from	O	-
MTP	O	-

NikeLab	B-ORG	North America
tracksuit	O	-
,	O	-
Nike	B-ORG	North America
ID	O	-

Man	O	-
got	O	-
overly	O	-
fucked	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
beef	O	-

Pretty	O	-
sure	O	-
I	O	-
landed	O	-
a	O	-
bang	O	-
to	O	-
his	O	-
teeth	O	-

Man	O	-
will	O	-
get	O	-
banged	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
face	O	-
by	O	-
me	O	-

Not	O	-
my	O	-
bredrin	B-MISC	European
,	O	-
banged	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
face	O	-
by	O	-
me	O	-

And	O	-
me	O	-

Man	O	-
talk	O	-
tough	O	-
,	O	-
we'll	O	-
see	O	-

Hit	O	-
him	O	-
with	O	-
the	O	-
left-right	O	-
,	O	-
left-right	O	-
,	O	-
left-right	O	-
-	O	-
right	O	-

One	O	-
jab	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
I	O	-
duck	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
weave	O	-

Come	O	-
like	O	-
Trevor	B-MISC	North America
from	O	-
GTA	B-ORG	North America

If	O	-
I	O	-
bang	O	-
man's	O	-
face	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-
bop	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
lean	O	-

Kun	B-PER	Latin
Aguero	I-PER	Latin
,	O	-
man	O	-
dropped	O	-
the	O	-
shoulder	O	-
feint	O	-
once	O	-

Quick	O	-
kick	O	-
then	O	-
I	O	-
drop	O	-
man's	O	-
G	B-MISC	North America

First	O	-
time	O	-
I	O	-
link	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
Nando's	B-ORG	African
,	O	-
sweet	O	-

£	O	-
9	O	-
.	O	-
95	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
swipe	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
eat	O	-

I	O	-
one-two	O	-
rap	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
give	O	-
hat	O	-

Thiago	B-PER	Latin
Silva	I-PER	Latin
,	O	-
man	O	-
block	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
skeet	O	-

Had	O	-
man	O	-
screaming	O	-
"	O	-
look	O	-
,	O	-
there's	O	-
my	O	-
man	O	-
"	O	-

Hand	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
pouch	O	-
like	O	-
"	O	-
where	O	-
?	O	-
It's	O	-
not	O	-
me	O	-
"	O	-

Hand	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
pouch	O	-
like	O	-
"	O	-
where	O	-
?	O	-
It's	O	-
not	O	-
us	O	-
"	O	-

Turned	O	-
to	O	-
my	O	-
G	B-MISC	North America
like	O	-
"	O	-
where	O	-
?	O	-
It's	O	-
not	O	-
we	O	-
"	O	-

So	O	-
if	O	-
you	O	-
get	O	-
boom	O	-
with	O	-
the	O	-
.	O	-
45	O	-
long	O	-

It's	O	-
a	O	-
critical	O	-
hit	O	-
,	O	-
no	O	-
chance	O	-
to	O	-
repeat	O	-

And	O	-
if	O	-
you	O	-
see	O	-
Arge	B-PER	European
in	O	-
the	O	-
cut	O	-
with	O	-
the	O	-
dip	O	-

You're	O	-
pissed	O	-
so	O	-
quick	O	-
your	O	-
team	O	-
should	O	-
retreat	O	-

But	O	-
if	O	-
you	O	-
see	O	-
Juss	B-PER	European
in	O	-
the	O	-
cut	O	-
with	O	-
his	O	-
right	O	-
hand	O	-
tucked	O	-

You're	O	-
fucked	O	-
,	O	-
your	O	-
team	O	-
should	O	-
leave	O	-
,	O	-
G	B-MISC	North America

If	O	-
you	O	-
see	O	-
Rapz	B-PER	European
in	O	-
the	O	-
back	O	-
with	O	-
his	O	-
hand	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
bag	O	-

It's	O	-
mad	O	-
,	O	-
we	O	-
came	O	-
to	O	-
see	O	-
Ps	B-MISC	European

Walk	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
rave	O	-
,	O	-
smile	O	-
on	O	-
my	O	-
face	O	-

Drink	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
cup	O	-
,	O	-
hand	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
jeans	O	-

Man	O	-
talk	O	-
tough	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-
look	O	-
up	O	-
,	O	-
down	O	-
,	O	-
left	O	-
,	O	-
right	O	-

Straight	O	-
to	O	-
a	O	-
bang	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
teeth	O	-

Man	O	-
still	O	-
talk	O	-
tough	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-
saw	O	-
man	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
flesh	O	-

Now	O	-
man's	O	-
tryna	O	-
talk	O	-
to	O	-
my	O	-
Gs	B-MISC	North America

Nah	O	-
,	O	-
none	O	-
of	O	-
that	O	-
,	O	-
none	O	-
,	O	-
.	O	-
45	O	-
drum	O	-

Run	O	-
you	O	-
right	O	-
out	O	-
of	O	-
your	O	-
street	O	-

Walk	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
dance	O	-
,	O	-
chicks	O	-
wanna	O	-
glance	O	-

Hand	O	-
on	O	-
my	O	-
hip	O	-
,	O	-
shank	B-MISC	European
for	O	-
the	O	-
dip	O	-

If	O	-
I	O	-
shout	O	-
"	O	-
oi	O	-
"	O	-
,	O	-
them	O	-
man	O	-
there	O	-
best	O	-
skip	O	-

Better	O	-
tie	O	-
up	O	-
your	O	-
laces	O	-
tight	O	-
and	O	-
don't	O	-
trip	O	-

Trip	O	-
,	O	-
get	O	-
splashed	O	-

Couldn't	O	-
care	O	-
less	O	-
about	O	-
my	O	-
man's	O	-
gang	B-MISC	North America

We're	O	-
not	O	-
fam	B-MISC	European
,	O	-
we're	O	-
not	O	-
friends	O	-
or	O	-
bredrins	B-MISC	European

You'll	O	-
get	O	-
tanned	O	-
and	O	-
binned	O	-
,	O	-
cock	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
blam	O	-

(	O	-
169	O	-
)	O	-

Trap	O	-
,	O	-
TrapMoneyBenny	B-PER	North America

This	O	-
shit	O	-
got	O	-
me	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
feelings	O	-

Gotta	O	-
be	O	-
real	O	-
with	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Kiki	B-PER	North America
,	O	-
do	O	-
you	O	-
love	O	-
me	O	-
?	O	-
Are	O	-
you	O	-
riding	O	-
?	O	-

Say	O	-
you'll	O	-
never	O	-
ever	O	-
leave	O	-
from	O	-
beside	O	-
me	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
ya	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
ya	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
down	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
always	O	-

KB	B-PER	North America
,	O	-
do	O	-
you	O	-
love	O	-
me	O	-
?	O	-
Are	O	-
you	O	-
riding	O	-
?	O	-

Say	O	-
you'll	O	-
never	O	-
ever	O	-
leave	O	-
from	O	-
beside	O	-
me	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
ya	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
ya	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
down	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
always	O	-

Look	O	-
,	O	-
the	O	-
new	O	-
me	O	-
is	O	-
really	O	-
still	O	-
the	O	-
real	O	-
me	O	-

I	O	-
swear	O	-
you	O	-
gotta	O	-
feel	O	-
me	O	-
before	O	-
they	O	-
try	O	-
and	O	-
kill	O	-
me	O	-

They	O	-
gotta	O	-
make	O	-
some	O	-
choices	O	-
,	O	-
they	O	-
runnin'	O	-
out	O	-
of	O	-
options	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I've	O	-
been	O	-
goin'	O	-
off	O	-
and	O	-
they	O	-
don't	O	-
know	O	-
when	O	-
it's	O	-
stoppin'	O	-

And	O	-
when	O	-
you	O	-
get	O	-
to	O	-
toppin'	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
see	O	-
that	O	-
you've	O	-
been	O	-
learnin'	O	-

And	O	-
when	O	-
I	O	-
take	O	-
you	O	-
shoppin'	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
spend	O	-
it	O	-
like	O	-
you	O	-
earned	O	-
it	O	-

And	O	-
when	O	-
you	O	-
popped	O	-
off	O	-
on	O	-
your	O	-
ex	O	-
he	O	-
deserved	O	-
it	O	-

I	O	-
thought	O	-
you	O	-
were	O	-
the	O	-
one	O	-
from	O	-
the	O	-
jump	O	-
,	O	-
that	O	-
confirmed	O	-
it	O	-

TrapMoneyBenny	B-PER	North America
,	O	-
ayy	O	-

I	O	-
buy	O	-
you	O	-
Champagne	B-MISC	European
but	O	-
you	O	-
love	O	-
some	O	-
Henny	B-MISC	European

From	O	-
the	O	-
block	O	-
like	O	-
you	O	-
Jenny	B-PER	North America

I	O	-
know	O	-
you	O	-
special	O	-
,	O	-
girl	O	-
,	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
too	O	-
many	O	-

'	O	-
Resha	B-PER	North America
,	O	-
do	O	-
you	O	-
love	O	-
me	O	-
?	O	-
Are	O	-
you	O	-
riding	O	-
?	O	-

Say	O	-
you'll	O	-
never	O	-
ever	O	-
leave	O	-
from	O	-
beside	O	-
me	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
ya	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
ya	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
down	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
always	O	-

JT	B-PER	North America
,	O	-
do	O	-
you	O	-
love	O	-
me	O	-
?	O	-
Are	O	-
you	O	-
riding	O	-
?	O	-

Say	O	-
you'll	O	-
never	O	-
ever	O	-
leave	O	-
from	O	-
beside	O	-
me	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
ya	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
ya	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
down	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
always	O	-

Two	O	-
bad	O	-
bitches	O	-
and	O	-
we	O	-
kissin'	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
Wraith	B-ORG	European

Kissin'-kissin'	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
Wraith	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
kiss-kissin'	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
Wraith	B-ORG	European

I	O	-
need	O	-
that	O	-
black	B-MISC	Non-cultural
card	I-MISC	Non-cultural
and	O	-
the	O	-
code	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
safe	O	-

Code	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
safe	O	-
,	O	-
code-code	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
safe-safe	O	-

I	O	-
show	O	-
him	O	-
how	O	-
that	O	-
neck	O	-
work	O	-

Fuck	O	-
that	O	-
Netflix	B-ORG	North America
and	O	-
chill	O	-
—	O	-
what's	O	-
your	O	-
net-net	O	-
-	O	-
net	O	-
worth	O	-
?	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
ya	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
ya	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
down	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
always	O	-

Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
he	O	-
bad	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
down	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
always	O	-

Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
guess	O	-
who's	O	-
back	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
down	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
always	O	-

D-down	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
al	O	-
–	O	-

Black	O	-
biggy	O	-
biggy	O	-
black	O	-
biggy	O	-
black	O	-
blake	O	-

D-d	O	-
-	O	-
down	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
always	O	-

I	O	-
got	O	-
a	O	-
new	O	-
boy	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
that	O	-
nigga	O	-
trade	O	-
!	O	-

Kiki	B-PER	North America
,	O	-
do	O	-
you	O	-
love	O	-
me	O	-
?	O	-
Are	O	-
you	O	-
riding	O	-
?	O	-

Say	O	-
you'll	O	-
never	O	-
ever	O	-
leave	O	-
from	O	-
beside	O	-
me	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
you	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
you	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
down	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
always	O	-

KB	B-PER	North America
,	O	-
do	O	-
you	O	-
love	O	-
me	O	-
?	O	-
Are	O	-
you	O	-
riding	O	-
?	O	-

Say	O	-
you'll	O	-
never	O	-
ever	O	-
leave	O	-
from	O	-
beside	O	-
me	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
ya	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
–	O	-

Skate	O	-
and	O	-
Smoke	O	-
and	O	-
Rap	B-MISC	North America

Now	O	-
let	O	-
me	O	-
see	O	-
you	O	-

Bring	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
,	O	-
bring	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
,	O	-
bring	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
back	O	-
!	O	-

B-bring	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
,	O	-
bring	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
,	O	-
bring	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
back	O	-
!	O	-

Shawty	O	-
say	O	-
the	O	-
nigga	O	-
that	O	-
she	O	-
with	O	-
can't	O	-
hit	O	-

But	O	-
shawty	B-MISC	North America
,	O	-
I'ma	O	-
hit	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
hit	O	-
it	O	-
like	O	-
I	O	-
can't	O	-
miss	O	-

Now	O	-
let	O	-
me	O	-
see	O	-
you	O	-

Clap	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
,	O	-
you're	O	-
the	O	-
only	O	-
one	O	-
I	O	-
love	O	-

Clap	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
,	O	-
clap-clap	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
!	O	-

Bring	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
back	O	-
!	O	-

Clap-clap	O	-
-	O	-
clap	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
,	O	-
you're	O	-
the	O	-
only	O	-
one	O	-
I	O	-
love	O	-

Let's	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
let's	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
let's	O	-
go	O	-
!	O	-

Bring	O	-
that	O	-
ass	O	-
back	O	-
!	O	-

Trap	O	-
,	O	-
TrapMoneyBenny	B-PER	North America

This	O	-
shit	O	-
got	O	-
me	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
feelings	O	-

Gotta	O	-
be	O	-
real	O	-
with	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
yup	O	-

BlaqNmilD	B-PER	North America
,	O	-
you	O	-
a	O	-
genius	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
diggin'	O	-
me	O	-
?	O	-

I	O	-
don't	O	-
even	O	-
care	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
a	O	-
photo	O	-
with	O	-
Drake	B-PER	North America

Because	O	-
my	O	-
Instagram	O	-
is	O	-
weak	O	-
as	O	-
fuck	O	-

I'm	O	-
just	O	-
being	O	-
real	O	-
,	O	-
my	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
look	O	-
–	O	-

Bangladesh	B-PER	Middle Asian

Young	B-ORG	North America
Money	I-ORG	North America
!	O	-

You	O	-
dig	O	-
?	O	-

Mack	B-PER	North America
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
going	O	-
in	O	-

A	O	-
millionaire	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
a	O	-
Young	B-ORG	North America
Money	I-ORG	North America
millionaire	O	-

Tougher	O	-
than	O	-
Nigerian	B-LOC	African
hair	O	-

My	O	-
criteria	O	-
compared	O	-
to	O	-
your	O	-
career	O	-
just	O	-
isn't	O	-
fair	O	-

I'm	O	-
a	O	-
venereal	O	-
disease	O	-
,	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
menstrual	O	-
bleed	O	-

Through	O	-
the	O	-
pencil	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
leak	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
sheet	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
tablet	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
mind	O	-

‘	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
don't	O	-
write	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
‘	O	-
cause	O	-
I	O	-
ain't	O	-
got	O	-
time	O	-

‘	O	-
Cause	O	-
my	O	-
seconds	O	-
,	O	-
minutes	O	-
,	O	-
hours	O	-
go	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
almighty	O	-
dollar	O	-

And	O	-
the	O	-
almighty	O	-
power	O	-
of	O	-
that	O	-
ch-cha	O	-
-	O	-
cha-chopper	B-MISC	North America

Sister	O	-
,	O	-
brother	O	-
,	O	-
son	O	-
,	O	-
daughter	O	-
,	O	-
father	O	-
;	O	-
mother-fuck	O	-
a	O	-
copper	B-MISC	European

Got	O	-
the	O	-
Maserati	O	-
dancin'	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
bridge	O	-
,	O	-
pussy	O	-
poppin'	O	-

Tell	O	-
the	O	-
coppers	B-MISC	European
:	O	-
"	O	-
Ha-ha	O	-
-	O	-
ha-ha	O	-

You	O	-
can't	O	-
catch	O	-
him	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
can't	O	-
stop	O	-
him	O	-
"	O	-

I	O	-
go	O	-
by	O	-
them	O	-
goon	B-MISC	North America
rules	O	-
:	O	-
if	O	-
you	O	-
can't	O	-
beat	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
you	O	-
pop	B-MISC	North America
'	O	-
em	O	-

You	O	-
can't	O	-
man	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
you	O	-
mop	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-

You	O	-
can't	O	-
stand	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
you	O	-
drop	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-

You	O	-
pop	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
‘	O	-
cause	O	-
we	O	-
pop	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
like	O	-
Orville	B-PER	North America
Redenbacher	I-PER	North America

Motherfucker	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
ill	O	-

A	O	-
million	O	-
here	O	-
,	O	-
a	O	-
million	O	-
there	O	-

Sicilian	B-LOC	European
bitch	O	-
with	O	-
long	O	-
hair	O	-
,	O	-
with	O	-
coke	B-MISC	Non-cultural
in	O	-
her	O	-
derriere	B-MISC	European

Like	O	-
smoking	O	-
the	O	-
thinnest	O	-
air	O	-

I	O	-
open	O	-
the	O	-
Lamborghini	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
hopin'	O	-
them	O	-
crackers	O	-
see	O	-
me	O	-

Like	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Look	O	-
at	O	-
that	O	-
bastard	O	-
Weezy	B-PER	North America
!	O	-
"	O	-

He's	O	-
a	O	-
beast	O	-
,	O	-
he's	O	-
a	O	-
dog	O	-
,	O	-
he's	O	-
a	O	-
mothafuckin'	O	-
problem	O	-

Okay	O	-
,	O	-
you're	O	-
a	O	-
goon	B-MISC	North America
,	O	-
but	O	-
what's	O	-
a	O	-
goon	B-MISC	North America
to	O	-
a	O	-
goblin	B-MISC	Non-cultural
?	O	-

Nothin'	O	-
,	O	-
nothin'	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
ain't	O	-
scarin'	O	-
nothin'	O	-

On	O	-
some	O	-
faggot	O	-
bullshit	O	-
:	O	-
call	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
Dennis	B-PER	Non-cultural
Rodman	I-PER	North American

Call	O	-
me	O	-
what	O	-
you	O	-
want	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-
!	O	-
Call	O	-
me	O	-
on	O	-
my	O	-
Sidekick	B-ORG	North American
!	O	-

Never	O	-
answer	O	-
when	O	-
it's	O	-
private	O	-
,	O	-
damn	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
hate	O	-
a	O	-
shy	O	-
bitch	O	-

Don't	O	-
you	O	-
hate	O	-
a	O	-
shy	O	-
bitch	O	-
?	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
ate	O	-
a	O	-
shy	O	-
bitch	O	-

She	O	-
ain't	O	-
shy	O	-
no	O	-
more	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
changed	O	-
her	O	-
name	O	-
to	O	-
My	O	-
Bitch	O	-

Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
nigga	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
my	O	-
bitch	O	-
,	O	-
so	O	-
when	O	-
she	O	-
ask	O	-

For	O	-
the	O	-
money	O	-
when	O	-
you	O	-
through	O	-
,	O	-
don't	O	-
be	O	-
surprised	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-
!	O	-

And	O	-
it	O	-
ain't	O	-
trickin'	O	-
if	O	-
you	O	-
got	O	-
it	O	-

But	O	-
you	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
bitch	O	-
with	O	-
no	O	-
ass	O	-
:	O	-
You	O	-
ain't	O	-
got	O	-
shit	O	-

Motherfucker	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
ill	O	-
,	O	-
not	O	-
sick	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
okay	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
my	O	-
watch	O	-
sick	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
my	O	-
drop	O	-
sick	O	-

Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
my	O	-
Glock	B-MISC	North American
sick	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
my	O	-
knot	O	-
thick	O	-
—	O	-
I'm	O	-
it	O	-

Motherfucker	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
ill	O	-

See	O	-
,	O	-
they	O	-
say	O	-
I'm	O	-
rappin'	O	-
like	O	-
B	B-PER	North American
.	I-PER	European
I	I-PER	North American
.	I-PER	European
G	I-PER	North America
.	O	-
,	O	-
Jay	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
and	O	-
2Pac	B-PER	North American

André	B-PER	North American
3000	I-PER	North American
,	O	-
where	O	-
is	O	-
Erykah	B-PER	North American
Badu	I-PER	North American
at	O	-
?	O	-
Who	O	-
that	O	-
?	O	-

Who	O	-
that	O	-
said	O	-
they	O	-
gon'	O	-
beat	O	-
Lil	B-PER	North American
Wayne	I-PER	North American
?	O	-

My	O	-
name	O	-
ain't	O	-
Bic	B-ORG	North American
,	O	-
but	O	-
I	O	-
keep	O	-
that	O	-
flame	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-

Who	O	-
that	O	-
one	O	-
that	O	-
do	O	-
that	O	-
,	O	-
boy	O	-
?	O	-

You	O	-
knew	O	-
that	O	-
true	O	-
that	O	-
,	O	-
swallow	O	-

And	O	-
I	O	-
be	O	-
the	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
now	O	-
you	O	-
got	O	-
loose	O	-
bowels	O	-

I	O	-
don't	O	-
owe	O	-
you	O	-
like	O	-
two	O	-
vowels	O	-

But	O	-
I	O	-
would	O	-
like	O	-
for	O	-
you	O	-
to	O	-
pay	O	-
me	O	-
by	O	-
the	O	-
hour	O	-

And	O	-
I'd	O	-
rather	O	-
be	O	-
pushin'	O	-
flowers	O	-

Than	O	-
to	O	-
be	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
pen	O	-
sharin'	O	-
showers	O	-

Tony	B-PER	North American
told	O	-
us	O	-
this	O	-
world	O	-
was	O	-
ours	O	-

And	O	-
the	O	-
Bible	B-MISC	Non-cultural
told	O	-
us	O	-
every	O	-
girl	O	-
was	O	-
sour	O	-

Don't	O	-
play	O	-
in	O	-
her	O	-
garden	O	-
and	O	-
don't	O	-
smell	O	-
her	O	-
flower	O	-

Call	O	-
me	O	-
Mr	B-PER	North American
.	I-PER	European
Carter	I-PER	North American
or	O	-
Mr	O	-
.	O	-
Lawn	O	-
Mower	O	-

Even	O	-
Gwen	B-PER	North American
Stefani	I-PER	North American
said	O	-
she	O	-
couldn't	O	-
doubt	O	-
me	O	-

Motherfucker	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
say	O	-
"	O	-
Life	O	-
ain't	O	-
shit	O	-
without	O	-
me	O	-
"	O	-

Chrome	O	-
lips	O	-
pokin'	O	-
out	O	-
the	O	-
coupe	B-MISC	European
,	O	-
look	O	-
like	O	-
it's	O	-
poutin'	O	-

I	O	-
do	O	-
what	O	-
I	O	-
do	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
you	O	-
do	O	-
what	O	-
you	O	-
can	O	-
do	O	-
about	O	-
it	O	-

Bitch	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
can	O	-
turn	O	-
a	O	-
crack	B-MISC	Non-cultural
rock	I-MISC	Non-cultural
into	O	-
a	O	-
mountain	O	-
—	O	-
dare	O	-
me	O	-

Don't	O	-
you	O	-
compare	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
‘	O	-
cause	O	-
there	O	-
ain't	O	-
nobody	O	-
near	O	-
me	O	-

They	O	-
don't	O	-
see	O	-
me	O	-
but	O	-
they	O	-
hear	O	-
me	O	-

They	O	-
don't	O	-
feel	O	-
me	O	-
but	O	-
they	O	-
fear	O	-
me	O	-

I'm	O	-
illy	O	-
,	O	-
C3	O	-
,	O	-
3	B-MISC	Non-cultural
Peat	I-MISC	Non-cultural

Uh	O	-
,	O	-
me	O	-
and	O	-
my	O	-
niggas	O	-
tryna	O	-
get	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

Hit	O	-
the	O	-
house	O	-
lick	B-MISC	North American
:	O	-
tell	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
is	O	-
you	O	-
wit'	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
?	O	-
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

Home	O	-
invasion	O	-
was	O	-
persuasive	O	-
(	O	-
Was	O	-
persuasive	O	-
)	O	-

From	O	-
nine	O	-
to	O	-
five	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
it's	O	-
vacant	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

Dreams	O	-
of	O	-
livin'	O	-
life	O	-
like	O	-
rappers	B-MISC	North American
do	O	-
(	O	-
Like	O	-
rappers	B-MISC	North American
do	O	-
)	O	-

Back	O	-
when	O	-
condom	O	-
wrappers	O	-
wasn't	O	-
cool	O	-
(	O	-
They	O	-
wasn't	O	-
cool	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
fucked	O	-
Sherane	B-PER	North American
and	O	-
went	O	-
to	O	-
tell	O	-
my	O	-
bros	O	-
(	O	-
Tell	O	-
my	O	-
bros	O	-
)	O	-

Then	O	-
Usher	B-PER	North American
Raymond	I-PER	North American
"	O	-
Let	B-MISC	North American
It	I-MISC	North American
Burn	I-MISC	North American
"	O	-
came	O	-
on	O	-
(	O	-
"	O	-
Let	B-MISC	North American
Burn	I-MISC	North American
"	O	-
came	O	-
on	O	-
)	O	-

Hot	O	-
sauce	O	-
all	O	-
in	O	-
our	O	-
Top	B-ORG	North American
Ramen	I-ORG	North American
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

Park	O	-
the	O	-
car	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
we	O	-
start	O	-
rhymin'	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

The	O	-
only	O	-
thing	O	-
we	O	-
had	O	-
to	O	-
free	O	-
our	O	-
mind	O	-
(	O	-
Free	O	-
our	O	-
mind	O	-
)	O	-

Then	O	-
freeze	O	-
that	O	-
verse	O	-
when	O	-
we	O	-
see	O	-
dollar	B-MISC	North American
signs	O	-
(	O	-
See	O	-
dollar	B-MISC	North American
signs	O	-
)	O	-

You	O	-
lookin'	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
easy	O	-
come-up	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

A	O	-
silver	O	-
spoon	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
you	O	-
come	O	-
from	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

And	O	-
that's	O	-
a	O	-
lifestyle	O	-
that	O	-
we	O	-
never	O	-
knew	O	-
(	O	-
We	O	-
never	O	-
knew	O	-
)	O	-

Go	O	-
at	O	-
a	O	-
reverend	O	-
for	O	-
the	O	-
revenue	O	-

It	O	-
go	O	-
Halle	B-PER	North American
Berry	I-PER	North American
or	O	-
hallelujah	B-MISC	North American

Pick	O	-
your	O	-
poison	O	-
,	O	-
tell	O	-
me	O	-
what	O	-
you	O	-
doin'	O	-

Everybody	O	-
gon'	O	-
respect	O	-
the	O	-
shooter	O	-

But	O	-
the	O	-
one	O	-
in	O	-
front	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
gun	O	-
lives	O	-
forever	O	-

(	O	-
The	O	-
one	O	-
in	O	-
front	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
gun	O	-
,	O	-
forever	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I	O	-
been	O	-
hustlin'	O	-
all	O	-
day	O	-

This-a	O	-
-	O	-
way	O	-
,	O	-
that-a	O	-
-	O	-
way	O	-

Through	O	-
canals	O	-
and	O	-
alleyways	O	-
,	O	-
just	O	-
to	O	-
say	O	-

Money	O	-
trees	O	-
is	O	-
the	O	-
perfect	O	-
place	O	-
for	O	-
shade	O	-

And	O	-
that's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-

Nah	O	-
,	O	-
nah	O	-

A	O	-
dollar	B-MISC	North American
might	O	-
just	O	-
fuck	O	-
your	O	-
main	O	-
bitch	O	-

That's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-
,	O	-
nah	O	-

A	O	-
dollar	B-MISC	North American
might	O	-
say	O	-
fuck	O	-
them	O	-
niggas	O	-
that	O	-
you	O	-
came	O	-
with	O	-

That's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-
,	O	-
nah	O	-
,	O	-
nah	O	-

A	O	-
dollar	B-MISC	North American
might	O	-
just	O	-
make	O	-
that	O	-
lane	O	-
switch	O	-

That's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-
,	O	-
nah	O	-

A	O	-
dollar	B-MISC	North American
might	O	-
turn	O	-
to	O	-
a	O	-
million	O	-
and	O	-
we	O	-
all	O	-
rich	O	-

That's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-

Dreams	O	-
of	O	-
livin'	O	-
life	O	-
like	O	-
rappers	B-MISC	North American
do	O	-
(	O	-
Like	O	-
rappers	B-MISC	North American
do	O	-
)	O	-

Bump	O	-
that	O	-
new	O	-
E-40	B-PER	North American
after	O	-
school	O	-
(	O	-
Way	O	-
after	O	-
school	O	-
)	O	-

You	O	-
know	O	-
,	O	-
“	O	-
Big	B-MISC	North American
Ballin'	I-MISC	North American
With	I-MISC	North American
My	I-MISC	North American
Homies	I-MISC	North American
”	O	-
(	O	-
My	O	-
homies	O	-
)	O	-

Earl	B-PER	North American
Stevens	I-PER	North American
had	O	-
us	O	-
thinkin'	O	-
rational	O	-
(	O	-
Thinkin'	O	-
rational	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
rational	O	-
)	O	-

Back	O	-
to	O	-
reality	O	-
,	O	-
we	O	-
poor	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	O	-
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	O	-
)	O	-

Another	O	-
casualty	O	-
at	O	-
war	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	O	-
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	O	-
)	O	-

Two	O	-
bullets	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
Uncle	B-PER	North American
Tony	I-PER	North American
head	O	-
(	O	-
My	O	-
Tony	B-PER	North American
head	O	-
)	O	-

He	O	-
said	O	-
one	O	-
day	O	-
I'll	O	-
be	O	-
on	O	-
tour	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

That	O	-
Louis	B-MISC	North American
Burgers	I-MISC	North American
never	O	-
be	O	-
the	O	-
same	O	-
(	O	-
Won't	O	-
be	O	-
the	O	-
same	O	-
)	O	-

A	O	-
Louis	B-ORG	North American
belt	O	-
that	O	-
never	O	-
ease	O	-
that	O	-
pain	O	-
(	O	-
Won't	O	-
ease	O	-
that	O	-
pain	O	-
)	O	-

But	O	-
I'ma	O	-
purchase	O	-
when	O	-
that	O	-
day	O	-
is	O	-
jerkin'	O	-
(	O	-
That	O	-
day	O	-
is	O	-
jerkin'	O	-
)	O	-

Pull	O	-
off	O	-
at	O	-
Church's	B-ORG	North American
,	O	-
with	O	-
Pirellis	B-ORG	European
skirtin'	O	-
(	O	-
Pirellis	B-ORG	European
skirtin'	O	-
)	O	-

Gang	O	-
signs	O	-
out	O	-
the	O	-
window	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

Hopin'	O	-
all	O	-
of	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
offend	O	-
you	O	-
,	O	-
ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Ya	O	-
bish	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

They	O	-
say	O	-
your	O	-
hood	O	-
is	O	-
a	O	-
pot	O	-
of	O	-
gold	O	-
(	O	-
A	O	-
pot	O	-
of	O	-
gold	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
we	O	-
gon'	O	-
crash	O	-
it	O	-
when	O	-
nobody's	O	-
home	O	-

It	O	-
go	O	-
Halle	B-PER	North American
Berry	I-PER	North American
or	O	-
hallelujah	B-MISC	North American

Pick	O	-
your	O	-
poison	O	-
,	O	-
tell	O	-
me	O	-
what	O	-
you	O	-
doin'	O	-

Everybody	O	-
gon'	O	-
respect	O	-
the	O	-
shooter	O	-

But	O	-
the	O	-
one	O	-
in	O	-
front	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
gun	O	-
lives	O	-
forever	O	-

(	O	-
The	O	-
one	O	-
in	O	-
front	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
gun	O	-
,	O	-
forever	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I	O	-
been	O	-
hustlin'	O	-
all	O	-
day	O	-

This-a	O	-
-	O	-
way	O	-
,	O	-
that-a	O	-
-	O	-
way	O	-

Through	O	-
canals	O	-
and	O	-
alleyways	O	-
,	O	-
just	O	-
to	O	-
say	O	-

Money	O	-
trees	O	-
is	O	-
the	O	-
perfect	O	-
place	O	-
for	O	-
shade	O	-

And	O	-
that's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-

Nah	O	-
,	O	-
nah	O	-

A	O	-
dollar	B-MISC	North American
might	O	-
just	O	-
fuck	O	-
your	O	-
main	O	-
bitch	O	-

That's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-
,	O	-
nah	O	-

A	O	-
dollar	B-MISC	North American
might	O	-
say	O	-
fuck	O	-
them	O	-
niggas	O	-
that	O	-
you	O	-
came	O	-
with	O	-

That's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-
,	O	-
nah	O	-
,	O	-
nah	O	-

A	O	-
dollar	B-MISC	North American
might	O	-
just	O	-
make	O	-
that	O	-
lane	O	-
switch	O	-

That's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-
,	O	-
nah	O	-

A	O	-
dollar	B-MISC	North American
might	O	-
turn	O	-
to	O	-
a	O	-
million	O	-
and	O	-
we	O	-
all	O	-
rich	O	-

That's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-

Be	O	-
the	O	-
last	O	-
one	O	-
out	O	-
to	O	-
get	O	-
this	O	-
dough	O	-
?	O	-
No	O	-
way	O	-
!	O	-

Love	O	-
one	O	-
of	O	-
you	O	-
bucket-headed	O	-
hoes	O	-
?	O	-
No	O	-
way	O	-
!	O	-

Hit	O	-
the	O	-
streets	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
we	O	-
break	O	-
the	O	-
code	O	-
?	O	-
No	O	-
way	O	-
!	O	-

Hit	O	-
the	O	-
brakes	O	-
when	O	-
they	O	-
on	O	-
patrol	O	-
?	O	-
No	O	-
way	O	-
!	O	-

Be	O	-
the	O	-
last	O	-
one	O	-
out	O	-
to	O	-
get	O	-
this	O	-
dough	O	-
?	O	-
No	O	-
way	O	-
!	O	-

Love	O	-
one	O	-
of	O	-
you	O	-
bucket-headed	O	-
hoes	O	-
?	O	-
No	O	-
way	O	-
!	O	-

Hit	O	-
the	O	-
streets	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
we	O	-
break	O	-
the	O	-
code	O	-
?	O	-
No	O	-
way	O	-
!	O	-

Hit	O	-
the	O	-
brakes	O	-
when	O	-
they	O	-
on	O	-
patrol	O	-
?	O	-
No	O	-
way	O	-
!	O	-

Imagine	O	-
Rock	B-PER	European
up	O	-
in	O	-
them	O	-
projects	O	-

Where	O	-
them	O	-
niggas	O	-
pick	O	-
your	O	-
pockets	O	-

Liquors	B-MISC	European
spillin'	O	-
,	O	-
pistols	O	-
poppin'	O	-

Bakin'	O	-
soda	O	-
YOLA	B-MISC	Non-cultural
whippin'	O	-

Ain't	O	-
no	O	-
turkey	O	-
on	O	-
Thanksgivin'	B-MISC	North American

My	O	-
homeboy	O	-
just	O	-
dome'd	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-

I	O	-
just	O	-
hope	O	-
the	O	-
Lord	B-PER	Non-cultural
forgive	O	-
him	O	-

Pots	O	-
with	O	-
cocaine	B-MISC	Non-cultural
residue	O	-

Every	O	-
day	O	-
I'm	O	-
hustlin'	O	-

What	O	-
else	O	-
is	O	-
a	O	-
thug	B-MISC	North American
to	O	-
do	O	-

When	O	-
you	O	-
eatin'	O	-
cheese	O	-
from	O	-
the	O	-
government	O	-
?	O	-

Gotta	O	-
provide	O	-
for	O	-
my	O	-
daughter	O	-
n'em	O	-

Get	O	-
the	O	-
fuck	O	-
up	O	-
out	O	-
my	O	-
way	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-

Got	O	-
that	O	-
drum	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
them	O	-
bands	O	-

Just	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
parade	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-

Drop	O	-
that	O	-
work	O	-
up	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
bushes	O	-

Hope	O	-
them	O	-
boys	O	-
don't	O	-
see	O	-
my	O	-
stash	B-MISC	North American

If	O	-
they	O	-
do	O	-
,	O	-
tell	O	-
the	O	-
truth	O	-

This	O	-
the	O	-
last	O	-
time	O	-
you	O	-
might	O	-
see	O	-
my	O	-
ass	O	-

From	O	-
the	O	-
gardens	O	-
where	O	-
the	O	-
grass	O	-
ain't	O	-
cut	O	-

Them	O	-
serpents	O	-
lurkin'	O	-
,	O	-
Blood	B-MISC	North American

Bitches	O	-
sellin'	O	-
pussy	O	-
,	O	-
niggas	O	-
sellin'	O	-
drugs	O	-

But	O	-
it's	O	-
all	O	-
good	O	-

Broken	O	-
promises	O	-
,	O	-
steal	O	-
your	O	-
watch	O	-

And	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
what	O	-
time	O	-
it	O	-
is	O	-

Take	O	-
your	O	-
J's	B-MISC	North American
and	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
to	O	-
kick	O	-
it	O	-
where	O	-
a	O	-
FootLocker	B-ORG	North American
is	O	-

In	O	-
the	O	-
streets	O	-
with	O	-
a	O	-
heater	O	-
under	O	-
my	O	-
Dungarees	B-ORG	North American

Dreams	O	-
of	O	-
me	O	-
gettin'	O	-
shaded	O	-
under	O	-
a	O	-
money	O	-
tree	O	-

It	O	-
go	O	-
Halle	B-PER	North American
Berry	I-PER	North American
or	O	-
hallelujah	B-MISC	North American

Pick	O	-
your	O	-
poison	O	-
,	O	-
tell	O	-
me	O	-
what	O	-
you	O	-
doin'	O	-

Everybody	O	-
gon'	O	-
respect	O	-
the	O	-
shooter	O	-

But	O	-
the	O	-
one	O	-
in	O	-
front	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
gun	O	-
lives	O	-
forever	O	-

(	O	-
The	O	-
one	O	-
in	O	-
front	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
gun	O	-
,	O	-
forever	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I	O	-
been	O	-
hustlin'	O	-
all	O	-
day	O	-

This-a	O	-
-	O	-
way	O	-
,	O	-
that-a	O	-
-	O	-
way	O	-

Through	O	-
canals	O	-
and	O	-
alleyways	O	-
,	O	-
just	O	-
to	O	-
say	O	-

Money	O	-
trees	O	-
is	O	-
the	O	-
perfect	O	-
place	O	-
for	O	-
shade	O	-

And	O	-
that's	O	-
just	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
feel	O	-

Kendrick’s	B-PER	North American
Mom	O	-
:	O	-
Kendrick	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
just	O	-
bring	O	-
my	O	-
car	O	-
back	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-
.	O	-
I	O	-
called	O	-
in	O	-
for	O	-
another	O	-
appointment	O	-
.	O	-
I	O	-
figured	O	-
you	O	-
weren’t	O	-
gonna	O	-
be	O	-
back	O	-
here	O	-
on	O	-
time	O	-
anyways	O	-
.	O	-
Look	O	-
,	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
just	O	-
wanna	O	-
get	O	-
out	O	-
the	O	-
house	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-
.	O	-
This	O	-
man	O	-
is	O	-
on	O	-
one	O	-
,	O	-
he	O	-
feelin'	O	-
good	O	-
as	O	-
a	O	-
motherfucker	O	-
.	O	-
Shit	O	-
,	O	-
I’m	O	-
tryna	O	-
get	O	-
my	O	-
thing	O	-
goin'	O	-
,	O	-
too	O	-
.	O	-
Just	O	-
bring	O	-
my	O	-
car	O	-
back	O	-
.	O	-
Shit	O	-
,	O	-
he	O	-
faded	O	-
.	O	-
He	O	-
feelin'	O	-
good	O	-
.	O	-
Look	O	-
,	O	-
listen	O	-
to	O	-
him	O	-
!	O	-

Kendrick’s	B-PER	North American
Dad	O	-
:	O	-
Girl	O	-
,	O	-
girl	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
your	O	-
body	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
your	O	-
body	O	-
,	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
of	O	-
that	O	-
big	O	-
ol’	O	-
fat	O	-
ass	O	-
.	O	-
Girl	O	-
,	O	-
girl	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
your	O	-
body	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
your	O	-
body	O	-
,	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
of	O	-
that	O	-
big	O	-
ol’	O	-
fat	O	-
ass	O	-

Kendrick’s	B-PER	North American
Mom	O	-
:	O	-
See	O	-
,	O	-
he	O	-
high	O	-
as	O	-
hell	O	-
.	O	-
Shit	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
he	O	-
ain’t	O	-
even	O	-
trippin'	O	-
off	O	-
them	O	-
damn	O	-
dominoes	O	-
anymore	O	-
.	O	-
Just	O	-
bring	O	-
the	O	-
car	O	-
back	O	-
!	O	-

Kendrick’s	B-PER	North American
Dad	O	-
:	O	-
Did	O	-
somebody	O	-
say	O	-
dominoes	O	-
?	O	-

For	O	-
real	O	-

You	O	-
the	O	-
only	O	-
father	O	-
that	O	-
I	O	-
ever	O	-
knew	O	-

I	O	-
get	O	-
my	O	-
bitch	O	-
pregnant	O	-
,	O	-
I'ma	O	-
be	O	-
a	O	-
better	O	-
you	O	-

Prophecies	O	-
that	O	-
I	O	-
made	O	-
way	O	-
back	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
Ville	B-LOC	North American

Fulfilled	O	-

Listen	O	-
,	O	-
even	O	-
back	O	-
when	O	-
we	O	-
was	O	-
broke	O	-
,	O	-
my	O	-
team	O	-
ill	O	-

One	O	-
time	O	-
for	O	-
my	O	-
L	B-ORG	North American
.	I-ORG	European
A	I-ORG	North American
.	O	-
sisters	O	-

One	O	-
time	O	-
for	O	-
my	O	-
L	B-ORG	North American
.	I-ORG	European
A	I-ORG	North American
.	O	-
hoes	O	-

Lame	O	-
niggas	O	-
can't	O	-
tell	O	-
the	O	-
difference	O	-

One	O	-
time	O	-
for	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
who	O	-
know	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

No	O	-
role	O	-
models	O	-
and	O	-
I'm	O	-
here	O	-
right	O	-
now	O	-

No	O	-
role	O	-
models	O	-
to	O	-
speak	O	-
of	O	-

Searchin'	O	-
through	O	-
my	O	-
memory	O	-
,	O	-
my	O	-
memory	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
couldn't	O	-
find	O	-
one	O	-

Last	O	-
night	O	-
I	O	-
was	O	-
gettin'	O	-
my	O	-
feet	O	-
rubbed	O	-
by	O	-
the	O	-
baddest	O	-
bitch	O	-

Not	O	-
Trina	B-PER	North American
but	O	-
I	O	-
swear	O	-
to	O	-
God	O	-
,	O	-
this	O	-
bitch'll	O	-
make	O	-
you	O	-
call	O	-
your	O	-
girl	O	-
up	O	-

And	O	-
tell	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Hey	O	-
,	O	-
what's	O	-
good	O	-
?	O	-

Sorry	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
never	O	-
comin'	O	-
home	O	-
,	O	-
I'ma	O	-
stay	O	-
for	O	-
good	O	-
"	O	-

Then	O	-
hang	O	-
the	O	-
phone	O	-
up	O	-
and	O	-
proceed	O	-
to	O	-
lay	O	-
the	O	-
wood	O	-

I	O	-
came	O	-
fast	O	-
like	O	-
9-1	B-MISC	North American
-	I-MISC	North American
1	I-MISC	North American
in	O	-
white	O	-
neighborhoods	O	-

Ain't	O	-
got	O	-
no	O	-
shame	O	-
'	O	-
bout	O	-
it	O	-

She	O	-
think	O	-
I'm	O	-
spoiled	O	-
and	O	-
I'm	O	-
rich	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
I	O	-
can	O	-
have	O	-
any	O	-
bitch	O	-

I	O	-
got	O	-
defensive	O	-
and	O	-
said	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Nah	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
was	O	-
the	O	-
same	O	-
without	O	-
it	O	-
"	O	-

But	O	-
then	O	-
I	O	-
thought	O	-
back	O	-
,	O	-
back	O	-
to	O	-
a	O	-
better	O	-
me	O	-

Before	O	-
I	O	-
was	O	-
a	O	-
B-list	B-MISC	North American
celebrity	O	-

'	O	-
Fore	O	-
I	O	-
started	O	-
callin'	O	-
bitches	O	-
"	O	-
bitches	O	-
"	O	-
so	O	-
heavily	O	-

Back	O	-
when	O	-
you	O	-
could	O	-
get	O	-
a	O	-
platinum	O	-
plaque	O	-
without	O	-
no	O	-
melody	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
wadn't	O	-
sweatin'	O	-
me	O	-

One	O	-
time	O	-
for	O	-
my	O	-
L	B-LOC	North American
.	I-LOC	European
A	I-LOC	North American
.	O	-
sisters	O	-

One	O	-
time	O	-
for	O	-
my	O	-
L	B-LOC	North American
.	I-LOC	European
A	I-LOC	North American
.	O	-
hoes	O	-

Lame	O	-
niggas	O	-
can't	O	-
tell	O	-
the	O	-
difference	O	-

One	O	-
time	O	-
for	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
who	O	-
know	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

I	O	-
want	O	-
a	O	-
real	O	-
love	O	-
,	O	-
dark-skinned	O	-
Aunt	B-PER	North American
Viv	I-PER	North American
love	O	-

That	O	-
Jada	B-PER	North American
and	O	-
that	O	-
Will	B-PER	North American
love	O	-

That	O	-
leave	O	-
a	O	-
toothbrush	O	-
at	O	-
your	O	-
crib	O	-
love	O	-

And	O	-
you	O	-
ain't	O	-
gotta	O	-
wonder	O	-
whether	O	-
that's	O	-
your	O	-
kid	O	-
love	O	-

Nigga	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
don't	O	-
want	O	-
no	O	-
bitch	O	-
from	O	-
reality	O	-
shows	O	-

Out-of	O	-
-	O	-
touch-with	O	-
-	O	-
reality	O	-
hoes	O	-

Out	O	-
in	O	-
Hollywood	B-LOC	North American
bringin'	O	-
back	O	-
five	O	-
or	O	-
six	O	-
hoes	O	-

Fuck	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
then	O	-
we	O	-
kick	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
do'	O	-
,	O	-
nigga	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
know	O	-
how	O	-
it	O	-
go	O	-

She	O	-
deserved	O	-
that	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
a	O	-
bird	O	-
,	O	-
it's	O	-
a	O	-
bird	O	-
trap	O	-

You	O	-
think	O	-
if	O	-
I	O	-
didn't	O	-
rap	O	-
she	O	-
would	O	-
flirt	O	-
back	O	-
?	O	-

Takin'	O	-
off	O	-
her	O	-
skirt	O	-
,	O	-
let	O	-
her	O	-
wear	O	-
my	O	-
shirt	O	-
,	O	-
'	O	-
fore	O	-
she	O	-
leave	O	-

"	O	-
I'ma	O	-
need	O	-
my	O	-
shirt	O	-
back	O	-
"	O	-
(	O	-
Nigga	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
know	O	-
how	O	-
it	O	-
go	O	-
)	O	-

One	O	-
time	O	-
for	O	-
my	O	-
L	B-LOC	North American
.	I-LOC	European
A	I-LOC	North American
.	I-LOC	European
sisters	O	-

One	O	-
time	O	-
for	O	-
my	O	-
L	B-LOC	North American
.	I-LOC	European
A	I-LOC	North American
.	I-LOC	European
hoes	O	-

Lame	O	-
niggas	O	-
can't	O	-
tell	O	-
the	O	-
difference	O	-

One	O	-
time	O	-
for	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
who	O	-
know	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

There's	O	-
an	O	-
old	O	-
saying	O	-
in	O	-
Tennessee	B-LOC	North American
—	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
it's	O	-
in	O	-
Texas	B-LOC	North American
,	O	-
probably	O	-
in	O	-
Tennessee	B-LOC	North American
—	O	-
that	O	-
says	O	-
,	O	-
fool	O	-
me	O	-
once	O	-
…	O	-
shame	O	-
on	O	-
…	O	-
shame	O	-
on	O	-
you	O	-
.	O	-
Fool	O	-
me	O	-
—	O	-
can't	O	-
get	O	-
fooled	O	-
again	O	-
.	O	-

Fool	O	-
me	O	-
one	O	-
time	O	-
,	O	-
shame	O	-
on	O	-
you	O	-
(	O	-
Ayy	O	-
)	O	-

Fool	O	-
me	O	-
three	O	-
times	O	-
,	O	-
fuck	O	-
the	O	-
peace	O	-
sign	O	-

Load	O	-
the	O	-
chopper	B-MISC	North America
,	O	-
let	O	-
it	O	-
rain	O	-
on	O	-
you	O	-
(	O	-
Bop	O	-
bop	O	-
bop	O	-
)	O	-

Fool	O	-
me	O	-
one	O	-
time	O	-
,	O	-
shame	O	-
on	O	-
you	O	-
(	O	-
Ayy	O	-
)	O	-

Fool	O	-
me	O	-
three	O	-
times	O	-
,	O	-
fuck	O	-
the	O	-
peace	O	-
sign	O	-

Load	O	-
the	O	-
chopper	B-MISC	North America
,	O	-
let	O	-
it	O	-
rain	O	-
on	O	-
you	O	-
(	O	-
Bop	O	-
bop	O	-
bop	O	-
)	O	-

My	O	-
only	O	-
regret	O	-
was	O	-
too	O	-
young	O	-
for	O	-
Lisa	B-PER	North American
Bonet	I-PER	North American

My	O	-
only	O	-
regret	O	-
was	O	-
too	O	-
young	O	-
for	O	-
Nia	B-PER	North American
Long	I-PER	North American

Now	O	-
all	O	-
I'm	O	-
left	O	-
with	O	-
is	O	-
hoes	O	-
from	O	-
reality	O	-
shows	O	-

Hand	O	-
her	O	-
a	O	-
script	O	-
,	O	-
the	O	-
bitch	O	-
prolly	O	-
couldn't	O	-
read	O	-
along	O	-

My	O	-
only	O	-
regret	O	-
was	O	-
too	O	-
young	O	-
for	O	-
Sade	B-PER	North American
Adu	I-PER	North American

My	O	-
only	O	-
regret	O	-
,	O	-
could	O	-
never	O	-
take	O	-
Aaliyah	B-PER	North American
home	O	-

Now	O	-
all	O	-
I'm	O	-
left	O	-
with	O	-
is	O	-
hoes	O	-
up	O	-
in	O	-
Greystone	B-LOC	North American

With	O	-
the	O	-
stale	O	-
face	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
they	O	-
know	O	-
it's	O	-
they	O	-
song	O	-

She	O	-
shallow	O	-
but	O	-
the	O	-
pussy	O	-
deep	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
shallow	O	-

She	O	-
shallow	O	-

She	O	-
shallow	O	-
but	O	-
the	O	-
pussy	O	-
deep	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
shallow	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
ayy	O	-
)	O	-

She	O	-
shallow	O	-

She	O	-
shallow	O	-
but	O	-
the	O	-
pussy	O	-
deep	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
shallow	O	-

She	O	-
shallow	O	-

She	O	-
shallow	O	-
but	O	-
the	O	-
pussy	O	-
deep	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
shallow	O	-

She	O	-
shallow	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Don't	O	-
save	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
wanna	O	-
be	O	-
saved	O	-

Double	O	-
OT	B-MISC	North American

I'm	O	-
a	O	-
new	O	-
three	O	-

Saucin'	O	-
,	O	-
saucin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
saucin'	O	-
on	O	-
you	O	-

I'm	O	-
swaggin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
swaggin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
swaggin'	O	-
,	O	-
oh-ooh	O	-
(	O	-
Swaggin'	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
ballin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
ballin'	O	-
,	O	-
Iverson	B-PER	North American
on	O	-
you	O	-
(	O	-
Swish	O	-
,	O	-
ooh	O	-
,	O	-
ayy	O	-
)	O	-

Watch	O	-
out	O	-
,	O	-
watch	O	-
out	O	-
,	O	-
watch	O	-
out	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

That's	O	-
my	O	-
shot	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
my	O	-
shot	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
my	O	-
shot	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Spendin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
spendin'	O	-
all	O	-
my	O	-
fuckin'	O	-
pay	O	-

I	O	-
got	O	-
me	O	-
some	O	-
braids	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
me	O	-
some	O	-
hoes	O	-

Started	O	-
rockin'	O	-
the	O	-
sleeve	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
can't	O	-
ball	O	-
with	O	-
no	O	-
Joes	B-MISC	North American

You	O	-
know	O	-
how	O	-
I	O	-
do	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
Concords	B-MISC	North American
on	O	-
my	O	-
toes	O	-

(	O	-
This	O	-
shit	O	-
is	O	-
hard	O	-
)	O	-
Oh	O	-

I	O	-
ain't	O	-
rich	O	-
yet	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
you	O	-
know	O	-
I	O	-
ain't	O	-
broke	O	-
,	O	-
ah	O	-

So	O	-
if	O	-
I	O	-
see	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
like	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
buy	O	-
that	O	-
from	O	-
the	O	-
store	O	-
,	O	-
ah	O	-
(	O	-
Store	O	-
,	O	-
ah	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
with	O	-
some	O	-
white	O	-
girls	O	-
and	O	-
they	O	-
lovin'	O	-
the	O	-
coca	B-MISC	Latin
(	O	-
Coca	B-MISC	Latin
)	O	-

Like	O	-
they	O	-
OT	B-MISC	North American

Double	O	-
OT	B-MISC	North American
like	O	-
I'm	O	-
KD	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
smokin'	O	-
OG	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Smokin'	O	-
OG	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

And	O	-
you	O	-
know	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
2-3s	B-MISC	North American
and	O	-
my	O	-
gold	O	-
teeth	O	-
(	O	-
And	O	-
my	O	-
gold	O	-
teeth	O	-
)	O	-

Bitch	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
smiling	O	-
,	O	-
bet	O	-
you	O	-
see	O	-
me	O	-
from	O	-
the	O	-
nosebleeds	O	-
(	O	-
Nosebleeds	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
the	O	-
new	O	-
three	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
change	O	-
out	O	-
to	O	-
my	O	-
new	O	-
3s	O	-
(	O	-
To	O	-
my	O	-
new	O	-
3s	O	-
)	O	-

White	O	-
Iverson	B-PER	North American

When	O	-
I	O	-
started	O	-
ballin'	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
was	O	-
young	O	-

You	O	-
gon'	O	-
think	O	-
about	O	-
me	O	-
when	O	-
I'm	O	-
gone	O	-

I	O	-
need	O	-
that	O	-
money	O	-
like	O	-
the	O	-
ring	O	-
I	O	-
never	O	-
won	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
won	O	-

Saucin'	O	-
,	O	-
saucin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
saucin'	O	-
on	O	-
you	O	-

I'm	O	-
swaggin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
swaggin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
swaggin'	O	-
,	O	-
oh-ooh	O	-

I'm	O	-
ballin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
ballin'	O	-
,	O	-
Iverson	O	-
on	O	-
you	O	-

Watch	O	-
out	O	-
,	O	-
watch	O	-
out	O	-
,	O	-
watch	O	-
out	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

That's	O	-
my	O	-
shot	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
my	O	-
shot	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
my	O	-
shot	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Spendin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
spendin'	O	-
all	O	-
my	O	-
fuckin'	O	-
pay	O	-

Ooh	O	-
,	O	-
Stoney	B-PER	North American

Cigarettes	O	-
and	O	-
a	O	-
headband	O	-

Commas	O	-
,	O	-
commas	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
head	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-

Slumped	O	-
over	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
dead	O	-
man	O	-

Red	O	-
and	O	-
black	O	-
,	O	-
'	O	-
bout	O	-
my	O	-
bread	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-

I'm	O	-
the	O	-
answer	O	-
,	O	-
never	O	-
question	O	-

Lace	O	-
up	O	-
,	O	-
learn	O	-
a	O	-
lesson	O	-

Bitch	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
saucin'	O	-
(	O	-
Wow	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
do	O	-
this	O	-
often	O	-
,	O	-
don't	O	-
do	O	-
no	O	-
talkin'	O	-
(	O	-
No	O	-
)	O	-

My	O	-
options	O	-
right	O	-
when	O	-
I	O	-
walk	O	-
in	O	-
,	O	-
jump	O	-
all	O	-
them	O	-
Jordans	B-ORG	North American
(	O	-
Ooh	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
ballin'	O	-
,	O	-
money	O	-
jumpin'	O	-

Like	O	-
I'm	O	-
Davis	B-PER	North American
from	O	-
New	B-LOC	North American
Orleans	I-LOC	North American

Or	O	-
bitch	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
Harden	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
I	O	-
don't	O	-
miss	O	-
nothin'	O	-

Fuck	O	-
practice	O	-
,	O	-
this	O	-
shit	O	-
just	O	-
happens	O	-
,	O	-
know	O	-
y'all	O	-
can't	O	-
stand	O	-
it	O	-
(	O	-
Ayy	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
have	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
never	O	-
pass	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
work	O	-
my	O	-
magic	O	-

High	O	-
average	O	-
,	O	-
ball	O	-
on	O	-
these	O	-
bastards	O	-
,	O	-
it	O	-
makes	O	-
me	O	-
happy	O	-

It's	O	-
tragic	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
make	O	-
it	O	-
happen	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
all	O	-
y'all	O	-
Shaqtin'	B-MISC	North American

White	O	-
Iverson	B-PER	North American

When	O	-
I	O	-
started	O	-
ballin'	O	-
I	O	-
was	O	-
young	O	-

You	O	-
gon'	O	-
think	O	-
about	O	-
me	O	-
when	O	-
I'm	O	-
gone	O	-

I	O	-
need	O	-
that	O	-
money	O	-
like	O	-
the	O	-
ring	O	-
I	O	-
never	O	-
won	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
won	O	-

Saucin'	O	-
,	O	-
saucin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
saucin'	O	-
on	O	-
you	O	-

I'm	O	-
swaggin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
swaggin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
swaggin'	O	-
,	O	-
oh-ooh	O	-

I'm	O	-
ballin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
ballin'	O	-
,	O	-
Iverson	B-PER	North American
on	O	-
you	O	-

Watch	O	-
out	O	-
,	O	-
watch	O	-
out	O	-
,	O	-
watch	O	-
out	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

That's	O	-
my	O	-
shot	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
my	O	-
shot	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
my	O	-
shot	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Spendin'	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
spendin'	O	-
all	O	-
my	O	-
fuckin'	O	-
pay	O	-

Ooh-ooh	O	-

Ooh-ooh	O	-

Ooh-ooh	O	-

Ooh-ooh	O	-

Yo	O	-
,	O	-
Pi'erre	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
you	O	-
wanna	O	-
come	O	-
out	O	-
here	O	-
?	O	-

Uh	O	-

In	O	-
New	B-LOC	North American
York	I-LOC	North American
I	O	-
Milly	B-MISC	North American
Rock	I-MISC	European
(	O	-
Rock	O	-
)	O	-

Hide	O	-
it	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
sock	O	-
(	O	-
Sock	O	-
)	O	-

Running	O	-
from	O	-
an	O	-
opp	O	-
(	O	-
Opp	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I	O	-
shoot	O	-
at	O	-
opp	O	-
(	O	-
Opp	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
block	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
block	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

In	O	-
New	B-LOC	North American
York	I-LOC	North American
I	O	-
Milly	B-MISC	North American
Rock	I-MISC	European
(	O	-
Hello	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Hide	O	-
it	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
sock	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Hide	O	-
it	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
sock	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Selling	O	-
that	O	-
rerock	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Uh	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

In	O	-
New	B-LOC	North American
York	I-LOC	North American
I	O	-
Milly	B-MISC	North American
Rock	I-MISC	European
(	O	-
Ooh	O	-
)	O	-

Hide	O	-
it	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
sock	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
)	O	-

Used	O	-
to	O	-
sell	O	-
rerock	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Runnin'	O	-
from	O	-
the	O	-
cops	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
)	O	-

Shootin'	O	-
at	O	-
these	O	-
opps	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
)	O	-

Yo	O	-
,	O	-
Pi'erre	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
you	O	-
wanna	O	-
come	O	-
out	O	-
here	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
)	O	-

Shooting	O	-
at	O	-
these	O	-
opps	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
run	O	-
they	O	-
block	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

Give	O	-
me	O	-
top	O	-
(	O	-
Top	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
,	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
drop-top	O	-

All	O	-
these	O	-
hoes	B-MISC	North American
gon'	O	-
flock	O	-
(	O	-
Flock	O	-
,	O	-
flock	O	-
)	O	-

When	O	-
I	O	-
drop	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
(	O	-
Drop	O	-
,	O	-
drop	O	-
)	O	-

All	O	-
these	O	-
hoes	B-MISC	North American
gon'	O	-
flock	O	-
(	O	-
Flock	O	-
,	O	-
flock	O	-
)	O	-

When	O	-
I	O	-
drop	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
(	O	-
Drop	O	-
,	O	-
drop	O	-
)	O	-

All	O	-
these	O	-
hoes	B-MISC	North American
gon'	O	-
flock	O	-
(	O	-
Flock	O	-
,	O	-
flock	O	-
)	O	-

When	O	-
I	O	-
drop	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
(	O	-
Drop	O	-
,	O	-
drop	O	-
)	O	-

Woo	O	-
,	O	-
woo	O	-
,	O	-
woo	O	-
,	O	-
woo	O	-
(	O	-
Beep	O	-
)	O	-

Woo	O	-
,	O	-
woo	O	-
(	O	-
Beep	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woo	O	-
,	O	-
woo	O	-
(	O	-
Beep	O	-
)	O	-

All	O	-
these	O	-
hoes	O	-
want	O	-
cash	O	-
(	O	-
Cash	B-PER	North American
)	O	-

All	O	-
these	O	-
hoes	O	-
want	O	-
bags	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

Fucking	O	-
on	O	-
your	O	-
bitch	O	-
(	O	-
Beep	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

I'm	O	-
her	O	-
dad	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

All	O	-
these	O	-
niggas	O	-
sound	O	-
like	O	-
Cash	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
sound	O	-
like	O	-
Cash	B-PER	North American
(	O	-
Blah	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
a	O	-
soldier	O	-
,	O	-
ooh	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Damn	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
thought	O	-
I	O	-
told	O	-
you	O	-
,	O	-
ooh	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Shootin'	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
soldier	O	-
,	O	-
ooh	O	-
(	O	-
Beep	O	-
)	O	-

Like	O	-
I'm	O	-
from	O	-
Magnolia	B-LOC	North American
,	O	-
ooh	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

All	O	-
these	O	-
niggas	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
always	O	-
fold	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Big	O	-
bank	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
never	O	-
fold	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
sippin'	O	-
Act'	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
fill	O	-
that	O	-
shit	O	-
slowly	O	-
(	O	-
Hello	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Bitches	O	-
on	O	-
me	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Beep	O	-
)	O	-
say	O	-
she	O	-
like	O	-
my	O	-
clothing	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
in	O	-
London	B-LOC	European
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
Yung	O	-
Carti	B-PER	North American
global	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Designer	B-MISC	Non-cultural
is	O	-
on	O	-
me	O	-
(	O	-
Phew	O	-
)	O	-
call	O	-
it	O	-
dirty	O	-
laundry	O	-
(	O	-
Phew	O	-
)	O	-

Ayy	O	-
,	O	-
Yung	O	-
Carti	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
Yung	O	-
Carti	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Hop	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
bit'	O	-
,	O	-
hop	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
bit'	O	-
)	O	-

Yung	O	-
Carti	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
Yung	O	-
Carti	B-PER	North American
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Hold	O	-
on	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

All	O	-
of	O	-
your	O	-
bitches	O	-
,	O	-
they	O	-
loose	O	-
,	O	-
hold	O	-
on	O	-

All	O	-
of	O	-
your	O	-
bitches	O	-
,	O	-
they	O	-
loose	O	-
,	O	-
hold	O	-
on	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

All	O	-
of	O	-
my	O	-
bitches	O	-
,	O	-
they	O	-
rich	O	-
,	O	-
hold	O	-
on	O	-

And	O	-
they	O	-
stay	O	-
rockin'	O	-
that	O	-
Rick	B-ORG	North American
,	O	-
hold	O	-
on	O	-

(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Uh	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Hold	O	-
on	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Uh	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Rich	O	-
,	O	-
rich	O	-
(	O	-
Rich	O	-
)	O	-

Cash	O	-
Carti	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
bitch	O	-
(	O	-
Bitch	O	-
)	O	-

Rich	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-
(	O	-
Hold	O	-
on	O	-
)	O	-

Got	O	-
a	O	-
rich	O	-
clique	B-MISC	European
(	O	-
Hold	O	-
on	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
suckin'	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
clit	O	-
(	O	-
Hold	O	-
on	O	-
)	O	-

She	O	-
suckin'	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
dick	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Give	O	-
that	O	-
ho	O	-
a	O	-
tip	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Told	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Buy	O	-
some	O	-
kicks	O	-
"	O	-
(	O	-
Kicks	O	-
)	O	-

Ooh	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
I	O	-
brush	O	-
my	O	-
teeth	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Hop	O	-
up	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
whip	O	-

Glocky	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
whip	O	-
(	O	-
Skrrt	O	-
)	O	-

Glocky	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
whip	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
cocky	O	-
,	O	-
fuckin'	O	-
on	O	-
a	O	-
thotty	O	-

She	O	-
just	O	-
wanna	O	-
plot	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-
can't	O	-
stop	O	-
me	O	-
(	O	-
Stop	O	-
me	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
ridin'	O	-
in	O	-
a	O	-
Masi	B-ORG	European
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Masi	B-ORG	European
)	O	-

This	O	-
ain't	O	-
even	O	-
my	O	-
Masi	B-ORG	European
(	O	-
Nah	O	-
)	O	-

Hope	O	-
that's	O	-
not	O	-
your	O	-
thotty	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Your	O	-
bitch	O	-
look	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
auntie	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Walked	O	-
in	O	-
with	O	-
Ashanti	B-PER	North American
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Damn	O	-
,	O	-
that	O	-
look	O	-
like	O	-
'	O	-
Shanti	B-PER	North American
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Damn	O	-
,	O	-
that	O	-
look	O	-
like	O	-
Carti	B-PER	North American
(	O	-
Yeah-yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
think	O	-
that	O	-
be	O	-
Yung	O	-
Carti	B-PER	North American

Heard	O	-
he	O	-
spent	O	-
a	O	-
hundred	O	-
on	O	-
a	O	-
fucking	O	-
watch	B-MISC	Non-cultural
piece	I-MISC	Non-cultural
,	O	-
that's	O	-
filthy	O	-
(	O	-
Phew	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
)	O	-

In	O	-
New	B-LOC	North American
York	I-LOC	North American
I	O	-
Milly	B-MISC	North American
Rock	I-MISC	European
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Hide	O	-
it	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
sock	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Running	O	-
from	O	-
an	O	-
opp	B-MISC	Non-cultural
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I	O	-
shoot	O	-
at	O	-
opp	B-MISC	Non-cultural
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
(	O	-
Phew	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
block	O	-
(	O	-
Phew	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
(	O	-
Hello	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
block	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

In	O	-
New	B-LOC	North American
York	I-LOC	North American
I	O	-
Milly	B-MISC	North American
Rock	I-MISC	European
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Hide	O	-
it	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
sock	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Hide	O	-
it	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
sock	O	-
(	O	-
Sock	O	-
)	O	-

Selling	O	-
that	O	-
rerock	O	-
(	O	-
Rerock	O	-
)	O	-

What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

What	O	-
?	O	-
Uh	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-

In	O	-
New	B-LOC	North American
York	I-LOC	North American
I	O	-
Milly	B-MISC	North American
Rock	I-MISC	European
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Hide	O	-
it	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
sock	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Use	O	-
to	O	-
sell	O	-
rerock	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

Runnin'	O	-
from	O	-
the	O	-
cops	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

Shootin'	O	-
at	O	-
these	O	-
opps	O	-

You	O	-
know	O	-
what	O	-
I'm	O	-
sayin'	O	-
?	O	-

Yo	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
Pi'erre	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
you	O	-
wanna	O	-
come	O	-
out	O	-
here	O	-
?	O	-

Bitch	O	-
ass	O	-
nigga	O	-
,	O	-
fuck	O	-
that	O	-
nigga	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-

Yeah	O	-

Now	O	-

Now	O	-
is	O	-
my	O	-
time	O	-

Now	O	-
is	O	-
my	O	-
time	O	-

(	O	-
That-that	O	-
-	O	-
that-that	O	-
-	O	-
that-that	O	-
be	O	-
Maaly	B-PER	North American
Raw	I-PER	North American
)	O	-

Everybody	O	-
rock	O	-
with	O	-
me	O	-
because	O	-
I'm	O	-
up	O	-
now	O	-

Took	O	-
your	O	-
girl	O	-
and	O	-
I'ma	O	-
score	O	-
like	O	-
I	O	-
made	O	-
the	O	-
touchdown	B-MISC	North American

Swervin'	B-MISC	North American
in	O	-
that	O	-
Lambo'	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
doors	O	-
go	O	-
up	O	-
,	O	-
not	O	-
on	O	-
a	O	-
bus	O	-
now	O	-

Used	O	-
to	O	-
want	O	-
a	O	-
G-Shock	B-ORG	North American
,	O	-
now	O	-
I'm	O	-
walking	O	-
with	O	-
a	O	-
bustdown	B-MISC	North American

Pull	O	-
up	O	-
and	O	-
I'm	O	-
flooded	O	-
with	O	-
a	O	-
iced	B-MISC	North American
out	I-MISC	North American
watch	O	-

Whip	O	-
,	O	-
it	O	-
look	O	-
like	O	-
butter	O	-
,	O	-
baby	O	-
,	O	-
pecan	O	-
drop	O	-

Pecan	O	-
drop	O	-
,	O	-
put	O	-
that	O	-
four	O	-
in	O	-
Sun	B-ORG	North American
Drop	I-ORG	North American

Stack	O	-
my	O	-
knots	O	-
,	O	-
count	O	-
a	O	-
lot	O	-
,	O	-
saw	O	-
a	O	-
lot	O	-

Got	O	-
them	O	-
rocks	O	-
,	O	-
diamond	O	-
rocks	O	-
,	O	-
whip	O	-
the	O	-
pot	O	-

Suicide	O	-
,	O	-
1600	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
that's	O	-
the	O	-
block	O	-

Hit	O	-
your	O	-
girl	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
check-free	O	-

She	O	-
ain't	O	-
used	O	-
to	O	-
text	O	-
me	O	-

Now	O	-
she	O	-
wanna	O	-
caress	O	-
me	O	-

She	O	-
keep	O	-
tryna	O	-
neck	O	-
me	O	-

I	O	-
gotta	O	-
tell	O	-
my	O	-
bestie	O	-

Someone	O	-
call	O	-
my	O	-
bestie	O	-

Think	O	-
I	O	-
found	O	-
my	O	-
bestie	O	-

Link	O	-
up	O	-
,	O	-
make	O	-
a	O	-
check	O	-
bleed	O	-

You	O	-
know	O	-
that	O	-
I'm	O	-
smokin'	O	-
dope	O	-
,	O	-
I'll	O	-
be	O	-
high	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
next	O	-
week	O	-

Know	O	-
I	O	-
had	O	-
to	O	-
let	O	-
her	O	-
go	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
she	O	-
can't	O	-
arrest	O	-
me	O	-

Uh	O	-
,	O	-
woke	O	-
up	O	-
with	O	-
my	O	-
toolie	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
what	O	-
it	O	-
do	O	-
?	O	-
Huh	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

Meet	O	-
me	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
alley	O	-
with	O	-
the	O	-
troops	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

I	O	-
got	O	-
red	O	-
shooters	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
blue	O	-
,	O	-
huh	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Let	O	-
that	O	-
thing	O	-
down	O	-
and	O	-
point	O	-
at	O	-
you	O	-
,	O	-
huh	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

Bentley	B-ORG	European
or	O	-
the	O	-
'	O	-
Rari	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
ho	O	-
,	O	-
let's	O	-
choose	O	-
,	O	-
ooh	O	-

We	O	-
gon'	O	-
rob	O	-
the	O	-
bank	O	-
,	O	-
bring	O	-
the	O	-
loot	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

We	O	-
gon'	O	-
take	O	-
these	O	-
boys	O	-
back	O	-
to	O	-
school	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

Money	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
floor	O	-
just	O	-
like	O	-
some	O	-
shoes	O	-

Uh	O	-
,	O	-
money	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
floor	O	-
just	O	-
like	O	-
some	O	-
shoes	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

I'ma	O	-
fuck	O	-
your	O	-
thot	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
she	O	-
just	O	-
a	O	-
swoop	O	-
,	O	-
hah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

I'ma	O	-
fuck	O	-
your	O	-
thot	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
she	O	-
just	O	-
a	O	-
swoop	O	-
,	O	-
hah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

And	O	-
I	O	-
love	O	-
my	O	-
goons	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

And	O	-
I	O	-
love	O	-
my	O	-
tool	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
I	O	-
love	O	-
my	O	-
loot	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Fuck	O	-
with	O	-
me	O	-
and	O	-
you	O	-
gon'	O	-
lose	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Don't	O	-
talk	O	-
to	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
just	O	-
talk	O	-
to	O	-
my	O	-
lil'	O	-
dude	O	-

Don't	O	-
talk	O	-
to	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
just	O	-
talk	O	-
to	O	-
my	O	-
lil'	O	-
dude	O	-

Uh	O	-
,	O	-
woke	O	-
up	O	-
with	O	-
my	O	-
toolie	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
what	O	-
it	O	-
do	O	-
?	O	-
Huh	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

Meet	O	-
me	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
alley	O	-
with	O	-
the	O	-
troops	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

I	O	-
got	O	-
red	O	-
shooters	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
blue	O	-
,	O	-
huh	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Let	O	-
that	O	-
thing	O	-
down	O	-
and	O	-
point	O	-
at	O	-
you	O	-
,	O	-
huh	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

Bentley	B-ORG	European
or	O	-
the	O	-
'	O	-
Rari	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
ho	O	-
,	O	-
let's	O	-
choose	O	-
,	O	-
ooh	O	-

We	O	-
gon'	O	-
rob	O	-
the	O	-
bank	O	-
,	O	-
bring	O	-
the	O	-
loot	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

We	O	-
gon'	O	-
take	O	-
these	O	-
boys	O	-
back	O	-
to	O	-
school	O	-
,	O	-
uh	O	-

Money	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
floor	O	-
just	O	-
like	O	-
some	O	-
shoes	O	-

I	O	-
said	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Girl	O	-
,	O	-
why	O	-
you	O	-
keep	O	-
callin'	O	-
?	O	-
"	O	-

I	O	-
said	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Girl	O	-
,	O	-
why	O	-
you	O	-
keep	O	-
callin'	O	-
?	O	-
"	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

She	O	-
said	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
a	O	-
new	O	-
whip	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
that	O	-
you	O	-
still	O	-
ballin'	O	-
"	O	-

She	O	-
just	O	-
wanna	O	-
go	O	-
back	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
future	O	-
,	O	-
so	O	-
I	O	-
bought	O	-
that	O	-
girl	O	-
a	O	-
DeLorean	B-ORG	European

Twenty	O	-
one	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I	O	-
got'	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
so	O	-
I	O	-
told	O	-
that	O	-
girl	O	-
I'm	O	-
gonna	O	-
slaughter	O	-
it	O	-

I	O	-
met	O	-
that	O	-
girl	O	-
right	O	-
up	O	-
at	O	-
my	O	-
show	O	-

Left	O	-
her	O	-
man	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
crowd	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
floor	O	-
(	O	-
Floor	O	-
)	O	-

Out	O	-
of	O	-
town	O	-
never	O	-
saw	O	-
her	O	-
before	O	-

Told	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Baby	O	-
,	O	-
we	O	-
don't	O	-
got	O	-
that	O	-
long	O	-
"	O	-

Listen	O	-
,	O	-
this	O	-
not	O	-
my	O	-
city	O	-
show	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
treat	O	-
it	O	-
like	O	-
my	O	-
city	O	-
show	O	-

Twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
,	O	-
twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
,	O	-
twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-

Twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
,	O	-
twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
am	O	-
not	O	-
slow	O	-
,	O	-
these	O	-
girls	O	-
just	O	-
want	O	-
me	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
the	O	-
dough	O	-

Pass	O	-
that	O	-
girl	O	-
right	O	-
on	O	-
my	O	-
friend	O	-
,	O	-
give	O	-
and	O	-
go	O	-

He	O	-
pass	O	-
me	O	-
her	O	-
friend	O	-
,	O	-
so	O	-
they	O	-
switchin'	O	-
roles	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
hit	O	-
it	O	-
fast	O	-
(	O	-
F-f	O	-
-	O	-
f-fast	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
hit	O	-
it	O	-
slow	O	-
(	O	-
Slow	O	-
)	O	-

But	O	-
by	O	-
the	O	-
mornin'	O	-
,	O	-
girl	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
gotta	O	-
go	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Gotta	O	-
get	O	-
ready	O	-
,	O	-
tonight	O	-
is	O	-
my	O	-
show	O	-

If	O	-
you	O	-
okay	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
might	O	-
open	O	-
my	O	-
show	O	-

Got	O	-
the	O	-
big	O	-
pointers	O	-
right	O	-
under	O	-
my	O	-
nose	O	-

These	O	-
niggas	O	-
mad	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
all	O	-
the	O	-
dough	B-MISC	North American

These	O	-
niggas	O	-
mad	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
all	O	-
the	O	-
dough	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Changin'	O	-
my	O	-
style	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
every	O	-
flow	O	-

Got	O	-
every	O	-
girl	O	-
,	O	-
ain't	O	-
no	O	-
toppin'	O	-
my	O	-
hoes	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
understand	O	-
that	O	-
is	O	-
your	O	-
girlfriend	O	-
,	O	-
bro	O	-

But	O	-
you	O	-
know	O	-
I	O	-
gotta	O	-
keep	O	-
her	O	-
close	O	-

Open	O	-
your	O	-
legs	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
keep	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
closed	O	-

Livin'	O	-
life	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
edge	O	-
,	O	-
on	O	-
a	O	-
tightrope	O	-

I	O	-
am	O	-
so	O	-
clean	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
might	O	-
start	O	-
movin'	O	-
soap	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Drive	O	-
a	O	-
new	O	-
'	O	-
Rari	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
I	O	-
don't	O	-
need	O	-
a	O	-
note	O	-
(	O	-
Skrrt	O	-
)	O	-

Drive	O	-
a	O	-
Bugatti	B-ORG	European
like	O	-
it's	O	-
a	O	-
Volvo	B-ORG	European

I	O	-
got	O	-
your	O	-
girl	O	-
and	O	-
you	O	-
already	O	-
know	O	-
(	O	-
Skrrt	O	-
)	O	-

Don't	O	-
really	O	-
like	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
we	O	-
friends	O	-
for	O	-
the	O	-
most	O	-

Cuban	B-LOC	Latin
link	O	-
tri-color	O	-
,	O	-
all	O	-
on	O	-
my	O	-
choker	B-MISC	Non-cultural
(	O	-
Skrrt	O	-
)	O	-

Don't	O	-
leave	O	-
the	O	-
crumb	O	-
,	O	-
got	O	-
the	O	-
bread	O	-
,	O	-
then	O	-
you	O	-
toast	O	-

If	O	-
you	O	-
start	O	-
touchin'	O	-
my	O	-
gun	O	-
,	O	-
got	O	-
no	O	-
holst'	O	-

I	O	-
put	O	-
a	O	-
coat	O	-
on	O	-
top	O	-
of	O	-
my	O	-
coat	O	-

Only	O	-
twenty	O	-
minutes	O	-
before	O	-
the	O	-
show	O	-
(	O	-
Show	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
met	O	-
that	O	-
girl	O	-
right	O	-
up	O	-
at	O	-
my	O	-
show	O	-

Left	O	-
her	O	-
man	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
crowd	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
floor	O	-

Out	O	-
of	O	-
town	O	-
,	O	-
never	O	-
saw	O	-
her	O	-
before	O	-

Told	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Baby	O	-
,	O	-
we	O	-
don't	O	-
got	O	-
that	O	-
long	O	-
"	O	-

Listen	O	-
,	O	-
this	O	-
not	O	-
my	O	-
city	O	-
show	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
treat	O	-
it	O	-
like	O	-
my	O	-
city	O	-
show	O	-

Twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
,	O	-
twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-

Twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
,	O	-
twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-

Twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
,	O	-
twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
am	O	-
not	O	-
slow	O	-
,	O	-
these	O	-
girls	O	-
just	O	-
want	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
the	O	-
dough	O	-

Pass	O	-
that	O	-
girl	O	-
right	O	-
on	O	-
my	O	-
friend	O	-
,	O	-
give	O	-
and	O	-
go	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

He	O	-
pass	O	-
me	O	-
her	O	-
friend	O	-
,	O	-
so	O	-
they	O	-
switchin'	O	-
roles	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Damn	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
just	O	-
started	O	-
it	O	-
(	O	-
Started	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
just	O	-
started	O	-
it	O	-

Oh	O	-
my	O	-
God	B-PER	Non-cultural
,	O	-
please	O	-
,	O	-
do	O	-
not	O	-
bother	O	-
me	O	-

Don't	O	-
got	O	-
enough	O	-
just	O	-
to	O	-
order	O	-
me	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
on	O	-
that	O	-
tree	O	-
like	O	-
an	O	-
ornament	O	-

Money	O	-
so	O	-
long	O	-
like	O	-
accordion	B-MISC	European
(	O	-
Woo	O	-
)	O	-

You	O	-
lied	O	-
to	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
wasn't	O	-
sorry	O	-
then	O	-

On	O	-
the	O	-
weekend	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
was	O	-
partyin'	O	-

It	O	-
was	O	-
just	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
was	O	-
targetin'	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

It	O	-
was	O	-
just	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
was	O	-
targetin'	O	-
(	O	-
Target	O	-
)	O	-

Jump	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
Porsche	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
I	O	-
might	O	-
target	O	-
it	O	-
(	O	-
Skrr	O	-
)	O	-

Jump	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
Lamb'	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
I	O	-
ain't	O	-
parkin'	O	-
it	O	-
(	O	-
Skrr	O	-
)	O	-

Ice	B-ORG	North American
is	O	-
so	O	-
cold	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
snowboard	O	-
in	O	-
it	O	-
(	O	-
Blaow	O	-
)	O	-

Go	O	-
to	O	-
my	O	-
show	O	-
,	O	-
they	O	-
applaud	O	-
me	O	-
in	O	-

She	O	-
call	O	-
my	O	-
phone	O	-
with	O	-
emergency	O	-
(	O	-
Ayy	O	-
)	O	-

She	O	-
call	O	-
my	O	-
phone	O	-
with	O	-
that	O	-
urgency	O	-
(	O	-
Ayy	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
said	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Girl	O	-
,	O	-
why	O	-
you	O	-
keep	O	-
callin'	O	-
?	O	-
"	O	-
(	O	-
Ayy	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
said	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Girl	O	-
,	O	-
why	O	-
you	O	-
keep	O	-
callin'	O	-
?	O	-
"	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

She	O	-
said	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
a	O	-
new	O	-
whip	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
"	O	-
yeah	O	-
(	O	-
Skrr	O	-
)	O	-

"	O	-
'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
that	O	-
you	O	-
still	O	-
ballin'	B-MISC	North American
"	O	-
(	O	-
Ball	O	-
!	O	-
)	O	-

She	O	-
just	O	-
wanna	O	-
go	O	-
back	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
future	O	-
,	O	-
so	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
brought	O	-
that	O	-
girl	O	-
a	O	-
DeLorean	B-ORG	European
(	O	-
Yah	O	-
)	O	-

Twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I	O	-
got'	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
so	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
told	O	-
that	O	-
girl	O	-
that	O	-
I'm	O	-
gonna	O	-
slaughter	O	-
it	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
met	O	-
that	O	-
girl	O	-
right	O	-
up	O	-
at	O	-
my	O	-
show	O	-

Left	O	-
her	O	-
man	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
crowd	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
floor	O	-

Out	O	-
of	O	-
town	O	-
,	O	-
never	O	-
saw	O	-
her	O	-
before	O	-

Told	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Baby	O	-
,	O	-
we	O	-
don't	O	-
got	O	-
that	O	-
long	O	-
"	O	-

Listen	O	-
,	O	-
this	O	-
not	O	-
my	O	-
city	O	-
show	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
treat	O	-
it	O	-
like	O	-
my	O	-
city	O	-
show	O	-

Twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
,	O	-
twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-

Twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
,	O	-
twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-

Twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
,	O	-
twenty	O	-
more	O	-
minutes	O	-
until	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
am	O	-
not	O	-
slow	O	-
,	O	-
these	O	-
girls	O	-
just	O	-
want	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
the	O	-
dough	O	-

Pass	O	-
that	O	-
girl	O	-
right	O	-
on	O	-
my	O	-
friend	O	-
,	O	-
give	O	-
and	O	-
go	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

He	O	-
pass	O	-
me	O	-
her	O	-
friend	O	-
,	O	-
so	O	-
they	O	-
switchin'	O	-
roles	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
yah	O	-

(	O	-
Four	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
)	O	-

(	O	-
Four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
don't	O	-
know	O	-
where	O	-
I’m	O	-
going	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

But	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
what	O	-
I'm	O	-
showing	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

Feelings	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
what	O	-
I’m	O	-
pouring	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

What	O	-
the	O	-
fuck	O	-
is	O	-
your	O	-
motive	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

Man	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
wish	O	-
you	O	-
would	O	-
call	O	-
me	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

By	B-MISC	North American
your	I-MISC	North American
name	I-MISC	North American
'	O	-
cause	O	-
I'm	O	-
sorry	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

This	O	-
is	O	-
not	O	-
apology	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

You	O	-
are	O	-
such	O	-
a	O	-
distraction	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

That's	O	-
what	O	-
T	B-PER	North American
on	O	-
,	O	-
aw	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

Fuckin'	O	-
up	O	-
my	O	-
ambiance	O	-
,	O	-
pause	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

You	O	-
drive	O	-
me	O	-
cuckoo	O	-
and	O	-
not	O	-
car	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
I	O	-
want	O	-
you	O	-
like	O	-
Leon	B-PER	North American
Ware	I-PER	North American
(	O	-
Fuck	O	-
that	O	-
)	O	-

Okay	O	-
,	O	-
say	O	-
again	O	-
it	O	-
(	O	-
Fuck	O	-
that	O	-
)	O	-

Okay	O	-
,	O	-
wait	O	-
a	O	-
minute	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
dread	O	-
that	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
am	O	-
Anwar	B-PER	Middle Eastern
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

Curiosity	O	-
killed	O	-
the	O	-
feline	O	-
,	O	-
gone	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
think	O	-
I've	O	-
fallen	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

This	O	-
time	O	-
I	O	-
think	O	-
it's	O	-
for	O	-
real	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
think	O	-
I’ve	O	-
fallen	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
)	O	-

This	O	-
time	O	-
I	O	-
think	O	-
it’s	O	-
for	O	-
real	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-
How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-
How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-
How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-
How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
notice	O	-
that	O	-
you're	O	-
there	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
I’m	O	-
always	O	-
in	O	-
your	O	-
hair	O	-

And	O	-
you're	O	-
always	O	-
under	O	-
my	O	-
microscope	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

Waste	O	-
of	O	-
bread	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
your	O	-
attention	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
off	O	-
balance	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
need	O	-
some	O	-
fixin'	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

I’m	O	-
your	O	-
puppet	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
are	O	-
Jim	B-PER	North American
Henson	I-PER	North American
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
)	O	-

Fallen	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
now	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
think	O	-
I've	O	-
fallen	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

Fell	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
now	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

This	O	-
time	O	-
I	O	-
think	O	-
it's	O	-
for	O	-
real	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
think	O	-
I'm	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
now	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
think	O	-
I've	O	-
fallen	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
think	O	-
I'm	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
now	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

This	O	-
time	O	-
I	O	-
think	O	-
it's	O	-
for	O	-
real	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Shut	O	-
the	O	-
fuck	O	-
up	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
You	O	-
fuckin'	O	-
bitch	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

How	O	-
can	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-

Take	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
bridge	O	-

(	O	-
Four	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
)	O	-

Four	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
think	O	-
I've	O	-
fallen	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

Fell	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
now	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

This	O	-
time	O	-
I	O	-
think	O	-
it's	O	-
for	O	-
real	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
think	O	-
I'm	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
now	O	-
(	O	-
Skate	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
think	O	-
I've	O	-
fallen	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
(	O	-
Four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
)	O	-

This	O	-
time	O	-
I	O	-
think	O	-
it's	O	-
for	O	-
real	O	-
(	O	-
Oh	O	-
,	O	-
oh	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
)	O	-

(	O	-
Four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
,	O	-
four	O	-
,	O	-
skate	O	-
)	O	-

(	O	-
Ness	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
beat	O	-
)	O	-

Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
okay	O	-
,	O	-
okay	O	-
,	O	-
okay	O	-

Demon	B-PER	Non-cultural
just	O	-
got	O	-
out	O	-
the	O	-
can	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
gave	O	-
my	O	-
bro	O	-
an	O	-
advance	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Love	O	-
is	O	-
just	O	-
not	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
plans	O	-

Not	O	-
even	O	-
takin'	O	-
a	O	-
chance	O	-

Studio	O	-
right	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
yaad	B-MISC	European

I'm	O	-
doin'	O	-
ten	O	-
in	O	-
a	O	-
week	O	-

How	O	-
long	O	-
I	O	-
been	O	-
on	O	-
this	O	-
streak	O	-
?	O	-

Dream	O	-
about	O	-
work	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
sleep	O	-
(	O	-
Oof	O	-
)	O	-

Okay	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
got	O	-
a	O	-
lock	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
streets	O	-

Shoutout	O	-
to	O	-
T	B-PER	North American
,	O	-
he	O	-
did	O	-
three	O	-

And	O	-
he	O	-
brought	O	-
it	O	-
in	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
of	O	-
me	O	-

You	O	-
don't	O	-
know	O	-
nothin'	O	-
'	O	-
bout	O	-
me	O	-

Life	O	-
for	O	-
my	O	-
bruddas	B-MISC	European
is	O	-
deep	O	-

Long	O	-
as	O	-
they	O	-
all	O	-
on	O	-
they	O	-
feet	O	-

Long	O	-
as	O	-
they	O	-
pockets	O	-
is	O	-
greaze	B-MISC	European
(	O	-
Greaze	O	-
!	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
penthouse	O	-
but	O	-
still	O	-
,	O	-
nothin'	O	-
is	O	-
sweet	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Dust	O	-
a	O	-
man	O	-
down	O	-
with	O	-
the	O	-
pen	O	-
,	O	-
it's	O	-
a	O	-
sweep	B-MISC	Non-cultural
(	O	-
Mmm	O	-
!	O	-
)	O	-

Taller	O	-
in	O	-
person	O	-
,	O	-
you'll	O	-
see	O	-
when	O	-
we	O	-
meet	O	-

I	O	-
heard	O	-
your	O	-
new	O	-
shit	O	-
and	O	-
I'm	O	-
kissin'	O	-
my	O	-
teeth	O	-

Jheeze	B-MISC	European
!	O	-

You	O	-
know	O	-
dem	B-MISC	European
ones	O	-
?	O	-
Hahaha	O	-

Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
ahh	O	-
!	O	-

Bringin'	O	-
that	O	-
dirty-dirty	O	-
,	O	-
bringin'	O	-
that	O	-
certy	B-MISC	European
(	O	-
Certy	O	-
)	O	-

Mizzy	B-PER	European
with	O	-
the	O	-
quick	O	-
extension	O	-
,	O	-
ringin'	O	-
off	O	-
thirty	O	-
(	O	-
Rah	O	-
!	O	-
)	O	-

I've	O	-
got	O	-
bitches	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
merky	B-MISC	European
,	O	-
swervin'	O	-
,	O	-
lookin'	O	-
all	O	-
curvy	O	-

And	O	-
you	O	-
already	O	-
know	O	-
I	O	-
love	O	-
them	O	-
breasts	O	-
,	O	-
lookin'	O	-
all	O	-
perky	O	-

Lookin'	O	-
all	O	-
Christmas	B-MISC	Non-cultural
gift-wrapped	O	-
,	O	-
lookin'	O	-
all	O	-
turkey	O	-

Spen	B-PER	European
jumped	O	-
out	O	-
the	O	-
Ghost	B-ORG	Non-cultural
in	O	-
a	O	-
suit	O	-
,	O	-
lookin'	O	-
all	O	-
churchy	B-MISC	Non-cultural
(	O	-
Oof	O	-
!	O	-
)	O	-

Fingers	O	-
all	O	-
itchin'	O	-
,	O	-
twitchin'	O	-
,	O	-
lookin'	O	-
all	O	-
jerky	O	-
(	O	-
Jerky	O	-
)	O	-

Whippin'	O	-
that	O	-
white	O	-
girl	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
cookin'	O	-
that	O	-
Cersei	B-ORG	European
(	O	-
Dah	O	-
!	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
was	O	-
pushin'	O	-
that	O	-
dark	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
pushin'	O	-
that	O	-
charcoal	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Now	O	-
this	O	-
is	O	-
that	O	-
big	O	-
bad	O	-
,	O	-
this	O	-
is	O	-
Gustavo	B-PER	Latin
(	O	-
Mmm	O	-
!	O	-
)	O	-

Look	O	-
at	O	-
them	O	-
jokers	O	-
,	O	-
look	O	-
at	O	-
that	O	-
arsehole	O	-
(	O	-
That	O	-
arsehole	O	-
)	O	-

Man	O	-
are	O	-
gettin'	O	-
bread	B-MISC	North American
now	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
this	O	-
is	O	-
that	O	-
hard	O	-
dough	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Clap	O	-
man	O	-
,	O	-
dominant	O	-
murder	O	-
(	O	-
'	O	-
Nant	O	-
murder	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
a	O	-
black	O	-
man	O	-
(	O	-
Black	O	-
man	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
government	O	-
earner	O	-
(	O	-
Earner	O	-
)	O	-

Could've	O	-
just	O	-
slapped	O	-
man	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
he	O	-
wanted	O	-
it	O	-
further	O	-
(	O	-
Why	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Batman	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
da-na	O	-
-	O	-
na-da	O	-
-	O	-
na	O	-

October	B-ORG	North American
Firm	I-ORG	North American

Aha	O	-
,	O	-
aha	O	-

I	O	-
said	O	-
it	O	-
must	O	-
be	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
got	O	-
dough	B-MISC	North American

Extraordinary	O	-
swag	B-MISC	North American
and	O	-
a	O	-
mouth	O	-
full	O	-
of	O	-
gold	O	-

Hoes	B-MISC	North American
at	O	-
my	O	-
shows	O	-
they	O	-
be	O	-
strippin'	O	-
off	O	-
they	O	-
clothes	O	-

And	O	-
them	O	-
college	O	-
girls	O	-
write	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
name	O	-
on	O	-
they	O	-
toes	O	-

Niggas	O	-
talk	O	-
shit	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
they	O	-
get	O	-
lockjaw	O	-

Chrome	B-MISC	Non-cultural
to	O	-
ya	O	-
dome	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
ya	O	-
get	O	-
glockjaw	B-MISC	North American

Party	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
cowboy	B-MISC	North American
or	O	-
a	O	-
rockstar	B-MISC	North American

Everybody	O	-
play	O	-
the	O	-
tough	O	-
guy	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
shit	O	-
pop	O	-
off	O	-

Let's	O	-
take	O	-
it	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
basics	O	-
,	O	-
you	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
midst	O	-
of	O	-
greatness	O	-

My	O	-
Martin	B-ORG	North American
was	O	-
a	O	-
Maison	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
rocked	O	-
Margielas	B-ORG	European
with	O	-
no	O	-
laces	O	-

Cristal	B-ORG	European
go	O	-
by	O	-
the	O	-
cases	O	-
,	O	-
wait	O	-
hold	O	-
up	O	-
that	O	-
was	O	-
racist	O	-

I	O	-
would	O	-
prefer	O	-
the	O	-
Aces	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
ain't	O	-
no	O	-
different	O	-
when	O	-
you	O	-
taste	O	-
it	O	-

A	O	-
40	O	-
ounce	O	-
to	O	-
chase	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
that's	O	-
just	O	-
a	O	-
understatement	O	-

I'm	O	-
early	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
party	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
my	O	-
'	O	-
Rari	B-ORG	European
is	O	-
the	O	-
latest	O	-

Somehow	O	-
it	O	-
seems	O	-
girls	O	-
in	O	-
they	O	-
late	O	-
teens	O	-

Remind	O	-
me	O	-
your	O	-
favorite	O	-
jeans	O	-
cause	O	-
they	O	-
naked	O	-
cause	O	-
you	O	-
famous	O	-

Life's	O	-
a	O	-
mothafucka	O	-
,	O	-
ain't	O	-
it	O	-
?	O	-
These	O	-
other	O	-
rappers	O	-
ain't	O	-
us	O	-

So	O	-
tell	O	-
me	O	-
what	O	-
your	O	-
name	O	-
is	O	-
,	O	-
I'ma	O	-
tell	O	-
it	O	-
to	O	-
my	O	-
stainless	O	-

You	O	-
aim	O	-
it	O	-
'	O	-
fore	O	-
you	O	-
bang	O	-
it	O	-
let	O	-
that	O	-
banger	O	-
leave	O	-
you	O	-
brainless	O	-

It's	O	-
just	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
myself	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
and	O	-
mothafuckas	O	-
that	O	-
I	O	-
came	O	-
with	O	-

Miscellaneous	O	-
niggas	O	-
wanna	O	-
hate	O	-
on	O	-
me	O	-

Until	O	-
I	O	-
tell	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
to	O	-
they	O	-
face	O	-
they	O	-
ain't	O	-
no	O	-
G	B-MISC	North America

Low	O	-
key	O	-
,	O	-
niggas	O	-
mad	O	-
cause	O	-
I'm	O	-
smooth	O	-
puffin'	O	-
Zig	B-MISC	European
Zags	I-MISC	European

Tell	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
quit	O	-
the	O	-
riff	B-MISC	Non-cultural
raff	I-MISC	Non-cultural
bitchin'	O	-
with	O	-
your	O	-
bitch	O	-
ass	O	-

I	O	-
said	O	-
it	O	-
must	O	-
be	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
got	O	-
dough	B-MISC	North American

Extraordinary	O	-
swag	B-MISC	North American
and	O	-
a	O	-
mouth	O	-
full	O	-
of	O	-
gold	O	-

Hoes	B-MISC	North American
at	O	-
my	O	-
shows	O	-
they	O	-
be	O	-
strippin'	O	-
off	O	-
they	O	-
clothes	O	-

And	O	-
them	O	-
college	O	-
girls	O	-
write	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
name	O	-
on	O	-
they	O	-
toes	O	-

Niggas	O	-
talk	O	-
shit	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
they	O	-
get	O	-
lockjaw	O	-

Chrome	B-MISC	Non-cultural
to	O	-
ya	O	-
dome	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
ya	O	-
get	O	-
glockjaw	B-MISC	North American

Party	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
cowboy	B-MISC	North American
or	O	-
a	O	-
rockstar	B-MISC	North American

Everybody	O	-
play	O	-
the	O	-
tough	O	-
guy	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
shit	O	-
pop	O	-
off	O	-

Yes	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
the	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
tell	O	-
me	O	-
do	O	-
it	O	-
stink	O	-
?	O	-

It	O	-
feel	O	-
good	O	-
wakin'	O	-
up	O	-
to	O	-
money	O	-
in	O	-
the	O	-
bank	O	-

Three	O	-
model	O	-
bitches	O	-
,	O	-
cocaine	B-MISC	Non-cultural
on	O	-
the	O	-
sink	O	-

And	O	-
I'm	O	-
so	O	-
'	O	-
bout	O	-
it	O	-
'	O	-
bout	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
might	O	-
roll	O	-
up	O	-
in	O	-
a	O	-
tank	O	-

Cause	O	-
my	O	-
chain	O	-
came	O	-
from	O	-
Cuba	B-LOC	Latin
,	O	-
got	O	-
a	O	-
lock	O	-
up	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
link	O	-

And	O	-
them	O	-
red	B-MISC	European
bottom	I-MISC	European
loafers	O	-
just	O	-
to	O	-
compliment	O	-
the	O	-
mink	O	-

Eyes	O	-
chink	O	-
,	O	-
rollin'	O	-
up	O	-
that	O	-
dank	O	-
,	O	-
blowin'	O	-
on	O	-
that	O	-
stank	O	-

What	O	-
you	O	-
mean	O	-
?	O	-
Tell	O	-
me	O	-
what	O	-
you	O	-
drink	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
on	O	-
that	O	-
kissin'	O	-
pink	O	-

Man	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
moon	O	-
,	O	-
got	O	-
a	O	-
condo	O	-
out	O	-
in	O	-
space	O	-

Open	O	-
up	O	-
your	O	-
legs	O	-
,	O	-
tell	O	-
me	O	-
how	O	-
it	O	-
taste	O	-

And	O	-
them	O	-
niggas	O	-
talkin'	O	-
shit	O	-
so	O	-
tell	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
,	O	-
“	O	-
Tell	O	-
it	O	-
to	O	-
my	O	-
face	O	-
”	O	-

Tell	O	-
that	O	-
bitch	O	-
,	O	-
hop	O	-
up	O	-
on	O	-
my	O	-
dick	O	-
,	O	-
rolled	O	-
up	O	-
on	O	-
her	O	-
quick	O	-

In	O	-
a	O	-
six	O	-
,	O	-
told	O	-
her	O	-
suck	O	-
a	O	-
dick	O	-
,	O	-
motorboat	O	-
her	O	-
tits	O	-

I'm	O	-
the	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
niggas	O	-
mad	O	-
cause	O	-
I'm	O	-
smooth	O	-
puffin'	O	-
Zig-Zags	B-MISC	European

Tell	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
quit	O	-
the	O	-
riff	B-MISC	Non-cultural
raff	I-MISC	Non-cultural
bitchin'	O	-
with	O	-
your	O	-
bitch	O	-
ass	O	-

I	O	-
said	O	-
it	O	-
must	O	-
be	O	-
'	O	-
cause	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
got	O	-
dough	B-MISC	North American

Extraordinary	O	-
swag	B-MISC	North American
and	O	-
a	O	-
mouth	O	-
full	O	-
of	O	-
gold	O	-

Hoes	B-MISC	North American
at	O	-
my	O	-
shows	O	-
they	O	-
be	O	-
strippin'	O	-
off	O	-
they	O	-
clothes	O	-

And	O	-
them	O	-
college	O	-
girls	O	-
write	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
name	O	-
on	O	-
they	O	-
toes	O	-

Niggas	O	-
talk	O	-
shit	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
they	O	-
get	O	-
lockjaw	O	-

Chrome	B-MISC	Non-cultural
to	O	-
ya	O	-
dome	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
ya	O	-
get	O	-
glockjaw	B-MISC	North American

Party	O	-
like	O	-
a	O	-
cowboy	B-MISC	North American
or	O	-
a	O	-
rockstar	B-MISC	North American

Everybody	O	-
play	O	-
the	O	-
tough	O	-
guy	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
shit	O	-
pop	O	-
off	O	-

Oh	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
oh	O	-
,	O	-
right	O	-

Oh	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Oh	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
oh	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Oh	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-

Everybody	O	-
play	O	-
the	O	-
tough	O	-
guy	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
shit	O	-
pop	O	-
off	O	-
(	O	-
Right	O	-
,	O	-
right	O	-
)	O	-

Every	O	-
day	O	-
I	O	-
spend	O	-
my	O	-
time	O	-

Drinkin'	O	-
wine	O	-
,	O	-
feelin'	O	-
fine	O	-

Waitin'	O	-
here	O	-
to	O	-
find	O	-
the	O	-
sign	O	-

That	O	-
I	O	-
can	O	-
understand	O	-
,	O	-
yes	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
am	O	-

So	O	-
every	O	-
day	O	-
I	O	-
spend	O	-
my	O	-
time	O	-

Drinkin'	O	-
wine	O	-
,	O	-
feelin'	O	-
fine	O	-

Waiting	O	-
here	O	-
to	O	-
find	O	-
the	O	-
sign	O	-

That	O	-
I	O	-
should	O	-
take	O	-
it	O	-
slow	O	-

Here	O	-
I	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
here	O	-
I	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
here	O	-
I	O	-
go	O	-

Off	O	-
again	O	-
,	O	-
there	O	-
he	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
to	O	-
another	O	-
dimension	O	-
,	O	-
my	O	-
mind	O	-

Body	O	-
,	O	-
soul	O	-
imprisoned	O	-
,	O	-
my	O	-
eye	O	-
probably	O	-
goin'	O	-
ballistic	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
,	O	-
listen	O	-

I'm	O	-
missin'	O	-
a	O	-
couple	O	-
of	O	-
screws	O	-
,	O	-
they	O	-
ain't	O	-
never	O	-
do	O	-
drillin'	O	-
true	O	-

You	O	-
been	O	-
sippin'	O	-
away	O	-
at	O	-
the	O	-
truth	O	-
,	O	-
a	O	-
double	O	-
shot	O	-
of	O	-
wisdom'll	O	-
do	O	-

Do	O	-
,	O	-
do	O	-
,	O	-
rollin'	O	-
through	O	-
,	O	-
hittin'	O	-
switches	O	-

Rolling	O	-
ditches	O	-
,	O	-
blowin'	O	-
kisses	O	-
,	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
bitches	O	-
,	O	-
holdin'	O	-
biscuits	O	-

What's	O	-
the	O	-
business	O	-
?	O	-
Beat	O	-
the	O	-
system	O	-

Co-defendants	O	-
,	O	-
blow	O	-
the	O	-
sentence	O	-
,	O	-
go	O	-
to	O	-
prison	O	-

Go	O	-
to	O	-
church	B-MISC	Non-cultural
and	O	-
pray	O	-
the	B-PER	Non-cultural
father	I-PER	Non-cultura
,	O	-
Lord	B-PER	Non-cultural
forgive	O	-
us	O	-
(	O	-
Amen	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
only	O	-
God	B-PER	Non-cultural
can	O	-
judge	O	-
me	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
he	O	-
don't	O	-
like	O	-
no	O	-
ugly	O	-

I	O	-
look	O	-
so	O	-
fuckin'	O	-
good	O	-
,	O	-
most	O	-
dykes'll	O	-
fuck	O	-
me	O	-
,	O	-
buddy	O	-

Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
a	O	-
piece	O	-
of	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
I	O	-
plead	O	-
the	O	-
fifth	O	-

I	O	-
tell	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Holler	O	-
if	O	-
ya	O	-
need	O	-
some	O	-
dick	O	-
"	O	-

The	O	-
devotion	O	-
is	O	-
gettin'	O	-
hopeless	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
,	O	-
hold	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
gettin'	O	-
close	O	-

As	O	-
my	O	-
soul	O	-
is	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
seein'	O	-
ghosts	O	-
,	O	-
a	O	-
solo	O	-
is	O	-
now	O	-
a	O	-
poet	O	-

Hypnosis	O	-
overdose	O	-
on	O	-
potions	O	-
,	O	-
adjustin'	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
motions	O	-

And	O	-
gettin'	O	-
out	O	-
all	O	-
my	O	-
emotions	O	-

Every	O	-
day	O	-
I	O	-
spend	O	-
my	O	-
time	O	-

Drinkin'	O	-
wine	O	-
,	O	-
feelin'	O	-
fine	O	-

Waitin'	O	-
here	O	-
to	O	-
find	O	-
the	O	-
sign	O	-

That	O	-
I	O	-
can	O	-
understand	O	-
,	O	-
yes	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
am	O	-

So	O	-
every	O	-
day	O	-
I	O	-
spend	O	-
my	O	-
time	O	-

Drinkin'	O	-
wine	O	-
,	O	-
feelin'	O	-
fine	O	-

Waiting	O	-
here	O	-
to	O	-
find	O	-
the	O	-
sign	O	-

That	O	-
I	O	-
should	O	-
take	O	-
it	O	-
slow	O	-

Here	O	-
I	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
here	O	-
I	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
here	O	-
I	O	-
go	O	-

Uh	O	-
,	O	-
this	O	-
type	O	-
of	O	-
shit	O	-

Make	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
wanna	O	-
flip	O	-
September	O	-
through	O	-
August	O	-

This	O	-
type	O	-
of	O	-
shit	O	-
got	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
bustin'	O	-
out	O	-
the	O	-
clip	O	-

In	O	-
the	O	-
middle	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
office	O	-

And	O	-
a	O	-
message	O	-
to	O	-
the	O	-
bosses	O	-

The	O	-
Misfits'	B-ORG	North American
new	O	-
outfit	O	-
is	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
bloglist	O	-

Gorgeous	O	-
hoes	O	-
keep	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
sayin'	O	-
that	O	-
they	O	-
'	O	-
caused	O	-
it	O	-

'	O	-
Cause	O	-
the	O	-
Porsches	B-ORG	European
get	O	-
'	O	-
em	O	-
nauseous	O	-

Plus	O	-
I	O	-
ain't	O	-
even	O	-
mad	O	-
yet	O	-
,	O	-
niggas	O	-
caught	O	-
me	O	-
in	O	-
a	O	-
good	O	-
mood	O	-

Paparazzi	B-MISC	European
wanna	O	-
nag	O	-
a	O	-
nigga	O	-
chillin'	O	-
at	O	-
the	O	-
bag	O	-
check	O	-

Hope	O	-
they	O	-
show	O	-
me	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
good	O	-
shoes	O	-

When	O	-
papa	O	-
got	O	-
the	O	-
brand	O	-
new	O	-
bag	O	-

Flacko	B-PER	European
got	O	-
the	O	-
brand	O	-
new	O	-
Raf	B-ORG	North American
,	O	-
that's	O	-
good	O	-
news	O	-

"	O	-
Hood	O	-
dudes	O	-
usually	O	-
don't	O	-
look	O	-
like	O	-
you	O	-
"	O	-

How	O	-
it	O	-
feel	O	-
to	O	-
get	O	-
a	O	-
deal	O	-
and	O	-
come	O	-
back	O	-

And	O	-
the	O	-
whole	O	-
hood	O	-
look	O	-
like	O	-
you	O	-
?	O	-

Screamin'	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Pimp	B-MISC	North American
Squad	I-MISC	North American
,	O	-
hold	O	-
it	O	-
down	O	-
!	O	-
"	O	-

Can't	O	-
drive	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-
,	O	-
I'm	O	-
legally	O	-
blind	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-

If	O	-
I	O	-
live	O	-
or	O	-
die	O	-
,	O	-
it's	O	-
up	O	-
to	O	-
me	O	-
to	O	-
decide	O	-

Shit	O	-
,	O	-
niggas	O	-
coppin'	O	-
guns	O	-
like	O	-
they	O	-
legal	O	-
to	O	-
buy	O	-

The	O	-
only	O	-
key	O	-
to	O	-
survive	O	-
and	O	-
get	O	-
a	O	-
piece	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
pie	O	-

Is	O	-
to	O	-
agree	O	-
with	O	-
a	O	-
lot	O	-
or	O	-
just	O	-
believe	O	-
a	O	-
façade	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-

And	O	-
I'll	O	-
be	O	-
fine	O	-
just-a	O	-
drinkin'	O	-
my	O	-
wine	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-

I	O	-
got	O	-
the	O	-
love	O	-
birds	O	-
chirpin'	O	-
at	O	-
the	O	-
window	O	-

But	O	-
I	O	-
don't	O	-
need	O	-
love	O	-
no	O	-
more	O	-

I'll	O	-
be	O	-
fine	O	-
,	O	-
sippin'	O	-
wine	O	-

Takin'	O	-
time	O	-
slow	O	-

I	O	-
got	O	-
the	O	-
love	O	-
birds	O	-
chirpin'	O	-
at	O	-
the	O	-
window	O	-

But	O	-
I	O	-
don't	O	-
need	O	-
love	O	-
no	O	-
more	O	-

I'll	O	-
be	O	-
fine	O	-
,	O	-
sippin'	O	-
wine	O	-

So	O	-
every	O	-
day	O	-
I	O	-
spend	O	-
my	O	-
time	O	-

Drinkin'	O	-
wine	O	-
,	O	-
feelin'	O	-
fine	O	-

Waiting	O	-
here	O	-
to	O	-
find	O	-
the	O	-
sign	O	-

That	O	-
I	O	-
can	O	-
understand	O	-
,	O	-
yes	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
am	O	-

Every	O	-
day	O	-
I	O	-
spend	O	-
my	O	-
time	O	-

Drinkin'	O	-
wine	O	-
,	O	-
feelin'	O	-
fine	O	-

Waitin'	O	-
here	O	-
to	O	-
find	O	-
the	O	-
sign	O	-

I	O	-
don't	O	-
care	O	-
if	O	-
I	O	-
ever	O	-
know	O	-

Here	O	-
I	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
here	O	-
I	O	-
go	O	-
,	O	-
here	O	-
I	O	-
go	O	-
!	O	-

I	O	-
got	O	-
the	O	-
love	O	-
birds	O	-
chirpin'	O	-
at	O	-
the	O	-
window	O	-

But	O	-
I	O	-
don't	O	-
need	O	-
love	O	-
no	O	-
more	O	-
,	O	-
oh	O	-
,	O	-
no	O	-

I'll	O	-
be	O	-
fine	O	-
,	O	-
sippin'	O	-
wine	O	-

Takin'	O	-
time	O	-
slow	O	-

I	O	-
got	O	-
the	O	-
love	O	-
birds	O	-
chirpin'	O	-
at	O	-
the	O	-
window	O	-

But	O	-
I	O	-
don't	O	-
need	O	-
love	O	-
no	O	-
more	O	-
,	O	-
oh	O	-
,	O	-
no	O	-

I'll	O	-
be	O	-
fine	O	-
,	O	-
sippin'	O	-
wine	O	-

Takin'	O	-
time	O	-
slow	O	-

What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-

I'm	O	-
so	O	-
high	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
can't	O	-
even	O	-
feel	O	-
shit	O	-

I	O	-
told	O	-
my	O	-
boy	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Go	O	-
roll	O	-
like	O	-
ten	O	-
blunts	B-MISC	North American
for	O	-
me	O	-
"	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Roll	O	-
ten	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
told	O	-
my	O	-
boy	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Go	O	-
roll	O	-
like	O	-
ten	O	-
blunts	B-MISC	North American
for	O	-
me	O	-
"	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Roll	O	-
ten	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
tryna	O	-
get	O	-
high	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
I	O	-
can't	O	-
feel	O	-
nothin'	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
tryna	O	-
get	O	-
high	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
I	O	-
can't	O	-
feel	O	-
nothin'	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Let's	O	-
go	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
could	O	-
fall	O	-
out	O	-
the	O	-
sky	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
still	O	-
won't	O	-
feel	O	-
nothin'	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
slatt	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

I	O	-
could	O	-
fall	O	-
out	O	-
the	O	-
sky	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
still	O	-
won't	O	-
feel	O	-
nothin'	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
way	O	-
too	O	-
high	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
High	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
way	O	-
too	O	-
high	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
way	O	-
too	O	-
high	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
way	O	-
too	O	-
high	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
way	O	-
too	O	-
high	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
)	O	-

Wake	O	-
up	O	-
(	O	-
Wake	O	-
up	O	-
,	O	-
wake	O	-
up	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
)	O	-

It's	O	-
the	O	-
first	O	-
of	O	-
the	O	-
month	O	-
(	O	-
Slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
slatt	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

I	O	-
brush	O	-
my	O	-
teeth	O	-
and	O	-
count	O	-
up	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
woah	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
let	O	-
my	O	-
bitch	O	-
roll	O	-
my	O	-
blunt	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
slatt	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
'	O	-
bout	O	-
to	O	-
dirty	O	-
my	O	-
cup	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
bitch	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Pour	O	-
up	O	-
some	O	-
lean	B-MISC	North American
and	O	-
get	O	-
stuck	O	-
(	O	-
Pour	O	-
it	O	-
up	O	-
,	O	-
pour	O	-
it	O	-
up	O	-
,	O	-
pour	O	-
it	O	-
up	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
make	O	-
her	O	-
scream	O	-
when	O	-
we	O	-
fuck	O	-
(	O	-
Slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
scrеam	O	-
,	O	-
suck	O	-
it	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
don't	O	-
drive	O	-
R8s	B-ORG	European
,	O	-
I	O	-
don't	O	-
like	O	-
those	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
huh	O	-
,	O	-
chop	O	-
it	O	-
and	O	-
slidе	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
drive	O	-
the	O	-
Daytona	B-ORG	European
and	O	-
I	O	-
tinted	O	-
the	O	-
windows	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
skrrt	O	-
)	O	-

Can't	O	-
fuck	O	-
with	O	-
nobody	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
not	O	-
even	O	-
my	O	-
shadow	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
no	O	-
one	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
got	O	-
on	O	-
Ed	B-ORG	North American
Hardy	I-ORG	North American
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
got	O	-
on	O	-
stilettos	B-MISC	European
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

She	O	-
my	O	-
best	O	-
friend	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
we	O	-
not	O	-
a	O	-
couple	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

She	O	-
a	O	-
rockstar	B-MISC	North American
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
a	O	-
sex	B-MISC	Non-cultural
symbol	I-MISC	Non-cultural
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Let's	O	-
go	O	-
)	O	-

The	O	-
way	O	-
she	O	-
do	O	-
that	O	-
shit	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
make	O	-
it	O	-
look	O	-
simple	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

The	O	-
way	O	-
she	O	-
do	O	-
that	O	-
shit	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
make	O	-
it	O	-
look	O	-
simple	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Baby	O	-
,	O	-
tell	O	-
me	O	-
what	O	-
you	O	-
wanna	O	-
do	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
Wanna	O	-
do	O	-
)	O	-

Baby	O	-
,	O	-
tell	O	-
me	O	-
everybody	O	-
you	O	-
screw	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
who	O	-
?	O	-
Who	O	-
?	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

Tell	O	-
me	O	-
everybody	O	-
you	O	-
took	O	-
to	O	-
this	O	-
room	O	-
(	O	-
Who	O	-
?	O	-
Who	O	-
?	O	-
Who	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
gotta	O	-
know	O	-
who	O	-
you	O	-
fuck	O	-
,	O	-
fucked	O	-
in	O	-
this	O	-
room	O	-
(	O	-
Baby	O	-
,	O	-
who	O	-
?	O	-
Who	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
gotta	O	-
know	O	-
who	O	-
you	O	-
fucked	O	-
in	O	-
this	O	-
room	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
who	O	-
?	O	-
Who	O	-
?	O	-
Who	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
gotta	O	-
know	O	-
who	O	-
you	O	-
fucked	O	-
in	O	-
this	O	-
room	O	-
(	O	-
Bih'	O	-
,	O	-
who	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

Can't	O	-
trust	O	-
no	O	-
bitch	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Bih'	O	-
,	O	-
bih'	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
can't	O	-
trust	O	-
these	O	-
niggas	O	-
(	O	-
Bih	O	-
,	O	-
bih'	O	-
)	O	-

Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
with	O	-
my	O	-
money	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
In	O	-
love	O	-
with	O	-
my	O	-
money	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
in	O	-
love	O	-
with	O	-
my	O	-
pistols	O	-
(	O	-
In	O	-
love	O	-
with	O	-
that	O	-
pistol	O	-
)	O	-

In	O	-
love	O	-
with	O	-
my	O	-
bitch	O	-
(	O	-
Love	O	-
with	O	-
my	O	-
bitch	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
think	O	-
she	O	-
my	O	-
bitch	O	-
(	O	-
I	O	-
think	O	-
she	O	-
my	O	-
bitch	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
know	O	-
she	O	-
suck	O	-
dick	O	-
(	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
she	O	-
suck	O	-
dick	O	-
,	O	-
blatt	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
she	O	-
not	O	-
shit	O	-
(	O	-
I	O	-
know	O	-
she	O	-
not	O	-
shit	O	-
,	O	-
huh	O	-
,	O	-
huh	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
been	O	-
thinkin'	O	-
'	O	-
bout	O	-
it	O	-
(	O	-
Been	O	-
thinkin'	O	-
'	O	-
bout	O	-
it	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
finna	O	-
cut	O	-
off	O	-
that	O	-
bitch	O	-
(	O	-
Finna	O	-
cut	O	-
off	O	-
that	O	-
bitch	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

She	O	-
don't	O	-
cook	O	-
,	O	-
she	O	-
don't	O	-
clean	O	-
(	O	-
Damn	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
but	O	-
she	O	-
want	O	-
Ruth	B-ORG	North American
Chris	I-ORG	North American
(	O	-
Slatt	O	-
,	O	-
slatt	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
don't	O	-
even	O	-
like	O	-
to	O	-
hug	O	-
(	O	-
To	O	-
hug	O	-
,	O	-
hug	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
don't	O	-
even	O	-
like	O	-
to	O	-
kiss	O	-
(	O	-
Slatt	O	-
,	O	-
slatt	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
just	O	-
pat	O	-
her	O	-
on	O	-
the	O	-
ass	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
tell	O	-
her	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Good	O	-
shit	O	-
"	O	-
(	O	-
Slatt	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
just	O	-
walked	O	-
in	O	-
my	O	-
pad	O	-
(	O	-
Slatt	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
paparazzi	B-MISC	European
at	O	-
the	O	-
fence	O	-
(	O	-
Slatt	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
'	O	-
bout	O	-
to	O	-
pour	O	-
up	O	-
some	B-MISC	North American
red	I-MISC	European
(	I-MISC	North American
Red	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
shawty	O	-
gon'	O	-
roll	O	-
up	O	-
some	O	-
shit	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
slatt	B-MISC	North American
,	O	-
and	O	-
shawty	O	-
gon'	O	-
)	O	-

And	O	-
shawty	O	-
gon'	O	-
roll	O	-
up	O	-
some	O	-
shit	O	-
(	O	-
Slatt	B-MISC	North American
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
'	O	-
bout	O	-
to	O	-
pour	O	-
up	O	-
some	B-MISC	North American
red	I-MISC	European
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
and	O	-
shawty	O	-
gon'	O	-
roll	O	-
up	O	-
some	O	-
shit	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
told	O	-
my	O	-
boy	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Go	O	-
roll	O	-
like	O	-
ten	O	-
blunts	B-MISC	North American
for	O	-
me	O	-
"	O	-
(	O	-
Alright	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
told	O	-
my	O	-
boy	O	-
,	O	-
"	O	-
Go	O	-
roll	O	-
like	O	-
ten	O	-
blunts	B-MISC	North American
for	O	-
me	O	-
"	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
tryna	O	-
get	O	-
high	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
I	O	-
can't	O	-
feel	O	-
nothin'	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
tryna	O	-
get	O	-
high	O	-
'	O	-
til	O	-
I	O	-
can't	O	-
feel	O	-
nothin'	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Slatt	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
could	O	-
fall	O	-
out	O	-
the	O	-
sky	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
still	O	-
won't	O	-
feel	O	-
nothin'	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
Slatt	O	-
,	O	-
slatt	O	-
)	O	-

I	O	-
could	O	-
fall	O	-
out	O	-
the	O	-
sky	O	-
and	O	-
I	O	-
still	O	-
won't	O	-
feel	O	-
nothin'	O	-
(	O	-
Woah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
Slatt	O	-
,	O	-
slatt	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
way	O	-
too	O	-
high	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
what	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
Blatt	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
way	O	-
too	O	-
high	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
way	O	-
too	O	-
high	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
way	O	-
too	O	-
high	O	-
(	O	-
Yeah	O	-
,	O	-
yeah	O	-
,	O	-
huh	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
,	O	-
woah	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

I'm	O	-
way	O	-
too	O	-
high	O	-
(	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
)	O	-

What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-
What	O	-
?	O	-

I'm	O	-
so	O	-
high	O	-
,	O	-
man	O	-
,	O	-
I	O	-
can't	O	-
even	O	-
feel	O	-
shit	O	-
