Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Zaman	I-ORG
:	O
American	B-LOC
forces	O
killed	O
Shaikh	O
Abdullah	B-PER
al	I-PER
-	I-PER
Ani	I-PER
,	O
the	O
preacher	O
at	O
the	O
mosque	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
Qaim	B-LOC
,	O
near	O
the	O
Syrian	B-LOC
border	O
.	O

[	O
This	O
killing	O
of	O
a	O
respected	O
cleric	O
will	O
be	O
causing	O
us	O
trouble	O
for	O
years	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
]	O

DPA	B-ORG
:	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
authorities	O
announced	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
busted	O
up	O
3	O
terrorist	O
cells	O
operating	O
in	O
Baghdad	B-LOC
.	O

The	O
MoI	B-ORG
in	O
Iraq	B-LOC
is	O
equivalent	O
to	O
the	O
US	B-LOC
FBI	B-ORG
,	O
so	O
this	O
would	O
be	O
like	O
having	O
J.	B-PER
Edgar	I-PER
Hoover	I-PER
unwittingly	O
employ	O
at	O
a	O
high	O
level	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
Weathermen	B-ORG
bombers	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
1960s	O
.	O

The	O
third	O
was	O
being	O
run	O
by	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
an	O
investment	O
firm	O
.	O

You	O
wonder	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
manipulating	O
the	O
market	O
with	O
his	O
bombing	O
targets	O
.	O

The	O
cells	O
were	O
operating	O
in	O
the	O
Ghazaliyah	B-LOC
and	O
al	B-LOC
-	I-LOC
Jihad	I-LOC
districts	O
of	O
the	O
capital	O
.	O

Although	O
the	O
announcement	O
was	O
probably	O
made	O
to	O
show	O
progress	O
in	O
identifying	O
and	O
breaking	O
up	O
terror	O
cells	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
find	O
the	O
news	O
that	O
the	O
Baathists	O
continue	O
to	O
penetrate	O
the	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
government	O
very	O
hopeful	O
.	O

It	O
reminds	O
me	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
ARVN	B-ORG
officers	O
who	O
were	O
secretly	O
working	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
in	O
Vietnam	B-LOC
.	O

Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Zaman	I-ORG
:	O
Guerrillas	O
killed	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Kurdistan	B-ORG
Democratic	I-ORG
Party	I-ORG
after	O
kidnapping	O
him	O
in	O
Mosul	B-LOC
.	O

The	O
police	O
commander	O
of	O
Ninevah	B-LOC
Province	I-LOC
announced	O
that	O
bombings	O
had	O
declined	O
80	O
percent	O
in	O
Mosul	B-LOC
,	O
whereas	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
big	O
jump	O
in	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
kidnappings	O
.	O

On	O
Wednesday	O
guerrillas	O
had	O
kidnapped	O
a	O
cosmetic	O
surgeon	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
their	O
way	O
home	O
.	O

In	O
Suwayrah	B-LOC
,	O
Kut	B-LOC
Province	I-LOC
,	O
two	O
car	O
bombs	O
were	O
discovered	O
before	O
they	O
could	O
be	O
detonated	O
.	O

(	O
Kut	B-LOC
is	O
in	O
southeastern	O
Iraq	B-LOC
and	O
has	O
an	O
overwhelmingly	O
Shiite	O
population	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
on	O
the	O
lookout	O
for	O
Baathist	O
saboteurs	O
and	O
willingly	O
turn	O
them	O
in	O
.	O

This	O
willingness	O
is	O
the	O
main	O
difference	O
in	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
bombings	O
in	O
the	O
south	O
as	O
opposed	O
to	O
the	O
center	O
-	O
north	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
)	O

In	O
Baghdad	B-LOC
Kadhim	B-PER
Talal	I-PER
Husain	I-PER
,	O
assistant	O
dean	O
at	O
the	O
School	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Education	I-ORG
at	O
Mustansiriyah	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
,	O
was	O
assassinated	O
with	O
his	O
driver	O
in	O
the	O
Salikh	B-LOC
district	O
.	O

Guerrillas	O
killed	O
an	O
engineer	O
,	O
Asi	B-PER
Ali	I-PER
,	O
from	O
Tikrit	B-LOC
.	O

They	O
also	O
killed	O
Shaikh	O
Hamid	B-PER
'Akkab	I-PER
,	O
a	O
clan	O
elder	O
of	O
a	O
branch	O
of	O
the	O
Dulaim	B-ORG
tribe	O
in	O
Tikrit	B-LOC
.	O

His	O
mother	O
was	O
also	O
killed	O
in	O
the	O
attack	O
.	O

Two	O
other	O
Dulaim	B-ORG
leaders	O
have	O
been	O
killed	O
in	O
the	O
past	O
week	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O

Guerrillas	O
near	O
Hawijah	B-LOC
launched	O
an	O
attack	O
that	O
left	O
6	O
dead	O
,	O
including	O
4	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
soldiers	O
.	O

One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
Jubur	B-ORG
tribe	O
and	O
was	O
deputy	O
commander	O
of	O
the	O
Hawijah	B-ORG
garrison	O
.	O

Two	O
hundred	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
Batawi	B-ORG
clan	O
of	O
the	O
Dulaim	B-ORG
demonstrated	O
in	O
Baghdad	B-LOC
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
protesting	O
the	O
killing	O
of	O
their	O
clan	O
elder	O
,	O
Shaikh	O
Kadhim	B-PER
Sarhid	I-PER
and	O
4	O
of	O
his	O
sons	O
,	O
by	O
gunmen	O
wearing	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
army	O
uniforms	O
.	O

(	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
largely	O
Sunni	O
Arab	B-LOC
clan	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Sunni	O
observers	O
have	O
accused	O
Shiite	O
elements	O
in	O
the	O
government	O
of	O
being	O
behind	O
the	O
assassination	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
more	O
likely	O
the	O
work	O
of	O
Sunni	O
Arab	B-LOC
guerrillas	O
punishing	O
the	O
Batawi	B-ORG
leaders	O
for	O
cooperating	O
with	O
the	O
Dec.	O
15	O
elections	O
.	O
)	O

Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Zaman	I-ORG
:	O
The	O
Iraqi	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
Electoral	I-ORG
Commission	I-ORG
on	O
Friday	O
denied	O
a	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
Debaathification	B-ORG
Commission	I-ORG
to	O
exclude	O
51	O
individuals	O
from	O
running	O
on	O
party	O
lists	O
in	O
the	O
Dec.	O
15	O
elections	O
on	O
grounds	O
of	O
having	O
been	O
sufficiently	O
involved	O
in	O
Baath	O
activities	O
to	O
warrant	O
their	O
being	O
excluded	O
from	O
civil	O
office	O
.	O

The	O
Commission	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
no	O
legal	O
grounds	O
for	O
such	O
an	O
exclusion	O
.	O

This	O
item	O
is	O
a	O
small	O
one	O
and	O
easily	O
missed	O
.	O

But	O
in	O
my	O
view	O
it	O
is	O
highly	O
significant	O
.	O

The	O
Debaathification	B-ORG
Commission	I-ORG
had	O
been	O
pushed	O
by	O
Ahmad	B-PER
Chalabi	I-PER
and	O
his	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
National	B-ORG
Congress	I-ORG
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pushed	O
many	O
Sunni	O
Arabs	B-LOC
into	O
the	O
arms	O
of	O
the	O
guerrillas	O
.	O

Chalabi	B-PER
has	O
been	O
increasingly	O
marginalized	O
within	O
Iraq	B-LOC
,	O
however	O
,	O
despite	O
his	O
ties	O
of	O
clientelage	O
with	O
Washington	B-ORG
and	O
Tehran	B-ORG
.	O

He	O
is	O
no	O
longer	O
in	O
the	O
dominant	O
Shiite	O
list	O
,	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
Iraqi	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
,	O
and	O
wo	O
n't	O
have	O
many	O
seats	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
parliament	O
.	O

Some	O
2,000	O
junior	O
officers	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
Baath	O
army	O
have	O
been	O
recalled	O
to	O
duty	O
in	O
recent	O
months	O
,	O
something	O
Chalabi	B-PER
would	O
have	O
blocked	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
.	O

Now	O
the	O
Electoral	O
Commission	O
is	O
refusing	O
to	O
punish	O
people	O
for	O
mere	O
past	O
Baath	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
membership	O
.	O

The	O
situation	O
in	O
Iraq	B-LOC
is	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
better	O
this	O
way	O
.	O

If	O
someone	O
committed	O
a	O
crime	O
against	O
humanity	O
,	O
prosecute	O
the	O
person	O
.	O

If	O
he	O
or	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
same	O
rights	O
as	O
other	O
Iraqis	B-LOC
.	O

Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Sharq	I-ORG
al	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
Awsat	I-ORG
reports	O
that	O
a	O
key	O
eyewitness	O
in	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Saddam	B-PER
Hussein	I-PER
for	O
a	O
1982	O
massacre	O
at	O
Dujail	B-LOC
has	O
died	O
.	O

A	O
team	O
from	O
the	O
court	O
managed	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
deposition	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
.	O

The	O
trial	O
begins	O
again	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O

In	O
Baghdad	B-LOC
the	O
fighting	O
still	O
continues	O
in	O
several	O
areas	O
,	O
mostly	O
in	O
Sadr	B-LOC
city	I-LOC
and	O
Adhamiya	B-LOC
.	O

Baghdadis	B-LOC
do	O
n't	O
venture	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
neighbourhoods	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
know	O
where	O
you	O
might	O
get	O
stuck	O
.	O

There	O
has	O
been	O
talk	O
that	O
the	O
night	O
curfew	O
might	O
be	O
implemented	O
again	O
.	O

My	O
neighbourhood	O
has	O
been	O
surrounded	O
by	O
American	B-LOC
troops	O
for	O
three	O
days	O
now	O
,	O
helicopters	O
have	O
been	O
circling	O
over	O
our	O
heads	O
non-stop	O
.	O

Fedayeen	O
are	O
now	O
visible	O
on	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
become	O
bolder	O
than	O
ever	O
.	O

Yesterday	O
there	O
were	O
tens	O
of	O
them	O
putting	O
road	O
blocks	O
on	O
our	O
street	O
and	O
setting	O
up	O
mortars	O
,	O
they	O
only	O
come	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
when	O
Americans	B-LOC
leave	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
start	O
firing	O
mortars	O
indiscriminately	O
and	O
shooting	O
their	O
AK	B-MISC
-	I-MISC
47's	I-MISC
in	O
the	O
air	O
.	O

They	O
are	O
setting	O
the	O
road	O
blocks	O
at	O
the	O
exact	O
same	O
positions	O
they	O
were	O
during	O
the	O
war	O
last	O
year	O
,	O
which	O
indicates	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
people	O
.	O

And	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
we	O
can	O
do	O
about	O
it	O
really	O
,	O
people	O
who	O
are	O
suggesting	O
that	O
we	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
fight	O
them	O
are	O
living	O
in	O
dream	O
land	O
.	O

Even	O
the	O
IP	B-ORG
and	O
ICDC	B-ORG
have	O
abandoned	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
are	O
trained	O
and	O
armed	O
,	O
so	O
do	O
n't	O
expect	O
scared	O
civilians	O
to	O
do	O
anything	O
except	O
to	O
hide	O
inside	O
and	O
pray	O
a	O
helicopter	O
or	O
a	O
tank	O
does	O
n't	O
bomb	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
how	O
are	O
American	B-LOC
soldiers	O
going	O
to	O
distinguish	O
the	O
brave	O
and	O
valiant	O
civilians	O
from	O
the	O
Fedayeen	O
?	O

Everyone	O
is	O
apprehensive	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
talk	O
that	O
April	O
9th	O
and	O
10th	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
bloody	O
days	O
.	O

Most	O
people	O
have	O
n't	O
gone	O
to	O
work	O
the	O
last	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
although	O
it	O
seems	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
Baghdad	B-LOC
is	O
'	O
normal	O
'	O
(	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
define	O
what	O
normal	O
is	O
)	O
.	O

There	O
are	O
rumours	O
about	O
preparations	O
by	O
slum	O
dwellers	O
for	O
another	O
looting	O
spree	O
against	O
banks	O
,	O
governmental	O
and	O
public	O
property	O
similar	O
to	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
took	O
place	O
last	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
overheard	O
youngsters	O
in	O
my	O
neighbourhood	O
joking	O
about	O
it	O
and	O
saying	O
things	O
like	O
"	O
This	O
time	O
we	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
to	O
loot	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
n't	O
get	O
anything	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
"	O
.	O

Mosques	O
are	O
calling	O
for	O
donating	O
blood	O
,	O
food	O
,	O
and	O
medicine	O
for	O
Fallujah	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
several	O
convoys	O
have	O
already	O
headed	O
out	O
for	O
Fallujah	B-LOC
,	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
returned	O
later	O
though	O
.	O

What	O
irritates	O
me	O
is	O
this	O
sudden	O
false	O
'	O
solidarity	O
'	O
between	O
Sunni	O
and	O
Shi'ite	O
clerics	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
s	O
throats	O
when	O
they	O
have	O
the	O
chance	O
,	O
and	O
Shia	O
clerics	O
were	O
describing	O
Fallujan	B-LOC
insurgents	O
as	O
'	O
Ba'athists	O
'	O
,	O
'	O
Saddamites	B-PER
'	O
,	O
'	O
Wahhabis	B-PER
'	O
,	O
and	O
'	O
terrorists	O
'	O
just	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O

So	O
what	O
happened	O
?	O

I	O
guess	O
it	O
's	O
just	O
the	O
old	O
new	O
Arab	B-LOC
'	O
Me	O
against	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
against	O
my	O
cousin	O
,	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
cousin	O
against	O
my	O
enemy	O
'	O
,	O
or	O
'	O
The	O
enemy	O
of	O
my	O
enemy	O
is	O
my	O
friend	O
'	O
thing	O
going	O
on	O
again	O
.	O

Speaking	O
of	O
Fallujah	B-LOC
,	O
we	O
have	O
only	O
Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Jazeera	I-ORG
to	O
rely	O
on	O
for	O
our	O
news	O
from	O
there	O
.	O

They	O
have	O
sent	O
over	O
their	O
top	O
reporter	O
Ahmed	B-PER
Mansour	I-PER
to	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
spouting	O
all	O
kinds	O
of	O
propaganda	O
hourly	O
reminding	O
me	O
of	O
Al	B-PER
-	I-PER
Sahhaf	I-PER
.	O

"	O
They	O
are	O
targetting	O
ambulances	O
"	O
,	O
"	O
American	B-LOC
snipers	O
are	O
shooting	O
children	O
and	O
pregnant	O
women	O
"	O
,	O
and	O
"	O
They	O
are	O
using	O
cluster	O
bombs	O
against	O
civilians	O
"	O
is	O
all	O
you	O
get	O
to	O
hear	O
from	O
him	O
.	O

He	O
did	O
once	O
make	O
an	O
unforgivable	O
error	O
when	O
he	O
mentioned	O
that	O
Fallujan	B-LOC
militants	O
were	O
shooting	O
at	O
the	O
Marines	B-ORG
from	O
the	O
roofs	O
of	O
mosques	O
and	O
houses	O
in	O
Hay	B-LOC
Al	I-LOC
-	I-LOC
Golan	I-LOC
,	O
but	O
of	O
course	O
that	O
is	O
okay	O
for	O
Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Jazeera	I-ORG
.	O

Someone	O
who	O
called	O
himself	O
Abu	B-PER
Hafs	I-PER
from	O
the	O
Ibn	B-ORG
Al	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
Khattab	I-ORG
Brigades	I-ORG
(	O
another	O
new	O
group	O
)	O
was	O
on	O
Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Jazeera	I-ORG
describing	O
the	O
enormous	O
casualties	O
among	O
the	O
Marines	B-ORG
and	O
he	O
sweared	O
that	O
American	B-LOC
soldiers	O
were	O
mutilating	O
the	O
bodies	O
of	O
dead	O
insurgents	O
.	O

Over	O
300	O
Iraqis	B-LOC
are	O
reported	O
dead	O
and	O
500	O
reported	O
wounded	O
in	O
Fallujah	B-LOC
alone	O
.	O

Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Iraqiyah	I-ORG
tv	I-ORG
said	O
that	O
ICDC	B-ORG
were	O
controlling	O
Ramadi	B-LOC
.	O

Azzaman	B-ORG
newspaper	O
mentioned	O
an	O
announcement	O
signed	O
by	O
Abdul	B-PER
Aziz	I-PER
bin	I-PER
Muqrin	I-PER
,	O
an	O
Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
operative	O
in	O
Saudi	B-LOC
Arabia	I-LOC
on	O
an	O
Islamic	O
website	O
'	O
the	B-MISC
voice	I-MISC
of	I-MISC
Jihad	I-MISC
'	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
stated	O
that	O
"	O
although	O
mutilating	O
dead	O
bodies	O
is	O
not	O
originally	O
permitted	O
in	O
Islam	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
it	O
is	O
allowed	O
if	O
Muslims	O
use	O
it	O
against	O
infidels	O
to	O
deter	O
them	O
from	O
committing	O
criminal	O
actions	O
"	O
.	O

He	O
added	O
that	O
"	O
America	B-ORG
does	O
not	O
understand	O
anything	O
except	O
the	O
language	O
of	O
force	O
and	O
retaliation	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
kicked	O
out	O
of	O
Somalia	B-LOC
in	O
humiliation	O
after	O
that	O
soldier	O
was	O
dragged	O
in	O
Mogadishu	B-LOC
for	O
the	O
whole	O
world	O
to	O
see	O
"	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
"	O
the	O
day	O
will	O
come	O
when	O
the	O
dead	O
bodies	O
of	O
Americans	B-LOC
and	O
Jews	O
would	O
be	O
dragged	O
,	O
defiled	O
,	O
and	O
stepped	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
Arabian	B-LOC
peninsula	I-LOC
together	O
with	O
their	O
agents	O
and	O
supporters	O
"	O
.	O

Elena	B-PER
's	I-PER
motorcycle	O
tour	O
through	O
the	O
region	O
around	O
Chernobyl	B-LOC
has	O
revived	O
interest	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
serious	O
nuclear	O
disasters	O
in	O
history	O
.	O

We	O
all	O
know	O
what	O
happened	O
,	O
but	O
even	O
to	O
this	O
day	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
different	O
versions	O
and	O
opinions	O
on	O
how	O
it	O
happened	O
and	O
what	O
effect	O
Chernobyl	B-MISC
will	O
have	O
on	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
people	O
affected	O
by	O
the	O
fallout	O
.	O

UPDATE	O
:	O

Now	O
you	O
can	O
tour	O
Chernobyl	B-LOC
and	O
write	O
your	O
own	O
story	O
.	O

This	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
post	O
about	O
fault	O
-	O
finding	O
or	O
assigning	O
blame	O
.	O

It	O
is	O
a	O
time	O
to	O
learn	O
what	O
happened	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
may	O
affect	O
the	O
future	O
.	O

There	O
was	O
a	O
soothing	O
authoritative	O
UNSCEAR	B-ORG
(	O
United	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG
Scientific	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
on	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Effects	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Atomic	I-ORG
Radiation	I-ORG
)	O
report	O
in	O
2000	O
on	O
the	O
health	O
effects	O
of	O
Chernobyl	B-MISC
confirming	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
scientific	O
evidence	O
of	O
any	O
significant	O
radiation	O
-	O
related	O
health	O
effects	O
to	O
most	O
people	O
exposed	O
.	O

This	O
was	O
heavily	O
promoted	O
by	O
the	O
Australasian	B-ORG
Radiation	I-ORG
Protection	I-ORG
Society	I-ORG
in	O
a	O
press	O
release	O
titled	O
THE	B-MISC
MYTHS	I-MISC
OF	I-MISC
CHERNOBYL	I-MISC
which	O
contained	O
the	O
following	O
:	O

One	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
widespread	O
myths	O
of	O
recent	O
times	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
Chernobyl	B-MISC
nuclear	O
reactor	O
accident	O
in	O
1986	O
caused	O
many	O
thousands	O
of	O
extra	O
cancer	O
deaths	O
in	O
neighbouring	O
regions	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
public	O
health	O
has	O
been	O
severely	O
affected	O
by	O
exposure	O
to	O
radiation	O
.	O

Many	O
people	O
still	O
believe	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
even	O
though	O
the	O
Ministry	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Russian	I-ORG
Federation	I-ORG
on	I-ORG
Civil	I-ORG
Defence	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Emergencies	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Elimination	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Conseguences	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Natural	I-ORG
Disasters	I-ORG
(	O
EMERCOM	B-ORG
of	O
Russia	B-LOC
)	O
reported	O
this	O
in	O
1996	O
:	O

CHERNOBYL	B-MISC
ACCIDENT	O
:	O
TEN	O
YEARS	O
ON	O

In	O
the	O
last	O
decade	O
,	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
real	O
and	O
significant	O
increase	O
in	O
childhood	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
extent	O
,	O
adult	O
carcinoma	O
of	O
the	O
thyroid	O
in	O
contaminated	O
regions	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Soviet	B-ORG
Union	I-ORG
(	O
Wi940	O
)	O
which	O
should	O
be	O
attributed	O
to	O
the	O
Chernobyl	B-MISC
accident	O
until	O
proven	O
otherwise	O
.	O

The	O
prestigious	O
IAEA	B-ORG
(	O
International	B-ORG
Atomic	I-ORG
Energy	I-ORG
Agency	I-ORG
)	O
published	O
an	O
early	O
report	O
on	O
Chernobyl	B-MISC
which	O
was	O
based	O
on	O
information	O
from	O
Russian	B-LOC
sources	O
and	O
stated	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
significant	O
health	O
effects	O
.	O

However	O
,	O
in	O
April	O
2001	O
,	O
the	O
IAEA	B-ORG
published	O
Fifteen	B-MISC
Years	I-MISC
after	I-MISC
the	I-MISC
Chernobyl	I-MISC
Accident	I-MISC
-	I-MISC
Lessons	I-MISC
learned	I-MISC
.	O
which	O
contradict	O
the	O
earlier	O
reports	O
.	O

Here	O
are	O
some	O
excerpts	O
:	O

The	O
dramatic	O
increase	O
in	O
radiation	O
-	O
induced	O
thyroid	O
cancers	O
in	O
children	O
and	O
adolescents	O
in	O
Belarus	B-LOC
,	O
Russia	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
Ukraine	B-LOC
,	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
observed	O
since	O
1991	O
,	O
continues	O
to	O
this	O
day	O
.	O

...	O
a	O
drop	O
in	O
the	O
birth	O
rate	O
,	O
a	O
deterioration	O
in	O
women	O
's	O
reproductive	O
health	O
,	O
an	O
increase	O
in	O
complications	O
during	O
pregnancy	O
and	O
birth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
deterioration	O
in	O
neonatal	O
health	O
....	O

The	O
dynamics	O
of	O
change	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
of	O
children	O
affected	O
by	O
the	O
Chernobyl	B-MISC
accident	O
in	O
all	O
three	O
countries	O
-	O
Belarus	B-LOC
,	O
Russia	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
Ukraine	B-LOC
-	O
in	O
the	O
post-accident	O
period	O
is	O
characterized	O
by	O
persistent	O
negative	O
tendencies	O
:	O
the	O
morbidity	O
rate	O
is	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
really	O
healthy	O
children	O
is	O
dropping	O
,	O
and	O
disability	O
is	O
increasing	O
.	O

As	O
a	O
parent	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
well	O
imagine	O
how	O
painful	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
for	O
those	O
families	O
whose	O
children	O
are	O
succumbing	O
to	O
radiation	O
poisoning	O
.	O

There	O
is	O
a	O
lot	O
to	O
learn	O
about	O
Chernobyl	B-MISC
.	O

Being	O
well	O
-	O
informed	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
certainty	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
desirable	O
in	O
a	O
world	O
of	O
conflicting	O
reports	O
.	O

There	O
are	O
a	O
wealth	O
of	O
references	O
on	O
Chernobyl	B-MISC
.	O

Read	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
following	O
links	O
and	O
draw	O
your	O
own	O
conclusions	O
.	O

These	O
links	O
present	O
the	O
many	O
viewpoints	O
that	O
existed	O
and	O
still	O
exist	O
about	O
the	O
disaster	O
called	O
Chernobyl	B-MISC
:	O

IAEA	B-ORG
Report	O
Lessons	O
learned	O

http://www.ibiblio.org/expo/soviet.exhibit/chernobyl.html	B-MISC

http://www.ibrae.ac.ru/IBRAE/eng/chernobyl/nat_rep/nat_repe.htm#24	B-MISC

http://www.nsrl.ttu.edu/chernobyl/wildlifepreserve.htm	B-MISC

http://www.environmentalchemistry.com/yogi/hazmat/articles/chernobyl1.html	B-MISC

http://digon_va.tripod.com/Chernobyl.htm	B-MISC

http://www.oneworld.org/index_oc/issue196/byckau.html	B-MISC

http://www.collectinghistory.net/chernobyl/	B-MISC

http://www.ukrainianweb.com/chernobyl_ukraine.htm	B-MISC

http://www.bullatomsci.org/issues/1993/s93/s93Marples.html	B-MISC

http://www.calguard.ca.gov/ia/Chernobyl-15%20years.htm	B-MISC

http://www.infoukes.com/history/chornobyl/gregorovich/index.html	B-MISC

http://www.un.org/ha/chernobyl/	B-MISC

http://www.tecsoc.org/pubs/history/2002/apr26.htm	B-MISC

http://www.chernobyl.org.uk/page2.htm	B-MISC

http://www.time.com/time/daily/chernobyl/860901.accident.html	B-MISC

http://www.infoukes.com/history/chornobyl/elg/	B-MISC

http://www.world-nuclear.org/info/chernobyl/inf07.htm	B-MISC

http://www.nea.fr/html/rp/chernobyl/conclusions5.html	B-MISC

http://www.nea.fr/html/rp/chernobyl/c01.html	B-MISC

http://www.nea.fr/html/rp/chernobyl/c05.html	B-MISC

http://www.physics.isu.edu/radinf/chern.htm	B-MISC

http://www.chernobyl.info/en	B-MISC

http://www.arps.org.au/Chernobyl.htm	B-MISC

http://www-formal.stanford.edu/jmc/progress/chernobyl.html	B-MISC

http://www.21stcenturysciencetech.com/articles/chernobyl.html	B-MISC

I	O
would	O
be	O
interested	O
in	O
hearing	O
what	O
conclusions	O
you	O
reached	O
and	O
what	O
you	O
found	O
that	O
was	O
most	O
convincing	O
.	O

radiation	O
:	O

As	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
50's	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
glandular	O
problems	O
and	O
they	O
treated	O
it	O
with	O
radiation	O
therapy	O
(	O
primitive	O
at	O
best	O
!	O
)	O
and	O
stopped	O
when	O
a	O
lesion	O
on	O
my	O
neck	O
started	O
enlarging	O
--	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
CA	O
but	O
stopped	O
the	O
treatments	O
....	O

Remember	O
the	O
old	O
shoe	O
sizing	O
machines	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
form	O
of	O
radiation	O
xray	O
?	O

That	O
too	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O

Do	O
n't	O
have	O
to	O
mention	O
what	O
radiation	O
has	O
done	O
and	O
is	O
still	O
doing	O
to	O
Hirsohima	B-LOC
&	O
Nagaski	B-LOC
folks	O
--	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
no	O
doubts	O
about	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
radiation	O
in	O
Chernobyl	B-LOC
.......	O

The	O
Chernobyl	B-ORG
Children	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
(	O
http://www.adiccp.org/home/default.asp	B-MISC
)	O
offers	O
several	O
ways	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
children	O
of	O
that	O
region	O
.	O

One	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
the	O
Rest	B-MISC
and	I-MISC
Recuperation	I-MISC
Program	I-MISC
,	O
wherein	O
a	O
child	O
can	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
US	B-LOC
for	O
a	O
few	O
weeks	O
in	O
the	O
summer	O
.	O

Even	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
spent	O
receiving	O
wholesome	O
,	O
uncontaminated	O
food	O
,	O
good	O
medical	O
care	O
,	O
etc.	O
can	O
add	O
years	O
to	O
their	O
lives	O
.	O

S.	B-PER
and	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
who	O
has	O
hosted	O
several	O
of	O
these	O
children	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
to	O
see	O
these	O
little	O
ones	O
breaks	O
the	O
heart	O
.	O

The	O
urge	O
to	O
protect	O
and	O
gather	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
is	O
almost	O
overwhelming	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
me	O
more	O
grateful	O
for	O
the	O
blessings	O
I	O
have	O
.	O

Take	O
care	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
Linda	B-PER

I	O
'm	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
Elena	B-PER
's	I-PER
story	O
has	O
been	O
revealed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
fake	O
.	O

What	O
do	O
the	O
new	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
videotape	O
and	O
audio	O
speeches	O
of	O
Bin	B-PER
Laden	I-PER
and	O
Ayman	B-PER
al	I-PER
-	I-PER
Zawahiri	I-PER
tell	O
us	O
about	O
the	O
hopes	O
of	O
the	O
remaining	O
top	O
leadership	O
of	O
the	O
organization	O
?	O

Because	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
and	O
Pakistan	B-ORG
have	O
managed	O
to	O
capture	O
or	O
kill	O
about	O
2	O
/	O
3s	O
of	O
the	O
top	O
25	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
commanders	O
,	O
the	O
middle	O
managers	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
close	O
contact	O
with	O
al	B-PER
-	I-PER
Zawahiri	I-PER
and	O
Bin	B-PER
Laden	I-PER
.	O

The	O
tape	O
was	O
a	O
way	O
to	O
signal	O
priorities	O
.	O

These	O
are	O
1	O
)	O
Assassinate	O
or	O
overthrow	O
Gen.	O
Pervez	B-PER
Musharraf	I-PER
,	O
the	O
Pakistani	B-LOC
military	O
"	O
president	O
"	O
who	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
coup	O
in	O
1999	O
and	O
has	O
thrown	O
in	O
his	O
lot	O
with	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
against	O
the	O
Taliban	B-ORG
and	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
.	O

Musharraf	B-PER
has	O
been	O
trying	O
to	O
purge	O
his	O
officer	O
corps	O
of	O
the	O
substantial	O
number	O
of	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
sympathizers	O
.	O

His	O
military	O
intelligence	O
has	O
captured	O
major	O
figures	O
like	O
Abu	B-PER
Zubayda	I-PER
and	O
Khalid	B-PER
Shaykh	I-PER
Muhammad	I-PER
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
nearly	O
500	O
other	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
operatives	O
,	O
over	O
400	O
of	O
whom	O
the	O
Pakistanis	B-LOC
have	O
turned	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
.	O

Musharraf	B-PER
held	O
elections	O
in	O
October	O
of	O
2002	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
center	O
-	O
right	O
parties	O
did	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
which	O
nearly	O
20	O
percent	O
of	O
parliament	O
seats	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
fundamentalist	O
religious	O
party	O
coalition	O
,	O
MMA	B-ORG
.	O

MMA	B-ORG
also	O
captured	O
the	O
Northwest	B-LOC
Frontier	I-LOC
Province	I-LOC
,	O
which	O
probably	O
shelters	O
Bin	B-PER
Laden	I-PER
and	O
al	B-PER
-	I-PER
Zawahiri	I-PER
,	O
and	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
joint	O
government	O
of	O
Baluchistan	B-LOC
Province	O
,	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
Afghanistan	B-LOC
border	O
.	O

If	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
can	O
kill	O
Musharraf	B-PER
or	O
instigate	O
a	O
military	O
coup	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
Islamist	O
junior	O
officers	O
,	O
they	O
can	O
hope	O
to	O
catapult	O
the	O
MMA	B-ORG
to	O
power	O
as	O
political	O
allies	O
and	O
hosts	O
.	O

They	O
would	O
thereby	O
gain	O
control	O
of	O
a	O
major	O
base	O
for	O
terrorist	O
operations	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
nuclear	O
power	O
.	O

All	O
this	O
is	O
highly	O
unlikely	O
,	O
as	O
with	O
most	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
crackpot	O
schemes	O
.	O

But	O
so	O
was	O
it	O
unlikely	O
that	O
a	O
small	O
group	O
of	O
Arab	B-LOC
mujahidin	O
would	O
virtually	O
take	O
over	O
Afghanistan	B-LOC
.	O

Response	O
:	O
The	O
US	B-ORG
must	O
do	O
whatever	O
it	O
can	O
to	O
strengthen	O
the	O
legitimacy	O
of	O
the	O
Pakistani	B-LOC
government	O
.	O

On	O
the	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
pressure	O
Musharraf	B-PER
to	O
take	O
off	O
his	O
uniform	O
and	O
run	O
for	O
president	O
in	O
a	O
fair	O
election	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
repeal	O
the	O
contentious	O
"	O
Legal	O
Framework	O
Order	O
"	O
that	O
essentially	O
perpetuates	O
his	O
dictatorship	O
.	O

On	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
restrictions	O
should	O
be	O
lifted	O
on	O
the	O
mainstream	O
Muslim	B-ORG
League	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
N	I-ORG
and	O
Pakistan	B-ORG
People	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Party	I-ORG
,	O
who	O
can	O
defeat	O
the	O
MMA	B-ORG
in	O
fair	O
elections	O
if	O
not	O
hogtied	O
by	O
the	O
secret	O
police	O
.	O

On	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
should	O
strong	O
-	O
arm	O
India	B-ORG
and	O
Pakistan	B-ORG
into	O
a	O
final	O
settlement	O
of	O
the	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
issue	O
.	O

Al	B-PER
-	I-PER
Zawahiri	I-PER
attempted	O
to	O
use	O
Musharraf	B-PER
's	I-PER
lack	O
of	O
progress	O
in	O
helping	O
the	O
Muslims	O
of	O
that	O
Indian	B-LOC
state	O
as	O
a	O
justification	O
for	O
his	O
overthrow	O
.	O

The	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
issue	O
generates	O
far	O
more	O
terrorism	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
the	O
threat	O
of	O
nuclear	O
war	O
,	O
than	O
Iraq	B-ORG
ever	O
did	O
.	O

2	O
)	O
Target	O
Israel	B-LOC
and	O
encourage	O
the	O
worst	O
elements	O
of	O
the	O
Palestinians	B-LOC
by	O
playing	O
on	O
the	O
iron	O
fist	O
policies	O
of	O
the	O
Sharon	B-PER
government	O
.	O

Response	O
:	O
The	O
US	B-ORG
has	O
succeeded	O
in	O
politically	O
isolating	O
Hamas	B-ORG
,	O
and	O
started	O
the	O
process	O
of	O
cutting	O
off	O
its	O
funding	O
.	O

This	O
terrorist	O
organization	O
can	O
now	O
only	O
pull	O
off	O
far	O
less	O
sophisticated	O
bombings	O
and	O
attacks	O
.	O

It	O
should	O
continue	O
to	O
be	O
defanged	O
.	O

But	O
Sharon	B-PER
's	I-PER
iron	O
fist	O
is	O
simply	O
not	O
working	O
as	O
a	O
means	O
of	O
establishing	O
general	O
peace	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bush	B-PER
administration	O
will	O
have	O
to	O
finally	O
apply	O
effective	O
pressure	O
on	O
Sharon	B-PER
to	O
stop	O
his	O
outrages	O
in	O
and	O
colonization	O
of	O
the	O
West	B-LOC
Bank	I-LOC
and	O
Gaza	B-LOC
.	O

Sharon	B-PER
's	I-PER
hard	O
line	O
has	O
worked	O
in	O
tandem	O
with	O
Hamas	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
terrorism	O
to	O
ratchet	O
up	O
tensions	O
further	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
which	O
spill	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
Muslim	O
world	O
and	O
serve	O
as	O
a	O
recruiting	O
tool	O
for	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
in	O
its	O
search	O
for	O
agents	O
willing	O
to	O
hit	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
.	O

Israel	B-ORG
owes	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
at	O
least	O
this	O
much	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
crisis	O
,	O
to	O
cease	O
militarily	O
unnecessary	O
provocations	O
and	O
establish	O
genuine	O
peace	O
.	O

3	O
)	O
Make	O
Iraq	B-LOC
another	O
Afghanistan	B-LOC
,	O
using	O
the	O
Republican	B-ORG
Right	O
's	O
own	O
tactics	O
against	O
them	O
.	O

Response	O
:	O
Iraq	B-LOC
is	O
actually	O
hostile	O
territory	O
for	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
,	O
and	O
without	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
sympathizers	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
succeed	O
there	O
.	O

By	O
moving	O
quickly	O
to	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
sovereignty	O
and	O
improvement	O
of	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
lives	O
,	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
may	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
Iraqis	B-LOC
on	O
its	O
side	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
turn	O
in	O
the	O
foreigners	O
.	O

Certainly	O
,	O
the	O
Shiites	O
already	O
hate	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
and	O
would	O
help	O
;	O
likewise	O
the	O
Kurds	B-LOC
.	O

The	O
problem	O
of	O
mollifying	O
the	O
Sunnis	O
,	O
though	O
,	O
has	O
to	O
be	O
solved	O
to	O
avoid	O
giving	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
an	O
entrée	O
.	O

The	O
Americans	B-LOC
have	O
to	O
put	O
away	O
their	O
free	O
-	O
market	O
fetishism	O
for	O
a	O
while	O
and	O
find	O
ways	O
of	O
creating	O
jobs	O
and	O
pumping	O
money	O
into	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
households	O
.	O

We	O
need	O
an	O
FDR	B-ORG
in	O
Iraq	B-LOC
,	O
not	O
a	O
Ronald	B-PER
Reagan	I-PER
.	O

Of	O
course	O
,	O
the	O
sooner	O
the	O
US	B-LOC
soldiers	O
can	O
be	O
withdrawn	O
in	O
favor	O
of	O
less	O
-	O
provocative	O
local	O
or	O
international	O
forces	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
.	O

Getting	O
the	O
Spanish	B-LOC
out	O
of	O
Iraq	B-LOC
is	O
n't	O
nearly	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
rallying	O
cry	O
for	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
in	O
the	O
Arab	B-LOC
world	O
as	O
getting	O
the	O
Americans	B-LOC
and	O
British	B-LOC
out	O
.	O

The	O
thing	O
to	O
keep	O
in	O
mind	O
is	O
that	O
Sunni	O
Arab	B-LOC
nationalists	O
and	O
Baathists	O
and	O
local	O
Sunni	O
radicals	O
are	O
likely	O
to	O
remain	O
far	O
more	O
dangerous	O
to	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
in	O
Iraq	B-LOC
than	O
al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Qaeda	I-ORG
infiltrators	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
dangerous	O
to	O
take	O
one	O
's	O
eyes	O
off	O
the	O
former	O
ball	O
.	O

George	B-PER
W.	I-PER
Bush	I-PER
alleged	O
Thursday	O
that	O
John	B-PER
Edwards	I-PER
lacks	O
the	O
experience	O
necessary	O
to	O
be	O
president	O
.	O

Let	O
's	O
just	O
remember	O
a	O
seminal	O
Bush	B-PER
moment	O
in	O
1999	O
:	O

'	O
Bush	B-PER
fails	O
reporter	O
's	O
pop	O
quiz	O
on	O
international	O
leaders	O

November	O
5	O
,	O
1999	O

Web	O
posted	O
at	O
:	O
3:29	O
p.m.	O
EST	O
(	O
2029	O
GMT	O
)	O

WASHINGTON	B-LOC
(	O
CNN	B-ORG
)	O
--	O

Texas	B-LOC
Gov.	O
George	B-PER
W.	I-PER
Bush	I-PER
is	O
enduring	O
sharp	O
criticism	O
for	O
being	O
unable	O
to	O
name	O
the	O
leaders	O
of	O
four	O
current	O
world	O
hot	O
spots	O
,	O
but	O
President	O
Bill	B-PER
Clinton	I-PER
says	O
Bush	B-PER
"	O
should	O
,	O
and	O
probably	O
will	O
,	O
pick	O
up	O
"	O
those	O
names	O
.	O

The	O
front	O
-	O
runner	O
for	O
the	O
2000	O
Republican	B-ORG
presidential	O
nomination	O
faltered	O
Thursday	O
in	O
an	O
international	O
affairs	O
pop	O
quiz	O
posed	O
by	O
Andy	B-PER
Hiller	I-PER
,	O
a	O
political	O
reporter	O
for	O
WHDH	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
TV	I-ORG
in	O
Boston	B-LOC
.	O

Bush	B-PER

Hiller	B-PER
asked	O
Bush	B-PER
to	O
name	O
the	O
leaders	O
of	O
Chechnya	B-LOC
,	O
Taiwan	B-LOC
,	O
India	B-LOC
and	O
Pakistan	B-LOC
.	O

Bush	B-PER
was	O
only	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
partial	O
response	O
to	O
the	O
query	O
on	O
the	O
leader	O
of	O
Taiwan	B-LOC
,	O
referring	O
to	O
Taiwanese	B-LOC
President	O
Lee	B-PER
Teng	I-PER
-	I-PER
hui	I-PER
simply	O
as	O
"	O
Lee	B-PER
.	O
"	O

He	O
could	O
not	O
name	O
the	O
others	O
.	O

"	O
Can	O
you	O
name	O
the	O
general	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
Pakistan	B-LOC
?	O
"	O

Hiller	B-PER
asked	O
,	O
inquiring	O
about	O
Gen.	O
Pervaiz	B-PER
Musharraf	I-PER
,	O
who	O
seized	O
control	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
October	O
12	O
.	O

"	O
Wait	O
,	O
wait	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
50	O
questions	O
?	O
"	O
asked	O
Bush	B-PER
.	O

Hiller	B-PER
replied	O
:	O
"	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
four	O
questions	O
of	O
four	O
leaders	O
in	O
four	O
hot	O
spots	O
.	O
"	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

Bush	B-PER
,	O
in	O
answering	O
the	O
question	O
about	O
the	O
leader	O
of	O
Pakistan	B-LOC
,	O
also	O
said	O
:	O
"	O
The	O
new	O
Pakistani	B-LOC
general	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
just	O
been	O
elected	O
--	O
not	O
elected	O
,	O
this	O
guy	O
took	O
over	O
office	O
.	O

It	O
appears	O
this	O
guy	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
bring	O
stability	O
to	O
the	O
country	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
's	O
good	O
news	O
for	O
the	O
subcontinent	O
.	O
"	O

Gore	B-PER
released	O
a	O
statement	O
Friday	O
taking	O
Bush	B-PER
to	O
task	O
for	O
his	O
comments	O
on	O
Pakistan	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
recent	O
coup	O
.	O

"	O
I	O
find	O
it	O
troubling	O
that	O
a	O
candidate	O
for	O
president	O
in	O
our	O
country	O
--	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
oldest	O
democracy	O
--	O
would	O
characterize	O
the	O
military	O
takeover	O
as	O
"	O
good	O
news	O
,	O
"	O
Gore	B-PER
said	O
.	O

"	O
Further	O
,	O
I	O
find	O
it	O
even	O
more	O
disturbing	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
these	O
comments	O
about	O
a	O
nation	O
that	O
just	O
last	O
year	O
tested	O
nuclear	O
weapons	O
--	O
shortly	O
after	O
voicing	O
his	O
public	O
opposition	O
to	O
the	O
Comprehensive	B-MISC
Test	I-MISC
Ban	I-MISC
Treaty	I-MISC
.	O

A	O
spokesman	O
for	O
President	O
Clinton	B-PER
also	O
criticized	O
Bush	B-PER
's	I-PER
comments	O
.	O

"	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
dangerous	O
for	O
this	O
country	O
to	O
condone	O
the	O
overthrow	O
of	O
democratically	O
elected	O
governments	O
,	O
"	O
said	O
David	B-PER
Leavy	I-PER
,	O
spokesman	O
for	O
the	O
National	B-ORG
Security	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
.	O

Not	O
only	O
did	O
Bush	B-PER
not	O
know	O
who	O
General	O
Pervez	B-PER
Musharraf	I-PER
was	O
,	O
he	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
confused	O
coup	O
-	O
making	O
with	O
"	O
taking	O
office	O
,	O
"	O
and	O
moreover	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
suggest	O
that	O
the	O
overthrow	O
of	O
an	O
elected	O
prime	O
minister	O
and	O
the	O
installation	O
in	O
power	O
of	O
the	O
Pakistan	B-LOC
military	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
strongest	O
supporter	O
of	O
the	O
Taliban	B-ORG
,	O
would	O
bring	O
"	O
stability	O
!	O
"	O

Musharraf	B-PER
made	O
his	O
coup	O
in	O
part	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
military	O
's	O
anger	O
over	O
Prime	O
Minister	O
Nawaz	B-PER
Sharif	I-PER
's	I-PER
willingness	O
to	O
back	O
down	O
from	O
confronting	O
India	B-ORG
over	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
explicitly	O
came	O
to	O
power	O
as	O
a	O
warmonger	O
.	O

I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
ominous	O
I	O
found	O
Bush	B-PER
's	I-PER
performance	O
in	O
that	O
interview	O
.	O

I	O
still	O
remember	O
him	O
stuttering	O
about	O
"	O
the	O
General	O
,	O
"	O
unable	O
to	O
remember	O
Musharraf	B-PER
's	I-PER
name	O
.	O

He	O
obviously	O
had	O
no	O
idea	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
about	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
demonstrated	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
ill	O
-	O
fated	O
instincts	O
.	O

He	O
obviously	O
liked	O
authoritarian	O
rule	O
better	O
than	O
democracy	O
,	O
equating	O
dictatorship	O
with	O
"	O
stability	O
.	O
"	O

And	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
needed	O
to	O
know	O
anything	O
about	O
South	B-LOC
Asia	I-LOC
,	O
with	O
its	O
nuclear	O
giants	O
and	O
radical	O
religious	O
politics	O
--	O
the	O
latter	O
a	O
dire	O
security	O
threat	O
to	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
.	O

He	O
could	O
n't	O
tell	O
when	O
things	O
were	O
becoming	O
more	O
unstable	O
as	O
opposed	O
to	O
less	O
.	O

Musharraf	B-PER
went	O
on	O
to	O
play	O
nuclear	O
brinkmanship	O
with	O
India	B-LOC
in	O
2002	O
,	O
risking	O
war	O
twice	O
that	O
year	O
.	O

Although	O
Musharraf	B-PER
did	O
turn	O
against	O
the	O
Taliban	B-ORG
after	O
September	O
11	O
,	O
under	O
extreme	O
duress	O
from	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
,	O
elements	O
of	O
his	O
military	O
continued	O
to	O
support	O
radical	O
Islamism	O
and	O
have	O
recently	O
been	O
implicated	O
in	O
assassination	O
attempts	O
on	O
Musharraf	B-PER
himself	O
.	O

This	O
was	O
the	O
body	O
that	O
Bush	B-PER
proclaimed	O
was	O
bringing	O
"	O
stability	O
"	O
to	O
the	O
region	O
in	O
fall	O
of	O
1999	O
.	O

So	O
,	O
one	O
answer	O
to	O
Bush	B-PER
's	I-PER
charge	O
about	O
Edwards	B-PER
is	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
any	O
merit	O
,	O
Bush	B-PER
should	O
have	O
declined	O
to	O
run	O
himself	O
.	O

Another	O
answer	O
is	O
that	O
Edwards	B-PER
certainly	O
knows	O
far	O
more	O
about	O
foreign	O
affairs	O
now	O
than	O
Bush	B-PER
did	O
then	O
.	O

Indeed	O
,	O
given	O
how	O
Bush	B-PER
has	O
rampaged	O
around	O
the	O
world	O
alienating	O
allies	O
and	O
ignoring	O
vital	O
conflicts	O
with	O
the	O
potential	O
to	O
blow	O
back	O
on	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
,	O
one	O
might	O
well	O
argue	O
that	O
Edwards	B-PER
knows	O
more	O
now	O
than	O
Bush	B-PER
does	O
.	O

This	O
is	O
what	O
Edwards	B-PER
'	O
campaign	O
literature	O
said	O
about	O
his	O
positions	O
:	O
"	O
Edwards	B-PER
believes	O
that	O
the	O
U.S.	B-ORG
must	O
be	O
an	O
active	O
leader	O
to	O
help	O
resolve	O
conflicts	O
,	O
from	O
reducing	O
tensions	O
between	O
India	B-ORG
and	O
Pakistan	B-ORG
to	O
the	O
peace	O
process	O
in	O
Northern	B-LOC
Ireland	I-LOC
.	O

I	O
do	O
n't	O
see	O
Bush	B-PER
doing	O
any	O
of	O
this	O
.	O

From	O
Friday	O
's	O
Daily	B-ORG
Star	I-ORG

By	O
Juan	B-PER
Cole	I-PER

Friday	O
,	O
June	O
04	O
,	O
2004	O

As	O
the	O
American	B-LOC
public	O
gradually	O
wearies	O
of	O
the	O
Iraq	B-LOC
crisis	O
,	O
some	O
have	O
begun	O
worrying	O
that	O
the	O
war	O
could	O
blow	O
back	O
on	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
by	O
creating	O
the	O
conditions	O
for	O
anti-American	B-LOC
terrorism	O
.	O

Israel	B-ORG
,	O
however	O
,	O
is	O
much	O
closer	O
to	O
Iraq	B-LOC
and	O
is	O
likely	O
to	O
suffer	O
from	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
instability	O
much	O
more	O
acutely	O
than	O
will	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
.	O

Ironically	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
strongest	O
proponents	O
of	O
war	O
in	O
Iraq	B-LOC
were	O
Israeli	B-LOC
Prime	O
Minister	O
Ariel	B-PER
Sharon	I-PER
and	O
his	O
neoconservative	O
supporters	O
in	O
the	O
US	B-LOC
.	O

Have	O
they	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
actually	O
weakened	O
Israeli	B-LOC
security	O
?	O

The	O
biggest	O
threat	O
Israel	B-ORG
faces	O
is	O
not	O
from	O
conventional	O
armies	O
but	O
from	O
the	O
asymmetrical	O
tactics	O
of	O
Palestinian	B-LOC
national	O
liberation	O
movements	O
.	O

The	O
derailing	O
of	O
the	O
Oslo	B-LOC
peace	O
process	O
by	O
the	O
hard	O
-	O
line	O
policies	O
of	O
Sharon	B-PER
and	O
the	O
Palestinian	B-LOC
intifada	O
has	O
encouraged	O
suicide	O
bombings	O
.	O

This	O
,	O
in	O
turn	O
,	O
has	O
discouraged	O
international	O
investment	O
in	O
Israel	B-ORG
and	O
has	O
made	O
it	O
less	O
likely	O
that	O
immigrants	O
to	O
the	O
country	O
will	O
actually	O
remain	O
there	O
.	O

Although	O
Israel	B-ORG
withdrew	O
from	O
Lebanese	B-LOC
territory	O
in	O
May	O
2000	O
,	O
the	O
radical	O
Lebanese	B-LOC
Shiite	O
party	O
,	O
Hizbullah	B-ORG
,	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
mollified	O
.	O

It	O
is	O
estimated	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
5,000	O
armed	O
fighters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
pursued	O
attacks	O
against	O
Israeli	B-LOC
forces	O
to	O
compel	O
them	O
to	O
withdraw	O
from	O
the	O
Shebaa	B-LOC
Farms	I-LOC
,	O
a	O
sliver	O
of	O
Syrian	B-LOC
territory	O
that	O
Israel	B-ORG
annexed	O
after	O
the	O
1967	O
war	O
.	O

Any	O
thorough	O
assessment	O
of	O
the	O
impact	O
of	O
the	O
Iraq	B-MISC
war	I-MISC
and	O
its	O
aftermath	O
on	O
Israel	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
security	O
environment	O
must	O
,	O
therefore	O
,	O
closely	O
examine	O
its	O
likely	O
effect	O
on	O
the	O
conduct	O
of	O
asymmetrical	O
warfare	O
.	O

Although	O
it	O
is	O
often	O
alleged	O
(	O
without	O
much	O
evidence	O
)	O
that	O
Saddam	B-PER
Hussein	I-PER
gave	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
families	O
of	O
Palestinian	B-LOC
suicide	O
bombers	O
and	O
so	O
encouraged	O
asymmetrical	O
warfare	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
clear	O
that	O
he	O
actually	O
posed	O
a	O
danger	O
to	O
Israel	B-ORG
.	O

The	O
Palestinians	B-LOC
who	O
have	O
been	O
willing	O
to	O
kill	O
themselves	O
to	O
end	O
the	O
Israeli	B-LOC
occupation	O
of	O
the	O
Gaza	B-LOC
Strip	I-LOC
and	O
the	O
West	B-LOC
Bank	I-LOC
were	O
not	O
driven	O
by	O
economic	O
considerations	O
.	O

Saddam	B-PER
never	O
did	O
anything	O
practical	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
Palestinians	B-LOC
.	O

At	O
some	O
points	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
late	O
1980s	O
,	O
he	O
reportedly	O
made	O
behind	O
-	O
the	O
-	O
scenes	O
overtures	O
to	O
the	O
Israelis	B-LOC
to	O
arrive	O
at	O
some	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
deal	O
.	O

He	O
did	O
not	O
allow	O
Palestinian	B-LOC
radicals	O
to	O
launch	O
operations	O
against	O
Israel	B-ORG
from	O
Iraq	B-LOC
.	O

By	O
the	O
late	O
1990s	O
,	O
Iraq	B-ORG
had	O
no	O
nuclear	O
or	O
biological	O
weapons	O
program	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
destroyed	O
its	O
chemical	O
weapons	O
stockpiles	O
.	O

Its	O
ramshackle	O
army	O
had	O
virtually	O
collapsed	O
before	O
the	O
American	B-LOC
invasion	O
in	O
2003	O
.	O

If	O
it	O
is	O
hard	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
Baathist	O
Iraq	I-ORG
posed	O
any	O
real	O
threat	O
to	O
Israel	B-ORG
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
difficult	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
menace	O
in	O
the	O
current	O
instability	O
.	O

The	O
bungling	O
of	O
post-war	O
Iraq	B-LOC
by	O
the	O
Bush	B-PER
administration	O
created	O
a	O
weak	O
and	O
failed	O
state	O
.	O

Armed	O
militias	O
,	O
many	O
staffed	O
by	O
former	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
military	O
men	O
with	O
substantial	O
training	O
and	O
experience	O
,	O
have	O
proliferated	O
.	O

The	O
US	B-ORG
chose	O
to	O
ally	O
itself	O
with	O
such	O
groups	O
as	O
the	O
Supreme	B-ORG
Council	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Islamic	I-ORG
Revolution	I-ORG
in	O
Iraq	B-LOC
,	O
whose	O
15,000	O
-	O
strong	O
Badr	B-ORG
Corps	I-ORG
paramilitary	O
was	O
trained	O
by	O
the	O
Iranian	B-ORG
Revolutionary	I-ORG
Guards	I-ORG
.	O

Anti-Israeli	B-LOC
and	O
pro-Palestinian	B-LOC
feeling	O
is	O
strong	O
among	O
several	O
major	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
ideological	O
groups	O
and	O
currents	O
.	O

The	O
more	O
radical	O
Shiites	O
,	O
who	O
generally	O
follow	O
the	O
theocratic	O
notions	O
of	O
Iran	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
Ayatollah	B-PER
Ruhollah	I-PER
Khomeini	I-PER
,	O
routinely	O
chant	O
and	O
demonstrate	O
against	O
Israel	B-ORG
.	O

They	O
vehemently	O
protested	O
the	O
Israeli	B-LOC
assassination	O
of	O
Sheikh	O
Ahmed	B-PER
Yassin	I-PER
,	O
the	O
leader	O
of	O
Hamas	B-ORG
,	O
last	O
March	O
.	O

Worse	O
for	O
Israel	B-ORG
,	O
the	O
assassination	O
drew	O
a	O
denunciation	O
even	O
from	O
the	O
moderate	O
and	O
cautious	O
Grand	O
Ayatollah	O
Ali	B-PER
Sistani	I-PER
,	O
who	O
wields	O
enormous	O
moral	O
authority	O
over	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
Shiites	O
.	O

These	O
Shiite	O
movements	O
had	O
been	O
suppressed	O
by	O
Saddam	B-PER
Hussein	I-PER
's	I-PER
regime	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
now	O
organized	O
and	O
armed	O
themselves	O
.	O

They	O
have	O
also	O
reestablished	O
their	O
historical	O
links	O
with	O
Lebanese	B-LOC
and	O
Iranian	B-LOC
Shiites	O
.	O

It	O
is	O
inevitable	O
that	O
most	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
Shiites	O
will	O
side	O
with	O
their	O
Hizbullah	B-ORG
coreligionists	O
against	O
Israel	B-ORG
,	O
and	O
it	O
seems	O
likely	O
that	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
Shiites	O
will	O
get	O
rich	O
enough	O
from	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
petroleum	O
sales	O
in	O
the	O
future	O
that	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
position	O
to	O
bankroll	O
Lebanese	B-LOC
Shiite	O
radicals	O
.	O

Sunni	O
Arab	B-LOC
fundamentalists	O
deeply	O
sympathize	O
with	O
the	O
Palestinians	B-LOC
and	O
with	O
Hamas	B-ORG
,	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Iraq	B-LOC
have	O
deep	O
historical	O
inks	O
with	O
fundamentalists	O
in	O
Jordan	B-LOC
and	O
Palestine	B-LOC
.	O

Iraqi	B-LOC
cities	O
such	O
as	O
Fallujah	B-LOC
and	O
Ramadi	B-LOC
were	O
on	O
the	O
truck	O
route	O
from	O
Amman	B-LOC
to	O
Baghdad	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
so	O
came	O
under	O
the	O
influence	O
of	O
the	O
Salafi	O
movement	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
popular	O
in	O
Jordan	B-LOC
.	O

Secular	O
Arab	B-LOC
nationalist	O
groups	O
also	O
universally	O
sympathize	O
with	O
the	O
Palestinians	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
post-Saddam	B-PER
Iraq	B-LOC
are	O
no	O
exception	O
.	O

Whereas	O
Saddam	B-PER
Hussein	I-PER
's	I-PER
dictatorship	O
ensured	O
that	O
such	O
populist	O
currents	O
were	O
kept	O
firmly	O
under	O
control	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
free	O
to	O
organize	O
.	O

An	O
Iraq	B-LOC
in	O
which	O
armed	O
fundamentalist	O
and	O
nationalist	O
militias	O
proliferate	O
is	O
inevitably	O
a	O
security	O
worry	O
for	O
Israel	B-ORG
.	O

If	O
even	O
a	O
modicum	O
of	O
normality	O
and	O
security	O
can	O
be	O
returned	O
to	O
Iraq	B-LOC
,	O
its	O
citizens	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
benefit	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
's	O
petroleum	O
reserves	O
.	O

That	O
private	O
wealth	O
can	O
easily	O
be	O
funneled	O
into	O
aid	O
for	O
the	O
Palestinians	B-LOC
and	O
for	O
Lebanese	B-LOC
Shiites	O
.	O

Israel	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
security	O
interests	O
are	O
best	O
served	O
by	O
peace	O
with	O
its	O
neighbors	O
,	O
which	O
can	O
only	O
be	O
achieved	O
by	O
trading	O
land	O
for	O
peace	O
with	O
the	O
Palestinians	B-LOC
.	O

Ariel	B-PER
Sharon	I-PER
's	I-PER
aggressive	O
near	O
annexation	O
of	O
almost	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
occupied	O
West	B-LOC
Bank	I-LOC
and	O
his	O
indefinite	O
postponement	O
of	O
any	O
Palestinian	B-LOC
state	O
have	O
created	O
unprecedented	O
rage	O
and	O
violence	O
.	O

The	O
anger	O
has	O
spread	O
throughout	O
the	O
Muslim	O
world	O
,	O
including	O
Iraq	B-LOC
.	O

The	O
promotion	O
by	O
the	O
pro-Zionist	B-LOC
right	O
of	O
twin	O
occupations	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
West	B-LOC
Bank	I-LOC
and	O
in	O
Iraq	B-LOC
-	O
has	O
profoundly	O
weakened	O
,	O
not	O
strengthened	O
,	O
Israeli	B-LOC
security	O
.	O

Juan	B-PER
Cole	I-PER
(	O
www.juancole.com	B-MISC
)	O
is	O
a	O
professor	O
of	O
modern	O
Middle	B-LOC
East	I-LOC
history	O
at	O
the	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Michigan	I-ORG
and	O
author	O
of	O
"	O
Sacred	B-MISC
Space	I-MISC
and	I-MISC
Holy	I-MISC
War	I-MISC
"	O
(	O
I.B.	B-ORG
Tauris	I-ORG
,	O
2002	O
)	O
.	O

THE	O
DAILY	B-ORG
STAR	I-ORG
publishes	O
this	O
commentary	O
in	O
agreement	O
with	O
Agence	B-ORG
Global	I-ORG

Tamils	B-LOC
feel	O
that	O
the	O
proposed	O
defense	O
agreement	O
between	O
India	B-ORG
and	O
Sri	B-ORG
Lanka	I-ORG
would	O
encourage	O
Sinhala	B-LOC
rulers	O
to	O
prepare	O
for	O
another	O
war	O
abandoning	O
the	O
current	O
peace	O
process	O

But	O
there	O
are	O
strong	O
hints	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
that	O
a	O
new	O
Indo	B-LOC
-	I-LOC
Sri	I-LOC
Lanka	I-LOC
defense	O
deal	O
could	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
making	O
.	O

And	O
this	O
has	O
already	O
drawn	O
protests	O
from	O
the	O
Tamil	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
(	O
TNA	B-ORG
)	O
which	O
was	O
backed	O
by	O
the	O
LTTE	B-ORG
in	O
the	O
April	O
general	O
elections	O
held	O
in	O
Sri	B-LOC
Lanka	I-LOC
.	O

Apart	O
from	O
the	O
1,200	O
Indian	B-LOC
lives	O
lost	O
in	O
1987	O
,	O
the	O
Indian	B-LOC
peacekeeping	O
force	O
was	O
immensely	O
unpopular	O
not	O
only	O
in	O
Tamil	B-LOC
Nadu	I-LOC
and	O
the	O
Jaffna	B-LOC
peninsula	I-LOC
but	O
also	O
among	O
the	O
Sinhalese	B-LOC
majority	O
who	O
considered	O
it	O
a	O
violation	O
of	O
their	O
country	O
's	O
sovereignty	O
.	O

India	B-ORG
defensive	O
over	O
Sri	B-LOC
Lanka	I-LOC

By	O
Ranjit	B-PER
Devraj	I-PER

NEW	B-LOC
DELHI	I-LOC
-	O

While	O
India	B-ORG
is	O
ready	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
a	O
"	O
defense	O
cooperation	O
agreement	O
"	O
with	O
Sri	B-ORG
Lanka	I-ORG
,	O
it	O
is	O
wary	O
of	O
being	O
drawn	O
into	O
any	O
military	O
involvement	O
in	O
the	O
island	O
nation	O
's	O
two	O
decades	O
-	O
old	O
civil	O
war	O
that	O
has	O
seen	O
violent	O
strife	O
between	O
ethnic	O
Tamils	B-LOC
and	O
the	O
Sinhalese	B-LOC
majority	O
-	O
leaving	O
over	O
60,000	O
dead	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
.	O

And	O
that	O
explains	O
the	O
delay	O
in	O
the	O
signing	O
of	O
a	O
formal	O
defense	O
agreement	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
heart	O
of	O
Sri	B-LOC
Lankan	I-LOC
President	O
Chandrika	B-PER
Kumaratunga	I-PER
's	I-PER
four	O
-	O
day	O
visit	O
to	O
India	B-LOC
recently	O
.	O

According	O
to	O
Professor	O
S	B-PER
D	I-PER
Muni	I-PER
,	O
South	B-LOC
Asia	I-LOC
expert	O
at	O
the	O
Jawaharal	B-ORG
Nehru	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
two	O
-	O
year	O
peace	O
talks	O
between	O
Colombo	B-ORG
and	O
the	O
Liberation	B-ORG
Tigers	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Tamil	I-ORG
Eelam	I-ORG
(	O
LTTE	B-ORG
)	O
are	O
stalemated	O
.	O

For	O
that	O
reason	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Kumaratunga	B-PER
's	I-PER
government	O
was	O
keen	O
to	O
beef	O
up	O
military	O
preparedness	O
with	O
Indian	B-LOC
support	O
.	O

"	O
The	O
Sri	B-LOC
Lankan	I-LOC
government	O
does	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
initiate	O
a	O
conflict	O
but	O
would	O
be	O
interested	O
in	O
deterring	O
the	O
LTTE	B-ORG
from	O
starting	O
one	O
.	O

And	O
the	O
Tigers	B-ORG
look	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
on	O
the	O
brink	O
of	O
launching	O
another	O
offensive	O
,	O
"	O
Muni	B-PER
told	O
IPS	B-ORG
.	O

Colombo	B-ORG
held	O
six	O
rounds	O
of	O
talks	O
with	O
the	O
Tigers	B-ORG
between	O
September	O
2002	O
and	O
March	O
2003	O
.	O

But	O
last	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
rebels	O
abruptly	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
negotiations	O
demanding	O
recognition	O
,	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
to	O
self	O
-	O
rule	O
before	O
proceeding	O
any	O
further	O
.	O

Kumaratunga	B-PER
's	I-PER
India	B-LOC
tour	O
preceded	O
a	O
three	O
-	O
day	O
visit	O
to	O
Sri	B-LOC
Lanka	I-LOC
by	O
Norwegian	B-LOC
Foreign	O
Minister	O
Jan	B-PER
Petersen	I-PER
in	O
a	O
new	O
bid	O
to	O
revive	O
the	O
peace	O
talks	O
that	O
were	O
supposed	O
to	O
follow	O
a	O
ceasefire	O
that	O
Oslo	B-ORG
successfully	O
brokered	O
in	O
February	O
2002	O
.	O

Petersen	B-PER
held	O
discussions	O
with	O
both	O
Kumaratunga	B-PER
and	O
the	O
reclusive	O
LTTE	B-ORG
leader	O
Velupillai	B-PER
Prabhakaran	I-PER
in	O
the	O
rebel	O
stronghold	O
of	O
Kilinochchi	B-LOC
without	O
success	O
,	O
and	O
chief	O
Tamil	B-LOC
rebel	O
negotiator	O
Anton	B-PER
Balasingham	I-PER
and	O
Norwegian	B-LOC
envoy	O
Erik	B-PER
Solheim	I-PER
held	O
closed	O
-	O
door	O
talks	O
at	O
the	O
international	O
airport	O
late	O
Saturday	O
in	O
an	O
effort	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
salvage	O
effort	O
on	O
track	O
,	O
diplomatic	O
sources	O
said	O
.	O

But	O
they	O
,	O
too	O
,	O
failed	O
.	O

Colombo	B-ORG
,	O
too	O
,	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
an	O
intractable	O
position	O
.	O

According	O
to	O
former	O
Indian	B-LOC
army	O
general	O
A	B-PER
S	I-PER
Kalkat	I-PER
,	O
the	O
difficulty	O
for	O
Kumaratunga	B-PER
's	I-PER
government	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
that	O
the	O
LTTE	B-ORG
had	O
become	O
a	O
de	O
jure	O
power	O
in	O
the	O
north	O
and	O
east	O
of	O
the	O
island	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
every	O
aspect	O
of	O
civil	O
administration	O
in	O
the	O
areas	O
within	O
its	O
control	O
.	O

A	O
veteran	O
of	O
India	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
military	O
intervention	O
in	O
the	O
Jaffna	B-LOC
peninsula	I-LOC
to	O
help	O
implement	O
the	O
1987	O
Indo	B-MISC
-	B-MISC
Sri	I-MISC
Lanka	I-MISC
Peace	I-MISC
Accord	I-MISC
-	O
which	O
ambitiously	O
provided	O
for	O
the	O
disarming	O
of	O
the	O
formidable	O
LTTE	B-ORG
-	O
Kalkat	B-PER
said	O
the	O
new	O
defense	O
deal	O
would	O
essentially	O
be	O
a	O
reiteration	O
of	O
the	O
older	O
one	O
minus	O
its	O
military	O
commitment	O
.	O

Kalkat	B-PER
,	O
who	O
currently	O
chairs	O
the	O
independent	O
US	B-LOC
-	I-LOC
based	I-LOC
International	B-ORG
Council	I-ORG
on	I-ORG
Conflict	I-ORG
Resolution	I-ORG
,	O
said	O
despite	O
the	O
failure	O
of	O
the	O
Indian	B-LOC
army	O
to	O
disarm	O
or	O
even	O
subdue	O
the	O
Tigers	B-ORG
,	O
India	B-ORG
remained	O
the	O
only	O
power	O
capable	O
of	O
influencing	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
current	O
peace	O
talks	O
.	O

"	O
The	O
Norwegians	B-LOC
mean	O
well	O
but	O
their	O
role	O
is	O
limited	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
honest	O
broker	O
and	O
the	O
LTTE	B-ORG
is	O
keenly	O
aware	O
that	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
power	O
[	O
unlike	O
India	B-ORG
]	O
to	O
underwrite	O
any	O
arrangement	O
,	O
"	O
Kalkat	B-PER
told	O
IPS	B-ORG
in	O
an	O
interview	O
.	O

In	O
1987	O
,	O
the	O
Tamil	B-ORG
Tigers	I-ORG
reluctantly	O
accepted	O
the	O
peace	O
accord	O
under	O
Indian	B-LOC
pressure	O
.	O

Under	O
the	O
accord	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
northeastern	O
provincial	O
council	O
was	O
formed	O
and	O
the	O
Indian	B-LOC
army	O
was	O
deployed	O
as	O
peacekeepers	O
in	O
the	O
north	O
and	O
east	O
.	O

However	O
,	O
differences	O
between	O
India	B-ORG
and	O
LTTE	B-ORG
soon	O
surfaced	O
and	O
led	O
to	O
clashes	O
between	O
Tiger	B-ORG
guerrillas	O
and	O
the	O
Indian	B-LOC
peace	O
keeping	O
force	O
.	O

About	O
1,200	O
Indian	B-LOC
soldiers	O
were	O
killed	O
during	O
this	O
phase	O
of	O
the	O
conflict	O
.	O

India	B-ORG
had	O
to	O
pull	O
back	O
its	O
forces	O
from	O
Sri	B-LOC
Lanka	I-LOC
in	O
1989	O
following	O
the	O
election	O
of	O
Ranasinghe	B-PER
Premadasa	I-PER
,	O
a	O
strong	O
critic	O
of	O
Indian	B-LOC
mediation	O
.	O

Last	O
June	O
,	O
an	O
international	O
initiative	O
led	O
by	O
Japan	B-ORG
to	O
persuade	O
the	O
LTTE	B-ORG
to	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
negotiating	O
table	O
failed	O
despite	O
an	O
aid	O
package	O
offer	O
of	O
US$	B-MISC
4.5	O
billion	O
.	O

Japan	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
special	O
envoy	O
,	O
Yasushi	B-PER
Akashi	I-PER
,	O
who	O
called	O
for	O
tangible	O
progress	O
in	O
the	O
peace	O
process	O
before	O
the	O
money	O
would	O
be	O
released	O
,	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
visits	O
to	O
Colombo	B-LOC
and	O
Kilinochchi	B-LOC
in	O
early	O
November	O
a	O
frustrated	O
man	O
.	O

He	O
complained	O
about	O
the	O
"	O
visible	O
lack	O
of	O
progress	O
"	O
and	O
reaching	O
an	O
impasse	O
in	O
talks	O
with	O
both	O
sides	O
.	O

The	O
Tigers	B-ORG
'	O
chief	O
ideologue	O
,	O
Balasingham	B-PER
,	O
sniffed	O
at	O
the	O
proposal	O
saying	O
that	O
"	O
a	O
solution	O
to	O
the	O
ethnic	O
conflict	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
predetermined	O
by	O
the	O
resolutions	O
or	O
declarations	O
of	O
donor	O
conferences	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
to	O
be	O
negotiated	O
by	O
the	O
parties	O
in	O
conflict	O
without	O
the	O
constraints	O
of	O
external	O
forces	O
.	O
"	O

But	O
there	O
are	O
strong	O
hints	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
that	O
a	O
new	O
Indo	B-LOC
-	I-LOC
Sri	I-LOC
Lanka	I-LOC
defense	O
deal	O
could	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
making	O
.	O

And	O
this	O
has	O
already	O
drawn	O
protests	O
from	O
the	O
Tamil	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
(	O
TNA	B-ORG
)	O
which	O
was	O
backed	O
by	O
the	O
LTTE	B-ORG
in	O
the	O
April	O
general	O
elections	O
held	O
in	O
Sri	B-LOC
Lanka	I-LOC
.	O

"	O
Tamils	B-LOC
feel	O
that	O
the	O
proposed	O
defense	O
agreement	O
between	O
India	B-ORG
and	O
Sri	B-ORG
Lanka	I-ORG
would	O
encourage	O
Sinhala	B-LOC
rulers	O
to	O
prepare	O
for	O
another	O
war	O
abandoning	O
the	O
current	O
peace	O
process	O
,	O
"	O
TNA	B-ORG
member	O
of	O
parliament	O
P	B-PER
Sithamparanathan	I-PER
was	O
quoted	O
as	O
saying	O
in	O
a	O
statement	O
.	O

She	O
added	O
that	O
recent	O
visits	O
to	O
the	O
island	O
by	O
India	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
top	O
military	O
brass	O
including	O
army	O
chief	O
General	O
Nirmal	B-PER
Chander	I-PER
Vij	I-PER
have	O
"	O
caused	O
apprehension	O
among	O
Tamils	B-LOC
that	O
preparations	O
are	O
under	O
way	O
for	O
another	O
war	O
in	O
the	O
island	O
"	O
.	O

But	O
Kalkat	B-PER
pointed	O
out	O
that	O
India	B-ORG
would	O
be	O
ill	O
-	O
advised	O
to	O
be	O
involved	O
again	O
,	O
militarily	O
,	O
with	O
Sri	B-ORG
Lanka	I-ORG
if	O
only	O
because	O
it	O
still	O
had	O
to	O
consider	O
the	O
sentiments	O
of	O
45	O
million	O
ethnic	O
Tamils	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
Indian	B-LOC
state	O
of	O
Tamil	B-LOC
Nadu	I-LOC
-	O
separated	O
from	O
Sri	B-LOC
Lanka	I-LOC
's	I-LOC
Jaffna	B-LOC
peninsula	I-LOC
by	O
the	O
narrow	O
Palk	B-LOC
Straits	I-LOC
.	O

Apart	O
from	O
the	O
1,200	O
Indian	B-LOC
lives	O
lost	O
in	O
1987	O
,	O
the	O
Indian	B-LOC
peacekeeping	O
force	O
was	O
immensely	O
unpopular	O
not	O
only	O
in	O
Tamil	B-LOC
Nadu	I-LOC
and	O
the	O
Jaffna	B-LOC
peninsula	I-LOC
but	O
also	O
among	O
the	O
Sinhalese	B-LOC
majority	O
who	O
considered	O
it	O
a	O
violation	O
of	O
their	O
country	O
's	O
sovereignty	O
.	O

The	O
best	O
option	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
present	O
difficult	O
circumstances	O
is	O
for	O
Colombo	B-ORG
to	O
do	O
its	O
own	O
dirty	O
work	O
,	O
although	O
New	B-ORG
Delhi	I-ORG
can	O
always	O
be	O
counted	O
on	O
to	O
render	O
good	O
neighborly	O
help	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
shared	O
belief	O
that	O
religion	O
,	O
ethnicity	O
and	O
language	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
basis	O
for	O
secession	O
.	O

In	O
any	O
case	O
,	O
Kalkat	B-PER
puts	O
it	O
succinctly	O
:	O
"	O
There	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
military	O
option	O
to	O
what	O
is	O
a	O
political	O
situation	O
.	O
"	O

Asia	B-ORG
Times	I-ORG
Online	I-ORG
16/11/2004	O

Unreported	O
by	O
the	O
international	O
media	O
,	O
the	O
Valley	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Kashmir	I-LOC
has	O
seen	O
an	O
ethnic	O
and	O
cultural	O
genocide	O
that	O
has	O
resulted	O
in	O
the	O
fleeing	O
from	O
the	O
valley	O
of	O
almost	O
all	O
the	O
Hindu	O
families	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
living	O
there	O
since	O
human	O
habitation	O
was	O
first	O
recorded	O
.	O

Over	O
nine	O
dozen	O
temples	O
that	O
had	O
served	O
the	O
Hindu	O
population	O
have	O
been	O
destroyed	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
used	O
as	O
building	O
material	O
and	O
others	O
used	O
as	O
urinals	O
.	O

Thus	O
far	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
many	O
"	O
human	O
rights	O
"	O
busybodies	O
across	O
the	O
world	O
have	O
bothered	O
to	O
even	O
notice	O
such	O
a	O
development	O
.	O

Musharraf	B-PER
calls	O
the	O
bluff	O

M.D.	B-PER
Nalapat	I-PER

While	O
most	O
U.S.	B-LOC
secretaries	O
of	O
state	O
--	O
save	O
perhaps	O
Dean	B-PER
Rusk	I-PER
--	O
have	O
gobbled	O
up	O
credit	O
for	O
outcomes	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
,	O
few	O
have	O
been	O
as	O
brazen	O
as	O
Colin	B-PER
Powell	I-PER
.	O

Two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
Pakistani	B-LOC
President	O
Pervez	B-PER
Musharraf	I-PER
was	O
surprised	O
when	O
the	O
leader	O
of	O
the	O
main	O
Islamist	O
alliance	O
--	O
Maulana	B-PER
Fazlur	I-PER
Rahman	I-PER
--	O
visited	O
India	B-LOC
and	O
issued	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
highly	O
conciliatory	O
statements	O
.	O

As	O
Pakistan	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
president	O
had	O
been	O
telling	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
he	O
was	O
"	O
forced	O
"	O
into	O
taking	O
a	O
hawkish	O
line	O
on	O
India	B-ORG
precisely	O
by	O
the	O
likes	O
of	O
Rahman	B-PER
,	O
this	O
was	O
an	O
embarrassment	O
.	O

The	O
reality	O
is	O
that	O
India	B-ORG
is	O
no	O
longer	O
the	O
enemy	O
of	O
choice	O
for	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
Pakistan	B-LOC
.	O

That	O
distinction	O
has	O
now	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
.	O

Realists	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
even	O
includes	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
U.S.	B-LOC
Democratic	O
foreign	O
policy	O
establishment	O
such	O
as	O
Strobe	B-PER
Talbott	I-PER
,	O
who	O
have	O
long	O
sought	O
to	O
divest	O
India	B-ORG
of	O
its	O
defensive	O
capability	O
against	O
another	O
nuclear	O
power	O
in	O
Asia	B-LOC
,	O
understand	O
the	O
only	O
feasible	O
solution	O
for	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
is	O
the	O
acceptance	O
of	O
the	O
status	O
quo	O
.	O

India	B-ORG
keeps	O
what	O
it	O
has	O
while	O
Pakistan	B-ORG
and	O
China	B-ORG
(	O
which	O
was	O
gifted	O
a	O
slice	O
of	O
the	O
territory	O
three	O
decades	O
ago	O
)	O
do	O
likewise	O
.	O

Simultaneously	O
,	O
New	B-ORG
Delhi	I-ORG
would	O
ensure	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
autonomy	O
for	O
the	O
state	O
that	O
would	O
help	O
cut	O
popular	O
support	O
off	O
from	O
jihadis	O
attempting	O
to	O
convert	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
into	O
a	O
second	O
Afghanistan	B-LOC
.	O

Bill	B-PER
Clinton	I-PER
understood	O
this	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
his	O
term	O
in	O
office	O
yet	O
,	O
under	O
Colin	B-PER
Powell	I-PER
(	O
who	O
appears	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
affinity	O
for	O
generals	O
active	O
in	O
politics	O
)	O
,	O
the	O
pendulum	O
of	O
U.S.	B-LOC
policy	O
has	O
once	O
again	O
swung	O
toward	O
a	O
quixotic	O
effort	O
to	O
prize	O
at	O
least	O
the	O
Valley	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Kashmir	I-LOC
loose	O
from	O
India	B-LOC
.	O

This	O
,	O
Pakistan	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
lobbyist	O
in	O
Washington	B-LOC
Christina	B-PER
Rocca	I-PER
has	O
been	O
told	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
"	O
minimum	O
"	O
that	O
the	O
Pakistan	B-ORG
army	O
will	O
accept	O
.	O

It	O
is	O
also	O
far	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
any	O
administration	O
in	O
New	B-LOC
Delhi	I-LOC
can	O
deliver	O
.	O

This	O
writer	O
has	O
for	O
years	O
regarded	O
the	O
best	O
solution	O
to	O
the	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
problem	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
trifurcation	O
of	O
the	O
Indian	B-LOC
part	O
of	O
the	O
state	O
into	O
a	O
Hindu	O
-	O
majority	O
Jammu	B-LOC
,	O
a	O
Buddhist	O
-	O
dominated	O
Ladakh	B-LOC
and	O
the	O
overwhelmingly	O
Muslim	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
Valley	I-LOC
,	O
with	O
the	O
third	O
state	O
given	O
little	O
of	O
taxpayers	O
'	O
money	O
but	O
substantial	O
autonomy	O
.	O

With	O
luck	O
,	O
the	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
Valley	I-LOC
can	O
attract	O
investment	O
from	O
the	O
Middle	B-LOC
East	I-LOC
and	O
other	O
locations	O
where	O
Muslims	O
are	O
dominant	O
and	O
become	O
a	O
tourist	O
,	O
education	O
and	O
services	O
haven	O
within	O
India	B-LOC
.	O

The	O
overwhelming	O
majority	O
of	O
Muslims	O
in	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
would	O
be	O
happy	O
with	O
such	O
an	O
outcome	O
,	O
except	O
for	O
the	O
tiny	O
jihadi	O
segment	O
patronized	O
by	O
the	O
U.S.	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Department	I-ORG
and	O
the	O
Pakistan	B-ORG
Army	I-ORG
,	O
which	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
even	O
the	O
score	O
with	O
India	B-ORG
for	O
their	O
catastrophic	O
defeat	O
in	O
Bangladesh	B-LOC
in	O
1971	O
.	O

Unreported	O
by	O
the	O
international	O
media	O
,	O
the	O
Valley	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Kashmir	I-LOC
has	O
seen	O
an	O
ethnic	O
and	O
cultural	O
genocide	O
that	O
has	O
resulted	O
in	O
the	O
fleeing	O
from	O
the	O
valley	O
of	O
almost	O
all	O
the	O
Hindu	O
families	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
living	O
there	O
since	O
human	O
habitation	O
was	O
first	O
recorded	O
.	O

Over	O
nine	O
dozen	O
temples	O
that	O
had	O
served	O
the	O
Hindu	O
population	O
have	O
been	O
destroyed	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
used	O
as	O
building	O
material	O
and	O
others	O
used	O
as	O
urinals	O
.	O

Thus	O
far	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
many	O
"	O
human	O
rights	O
"	O
busybodies	O
across	O
the	O
world	O
have	O
bothered	O
to	O
even	O
notice	O
such	O
a	O
development	O
.	O

Indeed	O
,	O
their	O
reports	O
are	O
filled	O
with	O
tales	O
of	O
the	O
"	O
atrocities	O
"	O
of	O
Indian	B-LOC
troops	O
on	O
the	O
innocent	O
jihadis	O
.	O

Despite	O
Sept.	B-MISC
11	I-MISC
,	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
still	O
supports	O
the	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
groups	O
that	O
back	O
jihad	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
Washington	B-ORG
is	O
paying	O
to	O
keep	O
Pervez	B-PER
Musharraf	I-PER
happy	O
.	O

Unfortunately	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
general	O
has	O
decided	O
to	O
take	O
seriously	O
Colin	B-PER
Powell	I-PER
's	I-PER
frequent	O
boasts	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
nudging	O
that	O
the	O
Indians	B-LOC
made	O
conciliatory	O
gestures	O
toward	O
Islamabad	B-LOC
.	O

The	O
U.S.	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Department	I-ORG
and	O
the	O
misnamed	O
think	O
tanks	O
that	O
follow	O
its	O
lead	O
have	O
held	O
numerous	O
conferences	O
on	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
and	O
,	O
in	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
solution	O
that	O
has	O
emerged	O
is	O
a	O
valley	O
prized	O
loose	O
from	O
Indian	B-LOC
control	O
and	O
under	O
its	O
own	O
version	O
of	O
Ibrahim	B-PER
Rugova	I-PER
.	O

That	O
India	B-LOC
is	O
not	O
Yugoslavia	B-LOC
and	O
that	O
the	O
"	O
foreigner	O
-	O
led	O
"	O
Indian	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Congress	I-ORG
can	O
least	O
afford	O
to	O
ignore	O
Indian	B-LOC
nationalism	O
,	O
has	O
not	O
struck	O
the	O
conferees	O
,	O
among	O
whom	O
have	O
been	O
several	O
Indian	B-LOC
"	O
scholars	O
"	O
and	O
"	O
analysts	O
"	O
ready	O
to	O
say	O
and	O
endorse	O
anything	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
a	O
free	O
trip	O
to	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
or	O
Vienna	B-LOC
.	O

Despite	O
many	O
wrinkles	O
,	O
India	B-ORG
remains	O
a	O
part	O
-	O
democracy	O
and	O
merely	O
signing	O
on	O
to	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
that	O
calls	O
for	O
an	O
independent	O
Kashmir	B-LOC
does	O
not	O
get	O
you	O
into	O
the	O
trouble	O
that	O
writing	O
an	O
op	O
-	O
ed	O
piece	O
against	O
Sonia	B-PER
Gandhi	I-PER
or	O
Atal	B-PER
Behari	I-PER
Vajpayee	I-PER
would	O
instantly	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
the	O
business	O
community	O
in	O
India	B-LOC
that	O
stepped	O
in	O
after	O
Vajpayee	B-PER
indulged	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
bout	O
of	O
saber	O
rattling	O
in	O
2002	O
,	O
pointing	O
out	O
that	O
the	O
only	O
beneficiary	O
of	O
the	O
mythical	O
perception	O
that	O
war	O
--	O
especially	O
nuclear	O
war	O
--	O
was	O
around	O
the	O
corner	O
in	O
the	O
subcontinent	O
was	O
China	B-ORG
.	O

The	O
reason	O
for	O
this	O
is	O
that	O
India	B-LOC
is	O
emerging	O
as	O
an	O
alternative	O
investment	O
destination	O
to	O
China	B-LOC
,	O
hence	O
the	O
favor	O
that	O
the	O
generals	O
in	O
Islamabad	B-LOC
do	O
to	O
their	O
trusty	O
supplier	O
of	O
nukes	O
and	O
missiles	O
by	O
creating	O
a	O
scare	O
about	O
war	O
involving	O
India	B-ORG
when	O
in	O
fact	O
the	O
real	O
flashpoints	O
are	O
the	O
Taiwan	B-LOC
Straits	I-LOC
and	O
North	B-LOC
Korea	I-LOC
.	O

Since	O
then	O
,	O
India	B-ORG
has	O
talked	O
peace	O
while	O
always	O
signaling	O
that	O
only	O
the	O
status	O
quo	O
would	O
be	O
acceptable	O
as	O
a	O
final	O
settlement	O
:	O
a	O
line	O
of	O
action	O
that	O
is	O
followed	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
disputes	O
with	O
China	B-ORG
as	O
well	O
.	O

Unfortunately	O
for	O
those	O
eager	O
to	O
indefinitely	O
carry	O
on	O
with	O
the	O
lucrative	O
business	O
of	O
conflict	O
resolution	O
in	O
South	B-LOC
Asia	I-LOC
,	O
Pervez	B-PER
Musharraf	I-PER
has	O
now	O
called	O
Colin	B-PER
Powell	I-PER
's	I-PER
bluff	O
,	O
challenging	O
him	O
to	O
deliver	O
on	O
his	O
frequent	O
statements	O
implying	O
that	O
the	O
Indians	B-LOC
jump	O
to	O
his	O
commands	O
.	O

Once	O
the	O
Manmohan	B-PER
Singh	I-PER
government	O
shows	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
little	O
appetite	O
for	O
suicide	O
,	O
Musharraf	B-PER
will	O
face	O
the	O
moment	O
of	O
truth	O
:	O
accept	O
the	O
inevitable	O
,	O
or	O
once	O
again	O
ramp	O
up	O
the	O
insurgency	O
and	O
spawn	O
a	O
fresh	O
lot	O
of	O
killers	O
that	O
can	O
hit	O
not	O
merely	O
Mumbai	B-LOC
and	O
New	B-LOC
Delhi	I-LOC
but	O
London	B-LOC
and	O
Chicago	B-LOC
as	O
well	O
.	O

The	O
one	O
country	O
that	O
has	O
shown	O
that	O
it	O
understands	O
the	O
realities	O
in	O
South	B-LOC
Asia	I-LOC
is	O
China	B-ORG
.	O

Under	O
President	O
Hu	B-PER
Jintao	I-PER
,	O
Beijing	B-ORG
has	O
opened	O
out	O
to	O
New	B-ORG
Delhi	I-ORG
and	O
Prime	O
Minister	O
Wen	B-PER
Jiabao	I-PER
is	O
expected	O
to	O
visit	O
early	O
next	O
year	O
,	O
making	O
friends	O
by	O
formally	O
accepting	O
Sikkim	B-LOC
as	O
part	O
of	O
India	B-LOC
and	O
backing	O
India	B-ORG
as	O
a	O
permanent	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
U.N.	B-ORG
Security	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
--	O
thus	O
leaving	O
Washington	B-ORG
as	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
"	O
permanent	O
five	O
"	O
that	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
done	O
so	O
.	O

With	O
Colin	B-PER
Powell	I-PER
around	O
,	O
the	O
U.S.	B-ORG
has	O
no	O
need	O
of	O
an	O
Osama	B-PER
bin	I-PER
Laden	I-PER

M.D.	B-PER
Nalapat	I-PER
,	O
an	O
expert	O
on	O
jihad	O
,	O
is	O
professor	O
of	O
geopolitics	O
at	O
the	O
Manipal	B-ORG
Academy	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Higher	I-ORG
Education	I-ORG
,	O
India	B-LOC
.	O

Washington	B-ORG
Times	I-ORG
28/10/2004	O

Ok	O
.	O

We	O
all	O
know	O
that	O
John	B-PER
Kerry	I-PER
served	O
in	O
Vietnam	B-LOC
.	O

Four	O
whole	O
months	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
advantage	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
-	O
known	O
,	O
little	O
-	O
invoked	O
regulation	O
that	O
allowed	O
him	O
to	O
desert	O
his	O
"	O
band	O
of	O
brothers	O
"	O
.	O

We	O
also	O
know	O
how	O
Dan	B-PER
Rather	I-PER
libeled	O
George	B-PER
Bush	I-PER
and	O
impugned	O
his	O
service	O
in	O
the	O
Texas	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
National	I-ORG
Guard	I-ORG
on	O
a	O
"	O
60	B-MISC
Minutes	I-MISC
II	I-MISC
"	O
report	O
based	O
largely	O
on	O
forged	O
documents	O
.	O

During	O
his	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Guard	B-ORG
,	O
George	B-PER
Bush	I-PER
flew	O
the	O
F	B-MISC
-	I-MISC
102	I-MISC
Delta	I-MISC
Dagger	I-MISC
fighter	I-MISC
-	I-MISC
interceptor	I-MISC
.	O

The	O
F	B-MISC
-	I-MISC
102	I-MISC
saw	O
service	O
in	O
the	O
Vietnam	B-LOC
theater	O
between	O
March	O
1962	O
and	O
December	O
1969	O
.	O

During	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
F	B-MISC
-	I-MISC
102	I-MISC
squadrons	O
were	O
based	O
out	O
of	O
Tan	B-LOC
Son	I-LOC
Nhut	I-LOC
,	O
Da	B-LOC
Nang	I-LOC
and	O
Bien	B-LOC
Hoa	I-LOC
in	O
Vietnam	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
Udorn	B-LOC
and	O
Don	B-LOC
Muang	I-LOC
in	O
Thailand	B-LOC
.	O

(	O
Click	O
here	O
for	O
source	O
.	O
)	O

As	O
far	O
as	O
George	B-PER
Bush	I-PER
knew	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
unit	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
transferred	O
to	O
Vietnam	B-LOC
.	O

In	O
all	O
this	O
so	O
-	O
called	O
controversy	O
,	O
has	O
anyone	O
considered	O
that	O
perhaps	O
George	B-PER
Bush	I-PER
just	O
wanted	O
to	O
fly	O
jets	O
?	O

And	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
remember	O
,	O
flying	O
supersonic	O
fighter	O
jets	O
is	O
dangerous	O
!	O

They	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
just	O
anybody	O
do	O
it	O
.	O

Some	O
reporters	O
(	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
the	O
ones	O
with	O
journalistic	O
ethics	O
)	O
have	O
actually	O
uncovered	O
the	O
truth	O
about	O
George	B-PER
Bush	I-PER
's	I-PER
service	O
in	O
the	O
Texas	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
National	I-ORG
Guard	I-ORG
.	O

For	O
example	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
George	B-PER
Bush	I-PER
spent	O
considerably	O
more	O
time	O
in	O
uniform	O
than	O
John	B-PER
Kerry	I-PER
?	O

What	O
follows	O
is	O
the	O
text	O
of	O
an	O
e-mail	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
(	O
thanks	O
to	O
Dave	B-PER
Manzano	I-PER
)	O
.	O

Read	O
on	O
to	O
learn	O
the	O
facts	O
.	O

---------	O

Bush	B-PER
’s	I-PER
National	B-ORG
Guard	I-ORG
years	O

Before	O
you	O
fall	O
for	O
Dems	B-ORG
’	O
spin	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
facts	O

What	O
do	O
you	O
really	O
know	O
about	O
George	B-PER
W.	I-PER
Bush	I-PER
’s	I-PER
time	O
in	O
the	O
Air	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Guard	I-ORG
?	O

That	O
he	O
did	O
n’t	O
show	O
up	O
for	O
duty	O
in	O
Alabama	B-LOC
?	O

That	O
he	O
missed	O
a	O
physical	O
?	O

That	O
his	O
daddy	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
?	O

News	O
coverage	O
of	O
the	O
president	O
’s	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
Guard	B-ORG
has	O
tended	O
to	O
focus	O
on	O
one	O
brief	O
portion	O
of	O
that	O
time	O
—	O
to	O
the	O
exclusion	O
of	O
virtually	O
everything	O
else	O
.	O

So	O
just	O
for	O
the	O
record	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
in	O
full	O
,	O
is	O
what	O
Bush	B-PER
did	O
:	O

The	O
future	O
president	O
joined	O
the	O
Guard	B-ORG
in	O
May	O
1968	O
.	O

Almost	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
an	O
extended	O
period	O
of	O
training	O
.	O

Six	O
weeks	O
of	O
basic	O
training	O
.	O

Fifty	O
-	O
three	O
weeks	O
of	O
flight	O
training	O
.	O

Twenty	O
-	O
one	O
weeks	O
of	O
fighter	O
-	O
interceptor	O
training	O
.	O

That	O
was	O
80	O
weeks	O
to	O
begin	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
training	O
periods	O
thrown	O
in	O
as	O
well	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
full	O
-	O
time	O
work	O
.	O

By	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
Bush	B-PER
had	O
served	O
nearly	O
two	O
years	O
.	O

Not	O
two	O
years	O
of	O
weekends	O
.	O

Two	O
years	O
.	O

After	O
training	O
,	O
Bush	B-PER
kept	O
flying	O
,	O
racking	O
up	O
hundreds	O
of	O
hours	O
in	O
F	B-MISC
-	I-MISC
102	I-MISC
jets	O
.	O

As	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
accumulated	O
points	O
toward	O
his	O
National	B-ORG
Guard	I-ORG
service	O
requirements	O
.	O

At	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
guardsmen	O
were	O
required	O
to	O
accumulate	O
a	O
minimum	O
of	O
50	O
points	O
to	O
meet	O
their	O
yearly	O
obligation	O
.	O

According	O
to	O
records	O
released	O
earlier	O
this	O
year	O
,	O
Bush	B-PER
earned	O
253	O
points	O
in	O
his	O
first	O
year	O
,	O
May	O
1968	O
to	O
May	O
1969	O
(	O
since	O
he	O
joined	O
in	O
May	O
1968	O
,	O
his	O
service	O
thereafter	O
was	O
measured	O
on	O
a	O
May	O
-	O
to	O
-	O
May	O
basis	O
)	O
.	O

Bush	B-PER
earned	O
340	O
points	O
in	O
1969	O
-	O
1970	O
.	O

[	O
In	O
other	O
words	O
,	O
Bush	B-PER
earned	O
enough	O
points	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
requirements	O
for	O
his	O
entire	O
six	O
year	O
hitch	O
in	O
1969	O
-	O
1970	O
alone	O
.	O

-	O
acd	O
]	O

He	O
earned	O
137	O
points	O
in	O
1970	O
-	O
1971	O
.	O

And	O
he	O
earned	O
112	O
points	O
in	O
1971	O
-	O
1972	O
.	O

The	O
numbers	O
indicate	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
first	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
Bush	B-PER
not	O
only	O
showed	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
showed	O
up	O
a	O
lot	O
.	O

Did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O

That	O
brings	O
the	O
story	O
to	O
May	O
1972	O
—	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
focus	O
of	O
so	O
many	O
news	O
reports	O
—	O
when	O
Bush	B-PER
“	O
deserted	O
”	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
anti-Bush	B-PER
filmmaker	O
Michael	B-PER
Moore	I-PER
)	O
or	O
went	O
“	O
AWOL	O
”	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
Terry	B-PER
McAuliffe	I-PER
,	O
chairman	O
of	O
the	O
Democratic	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
)	O
.	O

Bush	B-PER
asked	O
for	O
permission	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Alabama	B-LOC
to	O
work	O
on	O
a	O
Senate	B-ORG
campaign	O
.	O

His	O
superior	O
officers	O
said	O
OK	O
.	O

Requests	O
like	O
that	O
were	O
n’t	O
unusual	O
,	O
says	O
retired	O
Col.	O
William	B-PER
Campenni	I-PER
,	O
who	O
flew	O
with	O
Bush	B-PER
in	O
1970	O
and	O
1971	O
.	O

“	O
In	O
1972	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
enormous	O
glut	O
of	O
pilots	O
,	O
”	O
Campenni	B-PER
says	O
.	O

“	O
The	O
Vietnam	B-MISC
War	I-MISC
was	O
winding	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Air	B-ORG
Force	I-ORG
was	O
putting	O
pilots	O
in	O
desk	O
jobs	O
.	O

In	O
’72	O
or	O
’73	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
were	O
a	O
pilot	O
,	O
active	O
or	O
Guard	B-ORG
,	O
and	O
you	O
had	O
an	O
obligation	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
no	O
problem	O
.	O

In	O
fact	O
,	O
you	O
were	O
helping	O
them	O
solve	O
their	O
problem	O
.	O
”	O

So	O
Bush	B-PER
stopped	O
flying	O
.	O

From	O
May	O
1972	O
to	O
May	O
1973	O
,	O
he	O
earned	O
just	O
56	O
points	O
—	O
not	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
enough	O
to	O
meet	O
his	O
requirement	O
.	O

Then	O
,	O
in	O
1973	O
,	O
as	O
Bush	B-PER
made	O
plans	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Guard	B-ORG
and	O
go	O
to	O
Harvard	B-ORG
Business	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
,	O
he	O
again	O
started	O
showing	O
up	O
frequently	O
.	O

In	O
June	O
and	O
July	O
of	O
1973	O
,	O
he	O
accumulated	O
56	O
points	O
,	O
enough	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
minimum	O
requirement	O
for	O
the	O
1973	O
-	O
1974	O
year	O
.	O

Then	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
request	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
given	O
permission	O
to	O
go	O
.	O

Bush	B-PER
received	O
an	O
honorable	O
discharge	O
after	O
serving	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
four	O
months	O
and	O
five	O
days	O
of	O
his	O
original	O
six	O
-	O
year	O
commitment	O
.	O

By	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
accumulated	O
enough	O
points	O
in	O
each	O
year	O
to	O
cover	O
six	O
years	O
of	O
service	O
.	O

During	O
his	O
service	O
,	O
Bush	B-PER
received	O
high	O
marks	O
as	O
a	O
pilot	O
.	O

A	O
1970	O
evaluation	O
said	O
Bush	B-PER
“	O
clearly	O
stands	O
out	O
as	O
a	O
top	O
notch	O
fighter	O
interceptor	O
pilot	O
”	O
and	O
was	O
“	O
a	O
natural	O
leader	O
whom	O
his	O
contemporaries	O
look	O
to	O
for	O
leadership	O
.	O
”	O

A	O
1971	O
evaluation	O
called	O
Bush	B-PER
“	O
an	O
exceptionally	O
fine	O
young	O
officer	O
and	O
pilot	O
”	O
who	O
“	O
continually	O
flies	O
intercept	O
missions	O
with	O
the	O
unit	O
to	O
increase	O
his	O
proficiency	O
even	O
further	O
.	O
”	O

And	O
a	O
1972	O
evaluation	O
called	O
Bush	B-PER
“	O
an	O
exceptional	O
fighter	O
interceptor	O
pilot	O
and	O
officer	O
.	O
”	O

Now	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
natural	O
that	O
news	O
reports	O
questioning	O
Bush	B-PER
’s	I-PER
service	O
—	O
in	O
The	O
Boston	B-ORG
Globe	I-ORG
and	O
The	O
New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
Times	I-ORG
,	O
on	O
CBS	B-ORG
and	O
in	O
other	O
outlets	O
—	O
would	O
come	O
out	O
now	O
.	O

Democrats	B-ORG
are	O
spitting	O
mad	O
over	O
attacks	O
on	O
John	B-PER
Kerry	I-PER
’s	I-PER
record	O
by	O
the	O
group	O
Swift	B-ORG
Boat	I-ORG
Veterans	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Truth	I-ORG
.	O

And	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
with	O
Kerry	B-PER
,	O
it	O
’s	O
reasonable	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
candidate	O
’s	O
entire	O
record	O
,	O
including	O
his	O
military	O
service	O
—	O
or	O
lack	O
of	O
it	O
.	O

Voters	O
are	O
perfectly	O
able	O
to	O
decide	O
whether	O
it	O
’s	O
important	O
or	O
not	O
in	O
November	O
.	O

The	O
Kerry	B-PER
camp	O
blames	O
Bush	B-PER
for	O
the	O
Swift	B-ORG
boat	I-ORG
veterans	I-ORG
’	O
attack	O
,	O
but	O
anyone	O
who	O
has	O
spent	O
much	O
time	O
talking	O
to	O
the	O
Swifties	B-ORG
gets	O
the	O
sense	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
doing	O
it	O
entirely	O
for	O
their	O
own	O
reasons	O
.	O

And	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
noted	O
in	O
passing	O
that	O
Kerry	B-PER
has	O
personally	O
questioned	O
Bush	B-PER
’s	I-PER
service	O
,	O
while	O
Bush	B-PER
has	O
not	O
personally	O
questioned	O
Kerry	B-PER
’s	I-PER
.	O

In	O
April	O
—	O
before	O
the	O
Swift	B-ORG
boat	I-ORG
veterans	I-ORG
had	O
said	O
a	O
word	O
—	O
Kerry	B-PER
said	O
Bush	B-PER
“	O
has	O
yet	O
to	O
explain	O
to	O
America	B-ORG
whether	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
about	O
whether	O
he	O
showed	O
up	O
for	O
duty	O
.	O
”	O

Earlier	O
,	O
Kerry	B-PER
said	O
,	O
“	O
Just	O
because	O
you	O
get	O
an	O
honorable	O
discharge	O
does	O
not	O
,	O
in	O
fact	O
,	O
answer	O
that	O
question	O
.	O
”	O

Now	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Swift	B-ORG
boat	I-ORG
episode	O
,	O
the	O
spotlight	O
has	O
returned	O
to	O
Bush	B-PER
.	O

That	O
’s	O
fine	O
.	O

We	O
should	O
know	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
we	O
can	O
.	O

And	O
perhaps	O
someday	O
Kerry	B-PER
will	O
release	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
military	O
records	O
as	O
well	O
.	O

Byron	B-PER
York	I-PER
is	O
a	O
White	B-LOC
House	I-LOC
correspondent	O
for	O
National	B-ORG
Review	I-ORG
.	O

His	O
column	O
appears	O
in	O
The	O
Hill	B-ORG
each	O
week	O
.	O

One	O
week	O
to	O
elections	O
day	O
and	O
the	O
general	O
atmosphere	O
in	O
the	O
capital	O
is	O
eerie	O
,	O
yet	O
strikingly	O
familiar	O
.	O

I	O
suspect	O
the	O
streets	O
of	O
Baghdad	B-LOC
will	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
a	O
war	O
is	O
looming	O
this	O
week	O
.	O

There	O
is	O
no	O
doubt	O
that	O
many	O
Iraqis	B-LOC
regard	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
30	O
January	O
as	O
a	O
day	O
of	O
renewed	O
hope	O
,	O
one	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
awaiting	O
all	O
their	O
lives	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
many	O
others	O
are	O
already	O
dreading	O
it	O
.	O

The	O
interim	O
government	O
has	O
promised	O
security	O
measures	O
that	O
would	O
reduce	O
the	O
violence	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
elections	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
fail	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
protect	O
all	O
5,000	O
(	O
or	O
so	O
)	O
balloting	O
centres	O
.	O

Many	O
voting	O
centres	O
have	O
already	O
been	O
successfully	O
attacked	O
or	O
destroyed	O
in	O
many	O
areas	O
.	O

Now	O
that	O
the	O
picture	O
is	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
main	O
competing	O
lists	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
Iraqi	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
list	O
and	O
Allawi	B-PER
's	I-PER
Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Iraqiya	I-ORG
list	O
.	O

Ayad	B-PER
Allawi	I-PER
,	O
and	O
other	O
ministers	O
running	O
on	O
his	O
list	O
,	O
have	O
quite	O
expectedly	O
used	O
their	O
governmental	O
positions	O
in	O
campaigning	O
.	O

One	O
minister	O
reportedly	O
handed	O
out	O
100	O
dollar	O
'	O
gifts	O
'	O
to	O
journalists	O
attending	O
a	O
press	O
conference	O
for	O
Allawi	B-PER
,	O
a	O
practice	O
that	O
brings	O
back	O
bad	O
memories	O
to	O
many	O
Iraqis	B-LOC
.	O

Sheikh	O
Naji	B-PER
Al	I-PER
-	I-PER
Abbudi	I-PER
,	O
a	O
spokesman	O
for	O
Sistani	B-PER
,	O
affirmed	O
the	O
claims	O
that	O
the	O
Grand	O
Ayatollah	O
is	O
backing	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
Iraqi	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
list	O
.	O

Indeed	O
,	O
Sistani	B-PER
's	I-PER
agents	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
country	O
have	O
been	O
quite	O
active	O
in	O
educating	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
Shia	O
on	O
the	O
merits	O
of	O
elections	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
led	O
to	O
the	O
assassination	O
of	O
at	O
least	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
.	O

Al	B-PER
-	I-PER
Abbudi	I-PER
stated	O
that	O
"	O
His	O
Emminence	O
"	O
decided	O
to	O
openly	O
support	O
the	O
list	O
because	O
"	O
others	O
"	O
(	O
obviously	O
a	O
reference	O
to	O
Allawi	B-PER
)	O
have	O
been	O
abusing	O
official	O
state	O
positions	O
and	O
media	O
outlets	O
in	O
their	O
campaigning	O
.	O

Again	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
official	O
written	O
statement	O
from	O
Sistani	B-PER
's	I-PER
office	O
confirming	O
this	O
allegation	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
is	O
intentional	O
.	O

Ahmed	B-PER
Al	I-PER
-	I-PER
Chalabi	I-PER
and	O
defense	O
minister	O
Hazim	B-PER
Al	I-PER
-	I-PER
Sha'lan	I-PER
have	O
been	O
engaging	O
in	O
shrill	O
public	O
attacks	O
over	O
the	O
media	O
.	O

Chalabi	B-PER
describing	O
Sha'lan	B-PER
as	O
a	O
"	O
Ba'athist	O
"	O
and	O
a	O
"	O
former	O
double	O
agent	O
for	O
Saddam	B-PER
and	O
the	O
CIA	B-ORG
"	O
,	O
while	O
Sha'lan	B-PER
dismisses	O
Chalabi	B-PER
as	O
a	O
"	O
thief	O
"	O
and	O
an	O
"	O
Iranian	B-LOC
stooge	O
who	O
longs	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
origins	O
by	O
defending	O
Iran	B-LOC
"	O
.	O

One	O
remark	O
made	O
by	O
Sha'lan	B-PER
on	O
Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Arabiya	I-ORG
TV	I-ORG
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
n't	O
say	O
more	O
about	O
Chalabi	B-PER
because	O
he	O
would	O
embarrass	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
viewers	O
almost	O
made	O
me	O
roll	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
an	O
extremely	O
amusing	O
episode	O
,	O
watching	O
Chalabi	B-PER
looking	O
smug	O
and	O
amused	O
,	O
contrasted	O
with	O
Sha'lan	B-PER
,	O
all	O
serious	O
and	O
barely	O
keeping	O
himself	O
from	O
swearing	O
.	O

Fistfights	O
,	O
please	O
.	O

Hazim	B-PER
Al	I-PER
-	I-PER
Sha'lan	I-PER
,	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Sheikh	O
of	O
Al	B-LOC
-	I-LOC
Khaza'il	I-LOC
in	O
Diwaniya	B-LOC
and	O
has	O
the	O
potential	O
to	O
replace	O
former	O
information	O
minister	O
,	O
M.S.	B-PER
Al	I-PER
-	I-PER
Sahaf	I-PER
,	O
in	O
his	O
nonsensical	O
media	O
statements	O
,	O
which	O
can	O
be	O
passed	O
as	O
jokes	O
.	O

The	O
main	O
Kurdish	B-LOC
coalition	O
list	O
(	O
PUK	B-ORG
and	O
KDP	B-ORG
)	O
is	O
barely	O
mentioned	O
outside	O
the	O
Kurdish	B-LOC
region	O
.	O

Even	O
there	O
,	O
many	O
Kurds	B-LOC
look	O
and	O
act	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
grab	O
the	O
chance	O
to	O
vote	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
power	O
.	O

I	O
doubt	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
outcome	O
though	O
.	O

Many	O
Iraqis	B-LOC
,	O
including	O
conservative	O
and	O
religious	O
Iraqis	B-LOC
,	O
are	O
surprisingly	O
rooting	O
for	O
the	O
Iraqi	B-ORG
Communist	I-ORG
party	I-ORG
,	O
probably	O
in	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
counter	O
the	O
influence	O
of	O
Islamists	O
in	O
the	O
forthcoming	O
National	B-ORG
Assembly	I-ORG
.	O

The	O
Communist	B-ORG
party	I-ORG
has	O
the	O
largest	O
number	O
of	O
registered	O
party	O
members	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
and	O
can	O
be	O
considered	O
as	O
the	O
oldest	O
popular	O
political	O
party	O
in	O
Iraq	B-LOC
.	O

Its	O
support	O
base	O
is	O
much	O
larger	O
than	O
what	O
it	O
seems	O
.	O

***	O

Several	O
candidates	O
were	O
assassinated	O
and	O
targeted	O
these	O
last	O
two	O
weeks	O
,	O
others	O
have	O
been	O
forced	O
under	O
threats	O
to	O
withdraw	O
and	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
example	O
of	O
the	O
Islamic	B-ORG
party	I-ORG
.	O

Sectarian	O
tensions	O
are	O
at	O
their	O
highest	O
since	O
April	O
,	O
2004	O
,	O
with	O
Sunni	O
insurgents	O
now	O
openly	O
attacking	O
Husseiniyas	B-PER
and	O
Shia	O
mosques	O
.	O

I	O
had	O
an	O
interesting	O
conversation	O
with	O
a	O
middle	O
-	O
aged	O
taxi	O
driver	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
Fallujah	B-LOC
and	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
relatives	O
in	O
Amiriya	B-LOC
,	O
Baghdad	B-LOC
.	O

After	O
asking	O
me	O
which	O
tribe	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
(	O
thus	O
assessing	O
my	O
sectarian	O
background	O
)	O
he	O
started	O
hurling	O
abuses	O
at	O
the	O
Shia	O
,	O
calling	O
them	O
Persians	B-LOC
,	O
Majoos	O
(	O
fire	O
worshippers	O
)	O
,	O
rabid	O
dogs	O
and	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
other	O
descriptions	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
mention	O
here	O
.	O

He	O
described	O
Allawi	B-PER
's	I-PER
face	O
as	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
f*ed	O
horse	O
and	O
he	O
dismissed	O
the	O
whole	O
government	O
as	O
a	O
band	O
of	O
thieves	O
and	O
traitors	O
.	O

I	O
did	O
n't	O
argue	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
believed	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
viable	O
solution	O
to	O
this	O
mess	O
.	O

He	O
said	O
that	O
resistance	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
commonsense	O
solution	O
.	O

First	O
driving	O
out	O
the	O
Americans	B-LOC
,	O
then	O
fighting	O
the	O
Shia	O
back	O
into	O
submission	O
(	O
as	O
in	O
1991	O
)	O
.	O

Sunni	O
Iraqis	B-LOC
contend	O
that	O
elections	O
are	O
impossible	O
to	O
hold	O
under	O
occupation	O
.	O

Leaving	O
aside	O
the	O
fact	O
that	O
this	O
views	O
conflicts	O
with	O
other	O
historical	O
examples	O
in	O
the	O
region	O
,	O
Sunnis	O
have	O
never	O
offered	O
an	O
alternative	O
choice	O
,	O
which	O
eventually	O
leads	O
one	O
to	O
guess	O
that	O
the	O
opinion	O
held	O
by	O
the	O
Fallujan	B-LOC
taxi	O
driver	O
above	O
is	O
precisely	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
planning	O
to	O
implement	O
.	O

I	O
had	O
another	O
conversation	O
some	O
months	O
ago	O
with	O
a	O
retired	O
Ba'athist	O
old	O
-	O
timer	O
who	O
claimed	O
that	O
Ba'athists	O
have	O
the	O
means	O
to	O
stage	O
a	O
third	O
coup	O
d'etat	O
and	O
return	O
to	O
power	O
within	O
10	O
hours	O
of	O
an	O
American	B-LOC
withdrawal	O
.	O

On	O
sensing	O
my	O
incredulity	O
to	O
his	O
statement	O
he	O
asserted	O
that	O
Ba'athist	O
cells	O
exist	O
in	O
all	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
do	O
have	O
a	O
central	O
command	O
,	O
even	O
though	O
many	O
have	O
formed	O
seperate	O
cells	O
(	O
often	O
under	O
Islamic	O
labels	O
)	O
with	O
their	O
own	O
leaderships	O
.	O

He	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
the	O
training	O
and	O
the	O
funding	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
neighbouring	O
and	O
regional	O
governments	O
.	O

I	O
concur	O
that	O
Ba'athists	O
and	O
former	O
security	O
forces	O
are	O
capable	O
of	O
immediately	O
controlling	O
at	O
least	O
5	O
out	O
of	O
18	O
governorates	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
capital	O
,	O
if	O
Americans	B-LOC
are	O
to	O
be	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
picture	O
entirely	O
.	O

But	O
I	O
also	O
see	O
that	O
as	O
a	O
fatal	O
misconception	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
doing	O
Sunnis	O
harm	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
is	O
going	O
anywhere	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O

Any	O
government	O
that	O
assumes	O
power	O
after	O
the	O
elections	O
also	O
realises	O
this	O
,	O
so	O
not	O
even	O
Sistani	B-PER
is	O
going	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
to	O
withdraw	O
its	O
troops	O
,	O
despite	O
what	O
he	O
is	O
saying	O
now	O
,	O
not	O
until	O
they	O
are	O
ensured	O
the	O
insurgency	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
picture	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
an	O
alternative	O
foreign	O
power	O
(	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
Iran	B-ORG
)	O
to	O
back	O
them	O
up	O
.	O

The	O
only	O
hope	O
now	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
following	O
the	O
elections	O
,	O
the	O
National	B-ORG
Assembly	I-ORG
would	O
offer	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
peace	O
and	O
reconciliation	O
to	O
the	O
dissenting	O
parties	O
.	O

I	O
would	O
suggest	O
going	O
for	O
tribal	O
Sheikhs	O
rather	O
than	O
clerics	O
,	O
since	O
they	O
have	O
the	O
upper	O
hand	O
in	O
their	O
areas	O
and	O
can	O
effectively	O
root	O
out	O
any	O
Ba'athists	O
in	O
their	O
midst	O
in	O
return	O
for	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
sharing	O
power	O
and	O
authority	O
.	O

Many	O
of	O
these	O
Sheikhs	O
have	O
been	O
disenfranchised	O
and	O
abused	O
over	O
the	O
last	O
two	O
years	O
.	O

Very	O
recently	O
,	O
US	B-LOC
forces	O
in	O
Al	B-LOC
-	I-LOC
Anbar	I-LOC
made	O
a	O
terrible	O
blunder	O
by	O
accidentally	O
killing	O
Abdul	B-PER
-	I-PER
Razaq	I-PER
Inad	I-PER
Al	I-PER
-	I-PER
Gu'ud	I-PER
,	O
Sheikh	O
of	O
the	O
Al	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Bu	I-ORG
Nimr	I-ORG
clan	O
from	O
the	O
powerful	O
Dulaym	B-ORG
tribe	O
.	O

Al	B-PER
-	I-PER
Gu'ud	I-PER
had	O
favoured	O
elections	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
good	O
terms	O
with	O
the	O
government	O
.	O

The	O
Gu'ud	B-PER
family	O
even	O
accepted	O
to	O
be	O
offered	O
the	O
seat	O
of	O
Al	B-LOC
-	I-LOC
Anbar	I-LOC
governor	O
some	O
months	O
back	O
.	O

The	O
Al	B-ORG
-	B-ORG
Bu	I-ORG
Nimr	I-ORG
in	O
Ramadi	B-LOC
and	O
Al	B-ORG
-	B-ORG
Qaim	I-ORG
rose	O
in	O
arms	O
against	O
Saddam	B-PER
in	O
the	O
mid-nineties	O
following	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
Thamir	B-PER
Madhlum	I-PER
Al	I-PER
-	I-PER
Dulaymi	I-PER
,	O
an	O
Air	B-ORG
Force	I-ORG
general	O
belonging	O
to	O
their	O
tribe	O
.	O

The	O
revolt	O
took	O
two	O
weeks	O
to	O
be	O
suppressed	O
by	O
the	O
Republican	B-ORG
Guard	I-ORG
.	O

Another	O
bad	O
step	O
was	O
the	O
recent	O
arrest	O
of	O
Sheikh	O
Hassan	B-PER
Al	I-PER
-	I-PER
Lihabi	I-PER
,	O
of	O
the	O
Lihaib	B-ORG
tribe	O
which	O
is	O
scattered	O
between	O
the	O
governorates	O
of	O
Al	B-LOC
-	I-LOC
Anbar	I-LOC
,	O
Mosul	B-LOC
and	O
Salah	B-LOC
Al	I-LOC
-	I-LOC
Din	I-LOC
.	O

Al	B-PER
-	I-PER
Lihaibi	I-PER
was	O
running	O
in	O
elections	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
said	O
to	O
have	O
withdrawn	O
following	O
this	O
incident	O
.	O

I	O
believe	O
national	O
reconciliation	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
only	O
path	O
forward	O
to	O
a	O
new	O
Iraq	B-ORG
.	O

The	O
Shia	O
can	O
not	O
live	O
without	O
the	O
Sunnis	O
,	O
and	O
vice	O
versa	O
.	O

Both	O
have	O
shared	O
this	O
country	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
14	O
centuries	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
possible	O
way	O
that	O
one	O
can	O
live	O
without	O
the	O
other	O
.	O

Even	O
partition	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
possibility	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
clear	O
borders	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
.	O

Remember	O
Luis	B-PER
Posada	I-PER
Carriles	I-PER
?	O

Here	O
's	O
a	O
Miami	B-ORG
Herald	I-ORG
interview	O
with	O
the	O
relaxed	O
terrorist	O
and	O
former	O
CIA	B-ORG
operative	O
in	O
a	O
luxury	O
condo	O
,	O
published	O
yesterday	O
.	O

(	O
"	O
At	O
first	O
I	O
hid	O
a	O
lot	O
.	O

I	O
thought	O
the	O
US	B-LOC
government	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
me	O
.	O

Now	O
I	O
hide	O
a	O
lot	O
less	O
.	O
"	O
)	O

Because	O
of	O
such	O
talk	O
,	O
Posada	B-PER
has	O
been	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
by	O
Immigration	O
officials	O
.	O

I	O
ca	O
n't	O
imagine	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
.	O

Authorities	O
would	O
likely	O
have	O
been	O
happy	O
answering	O
questions	O
about	O
Posada	B-PER
's	I-PER
whereabouts	O
with	O
an	O
indefinite	O
shrug	O
.	O

As	O
recently	O
as	O
last	O
week	O
the	O
official	O
line	O
stated	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
knowledge	O
he	O
had	O
entered	O
the	O
country	O
.	O

But	O
comfortable	O
among	O
the	O
thugs	O
,	O
Posada	B-PER
overplayed	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
embarrassed	O
his	O
old	O
patron	O
,	O
the	O
US	B-LOC
government	O
.	O

And	O
though	O
he	O
'd	O
been	O
a	O
faithful	O
servant	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
such	O
a	O
player	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
away	O
with	O
that	O
.	O

He	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
cue	O
from	O
another	O
bomber	O
some	O
pesky	O
dark	O
-	O
skinned	O
foreigners	O
want	O
extradited	O
,	O
CIA	B-ORG
operative	O
Michael	B-PER
Meiring	I-PER
.	O

Posada	B-PER
should	O
have	O
told	O
any	O
inquisitive	O
journalist	O
at	O
his	O
doorstep	O
something	O
like	O
Meiring	B-PER
told	O
the	O
single	O
American	B-LOC
reporter	O
who	O
bothered	O
following	O
his	O
bloody	O
trail	O
from	O
the	O
Philippines	B-LOC
,	O
that	O
"	O
If	O
this	O
harms	O
me	O
in	O
any	O
way	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
my	O
power	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
"	O

But	O
then	O
,	O
maybe	O
that	O
would	O
n't	O
have	O
saved	O
him	O
either	O
,	O
because	O
Posada	B-PER
is	O
not	O
Meiring	B-PER
.	O

Posada	B-PER
can	O
be	O
given	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
Meiring	B-PER
ca	O
n't	O
.	O

Meiring	B-PER
's	I-PER
crimes	O
are	O
fresh	O
,	O
and	O
wave	O
the	O
false	O
flag	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
"	O
War	B-MISC
on	I-MISC
Terror	I-MISC
.	O
"	O

They	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
Philippines	B-LOC
which	O
,	O
like	O
Pakistan	B-LOC
,	O
is	O
an	O
important	O
and	O
vulnerable	O
node	O
for	O
the	O
business	O
which	O
intelligence	O
agencies	O
and	O
terrorist	O
organizations	O
conduct	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
.	O

(	O
Ask	O
Terry	B-PER
Nichols	I-PER
about	O
the	O
Philippines	B-LOC
.	O
)	O

The	O
bombings	O
implicated	O
Muslims	O
,	O
and	O
exacerbated	O
regional	O
tensions	O
which	O
the	O
Bush	B-PER
regime	O
and	O
its	O
friends	O
wearing	O
the	O
brass	O
in	O
the	O
Philippine	B-LOC
military	O
sought	O
to	O
exploit	O
.	O

Posada	B-PER
's	I-PER
crimes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
must	O
seem	O
like	O
ancient	O
history	O
,	O
especially	O
to	O
a	O
people	O
who	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
their	O
history	O
.	O

And	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
do	O
n't	O
even	O
know	O
their	O
crimes	O
,	O
not	O
even	O
that	O
.	O

But	O
will	O
Posada	B-PER
be	O
given	O
up	O
?	O

I	O
doubt	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
extradited	O
to	O
Venezuela	B-LOC
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
that	O
question	O
could	O
be	O
answered	O
with	O
a	O
Yes	O
.	O

I	O
expect	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
determined	O
that	O
,	O
under	O
"	O
Strong	O
Man	O
"	O
Hugo	B-PER
Chavez	I-PER
,	O
Posada	B-PER
could	O
not	O
be	O
guaranteed	O
a	O
fair	O
trial	O
.	O

The	O
hope	O
may	O
be	O
that	O
Posada	B-PER
can	O
soon	O
be	O
offered	O
to	O
a	O
post-Chavez	B-PER
Allawi	B-PER
-	I-PER
like	I-PER
puppet	O
in	O
Caracas	B-LOC
.	O

Whether	O
such	O
an	O
offer	O
were	O
accepted	O
or	O
declined	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
difference	O
;	O
justice	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
served	O
then	O
.	O

But	O
Posada	B-PER
's	I-PER
nearly	O
80	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Venezuelan	B-LOC
people	O
will	O
ensure	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
vain	O
hope	O
.	O

So	O
instead	O
Posada	B-PER
may	O
be	O
held	O
indefinitely	O
,	O
in	O
comfortable	O
custody	O
.	O

An	O
embarrassment	O
to	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
still	O
,	O
just	O
not	O
as	O
embarrassing	O
as	O
having	O
the	O
old	O
killer	O
strut	O
about	O
Miami	B-LOC
,	O
gloating	O
in	O
his	O
freedom	O
.	O

Meiring	B-PER
is	O
more	O
than	O
an	O
embarrassment	O
.	O

His	O
case	O
threatens	O
the	O
consensus	O
fiction	O
of	O
the	O
"	O
War	B-MISC
on	I-MISC
Terror	I-MISC
.	O
"	O

So	O
his	O
name	O
will	O
remain	O
unspoken	O
.	O

Another	O
connection	O
to	O
Philippine	B-LOC
terror	O
and	O
weapons	O
smuggling	O
-	O
dating	O
from	O
the	O
1980s	O
-	O
is	O
alleged	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
Disposable	B-MISC
Patriot	I-MISC
,	O
by	O
Jack	B-PER
Terrell	I-PER
.	O

Terrell	B-PER
,	O
a	O
CIA	B-ORG
asset	O
originally	O
recruited	O
for	O
the	O
Contra	B-MISC
effort	O
,	O
identifies	O
the	O
man	O
attempting	O
to	O
recruit	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Philippine	B-LOC
scheme	O
as	O
Oliver	B-PER
North	I-PER
...	O

I	O
seem	O
to	O
recall	O
the	O
object	O
was	O
to	O
smuggle	O
explosives	O
.	O

http://www.amazon.ca/exec/obidos/ASIN/0915765381/701-3377456-8181939	B-MISC

I	O
've	O
read	O
the	O
book	O
-	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
first	O
person	O
memoir	O
with	O
the	O
ring	O
of	O
truth	O
,	O
especially	O
since	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
wider	O
context	O
has	O
confirmed	O
the	O
allegations	O
of	O
Contra	B-MISC
drug	O
connections	O
that	O
led	O
to	O
Terrell	B-PER
becoming	O
a	O
target	O
for	O
discrediting	O
by	O
the	O
TWIG	B-ORG
counterintelligence	O
group	O
that	O
ran	O
interference	O
for	O
the	O
Contra	B-MISC
effort	O
,	O
staffed	O
by	O
covert	O
ops	O
types	O
including	O
Ollie	B-PER
North	I-PER
,	O
Robert	B-PER
Owen	I-PER
,	O
Vince	B-PER
Cannistaro	I-PER
and	O
Buck	B-PER
Revell	I-PER
.	O

Peter	B-PER
Dale	I-PER
Scott	I-PER
includes	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
how	O
Terrell	B-PER
's	I-PER
whistleblowing	O
was	O
stifled	O
by	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
book	O
Cocaine	B-MISC
Politics	I-MISC
.	O

...	O
same	O
ole	O
,	O
same	O
ole	O
...	O

Due	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
in	O
the	O
1983	O
case	O
ruling	O
that	O
a	O
CIA	B-ORG
agent	O
could	O
not	O
testify	O
using	O
a	O
pseudonym	O
,	O
therefore	O
opening	O
him	O
to	O
cross-examination	O
by	O
Wilson	B-PER
,	O
the	O
prosecution	O
had	O
a	O
problem	O
.	O

They	O
needed	O
someone	O
that	O
could	O
convince	O
the	O
jury	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
see	O
all	O
relevant	O
documents	O
in	O
CIA	B-ORG
files	O
on	O
Wilson	B-PER
.	O

Wilson	B-PER
was	O
claiming	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
for	O
the	O
CIA	B-ORG
when	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
C	B-MISC
-	I-MISC
4	I-MISC
to	O
Quaddaffi	B-PER
.	O

The	O
prosecution	O
was	O
charging	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
rogue	O
using	O
his	O
contacts	O
from	O
former	O
service	O
in	O
both	O
CIA	B-ORG
and	O
the	O
'	O
Office	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Naval	I-ORG
Intelligence	I-ORG
'	O
.	O

Wilson	B-PER
had	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
show	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
had	O
more	O
than	O
80	O
"	O
non-social	O
contacts	O
"	O
with	O
the	O
CIA	B-ORG
since	O
his	O
retirement	O
in	O
1971	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
prosecution	O
's	O
case	O
in	O
turmoil	O
.	O

Then	O
Charles	B-PER
A.	I-PER
Briggs	I-PER
came	O
to	O
the	O
rescue	O
.	O

Third	O
ranking	O
CIA	B-ORG
officer	O
,	O
Briggs	B-PER
signed	O
a	O
declaration	O
on	O
February	O
3rd	O
,	O
1983	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
November	O
8th	O
,	O
1982	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
authorized	O
a	O
search	O
of	O
CIA	B-ORG
records	O
"	O
for	O
any	O
material	O
that	O
in	O
any	O
way	O
pertains	O
to	O
Edwin	B-PER
P.	I-PER
Wilson	I-PER
,	O
or	O
the	O
various	O
allegations	O
concerning	O
his	O
activities	O
after	O
February	O
28th	O
,	O
1971	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
retired	O
from	O
the	O
CIA	B-ORG
.	O
"	O

The	O
Briggs	B-MISC
Declaration	I-MISC
states	O
that	O
with	O
one	O
exception	O
in	O
1972	O
,	O
Wilson	B-PER
did	O
not	O
work	O
"	O
directly	O
or	O
indirectly	O
"	O
for	O
the	O
CIA	B-ORG
since	O
retiring	O
.	O

http://www.disinfo.com/archive/pages/dossier/id334/pg1/	B-MISC

Last	O
week	O
,	O
Federal	O
District	O
Judge	O
Lynn	B-PER
Hughes	I-PER
in	O
Huston	B-LOC
,	O
Texas	B-LOC
,	O
threw	O
out	O
Wilson	B-PER
's	I-PER
two	O
-	O
decades	O
old	O
conviction	O
.	O

Judge	O
Hughes	B-PER
wrote	O
:	O
`	O
government	O
knowingly	O
used	O
false	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
'	O
concluding	O
`	O
honesty	O
comes	O
hard	O
to	O
government	O
.	O
'	O

http://www.bigeye.com/111003.htm	B-MISC

http://www.thekcrachannel.com/news/4503872/detail.html	B-MISC

looks	O
like	O
it	O
is	O
rearing	O
its	O
head	O
again	O
in	O
Louisianna	B-LOC
..	O

Former	O
Pastor	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Implicated	O
In	O
Church	O
Child	O
Sex	O
Abuse	O

PONCHATOULA	B-LOC
,	O
La.	B-LOC
--	O

Sheriff	O
's	O
deputies	O
in	O
Louisiana	B-LOC
made	O
a	O
third	O
arrest	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
the	O
ongoing	O
investigation	O
of	O
a	O
case	O
involving	O
allegations	O
of	O
sexual	O
abuse	O
of	O
children	O
and	O
animals	O
at	O
a	O
Ponchatoula	B-LOC
,	O
La.	I-LOC
,	O
church	O
.	O

Austin	B-PER
Aaron	I-PER
Bernard	I-PER
III	I-PER
,	O
36	O
,	O
was	O
arrested	O
on	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
aggravated	O
rape	O
of	O
a	O
child	O
under	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
13	O
.	O

Police	O
said	O
Bernard	B-PER
confessed	O
to	O
detectives	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sex	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
girl	O
in	O
November	O
2002	O
and	O
admitted	O
to	O
knowing	O
about	O
sexual	O
acts	O
involving	O
children	O
and	O
a	O
dog	O
that	O
occurred	O
at	O
Hosanna	B-LOC
Church	I-LOC
.	O

Tangipahoa	B-LOC
Parish	I-LOC
sheriff	O
's	O
deputy	O
Christopher	B-PER
Blair	I-PER
Labat	I-PER
,	O
24	O
,	O
was	O
booked	O
Tuesday	O
on	O
one	O
count	O
of	O
aggravated	O
rape	O
and	O
one	O
count	O
of	O
crime	O
against	O
nature	O
.	O

On	O
Monday	O
,	O
Louis	B-PER
Lamonica	I-PER
,	O
45	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
pastor	O
of	O
Hosanna	B-ORG
Church	I-ORG
,	O
was	O
booked	O
with	O
two	O
counts	O
of	O
aggravated	O
rape	O
and	O
one	O
count	O
of	O
crime	O
against	O
nature	O
after	O
he	O
walked	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Livingston	B-ORG
Parish	I-ORG
Sheriff	O
's	O
Office	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
implicate	O
others	O
in	O
a	O
situation	O
at	O
the	O
church	O
that	O
reportedly	O
occurred	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O

We	O
have	O
a	O
similar	O
case	O
unravelling	O
up	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
northwest	O
with	O
a	O
murder	O
of	O
a	O
family	O
and	O
missing	O
children	O
taken	O
for	O
some	O
purpose	O
.	O

If	O
I	O
was	O
Rummy	B-PER
I	O
'd	O
send	O
Posada	B-PER
to	O
Iraq	B-LOC
to	O
blow	O
things	O
up	O
there	O
.	O

yeah	O
,	O
"	O
things	O
"	O
...	O

Yesterday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
Posada	B-PER
story	O
was	O
featured	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
television	O
news	O
show	O
in	O
Germany	B-LOC
(	O
ARD	B-ORG
,	O
Tagesthemen	B-MISC
)	O
.	O

The	O
newly	O
released	O
papers	O
,	O
showing	O
him	O
complicit	O
in	O
the	O
airliner	O
bombing	O
,	O
were	O
mentioned	O

gandalf	B-PER

Now	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
post	O
I	O
can	O
relate	O
to	O
.	O

You	O
really	O
got	O
me	O
thinking	O
,	O
I	O
enjoy	O
reading	O
this	O
blog	O
.	O

I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
others	O
feel	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'm	O
definitely	O
looking	O
into	O
immigration	O
to	O
Canada	B-LOC
as	O
an	O
option	O
.	O

The	O
good	O
Ã³l	O
US	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
A	I-LOC
ai	O
nt	O
what	O
it	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
.	O

I	O
like	O
yuor	O
blog	O
.	O

Please	O
check	O
out	O
my	O
who	O
let	O
the	O
dog	O
out	O
blog	O
.	O

hey	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
great	O
blog	O
,	O
I	O
also	O
have	O
a	O
site	O
about	O
los	B-LOC
angeles	I-LOC
online	O
dating	O

you	O
can	O
check	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
los	B-LOC
angeles	I-LOC
online	O
dating	O

This	O
is	O
a	O
excellent	O
blog	O
.	O

Keep	O
it	O
going	O
.	O

This	O
may	O
be	O
of	O
interest	O
to	O
you	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
free	O
online	O
dating	O
service	O
.	O

It	O
pretty	O
much	O
covers	O
dating	O
stuff	O
.	O

I	O
'll	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
.	O

Hey	O
I	O
just	O
love	O
your	O
blog	O
.	O

I	O
also	O
have	O
a	O
dating	O
advice	O
blog	O
/	O
site	O
.	O

I	O
mostly	O
deals	O
with	O
dating	O
advice	O

Please	O
come	O
and	O
check	O
it	O
out	O
if	O
you	O
get	O
the	O
time	O
!	O

I	O
was	O
searching	O
for	O
dog	O
food	O
info	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
post	O
.	O

I	O
agree	O
totally	O
!	O

Paul	B-PER

How	O
Would	O
You	O
Like	O
To	O
Know	O
How	O
YOU	O
Can	O
Live	O
In	O
A	O
Beautiful	O
NEW	O
House	O
That	O
Is	O
Custom	O
-	O
Designed	O
To	O
YOUR	O
Specifications	O
.........	O
And	O
At	O
NO	O
COST	O
To	O
You	O
?	O

You	O
CAN	O
Do	O
It	O
.	O

And	O
It	O
's	O
Not	O
Hard	O
To	O
Do	O
....	O
IF	O
You	O
Know	O
HOW	O
.	O

Do	O
n't	O
Let	O
This	O
Pass	O
You	O
By	O
Without	O
At	O
Least	O
Taking	O
A	O
Look	O
.	O
